Not Yet Alive
A road opens as you tread along it.
A road that doesn't open isn't a road.
Roads are open to everyone.
But not everyone can have the roads.
- Mr. Jang Geu Rae.
- Did you find him?
Cairo Hotel.
I'll see you at the hotel entrance.
Mr. Jang Geu Rae!
Oh!
You were right.
We thought he'd be
in a premium hotel.
That's why we couldn't find him
in all the Jordan hotels.
It wasn't sold yet, right?
Right, let's hope it
ends in a civil way.
Let's go.
Maybe he checked out.
Mr. Seo.
Mr. Seo!
Geu Rae!
Roads are open to everyone.
But not everyone can have the roads.
[Misaeng]
[Please rinse yourself before
entering the public tub, thank you.]
[Spring, 2012]
[Episode 1]
Wow.
Wrap up now.
Being too fussy is an illness.
Yes, sir.
Uh…
Mr. Jang's leg is all better now.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Then tomorrow he'll come in…?
It's time you quit.
Will you do dead-end
part-time jobs forever?
You got discharged from
the army ages ago.
Are you looking for a job?
Yes.
It's hard, huh?
Should I look for
a go club opening?
No.
But that's what you
know how to do…
It's ok.
Alright.
Take your daily pay.
You still work as a driver
early in the morning?
Yes.
Alright.
I'll be there in a couple minutes.
Where are you exactly?
Huh?
It's ok.
Go straight from Shinnonhyeon
Station exit no. 6, then what?
Yes.
I'll be right there, sir.
A young guy should work hard...
...not sit behind the comfy wheel.
You can't get my money that easily.
Take that.
I'm so worried about
Korea, I can't sleep.
This is only $50…
Mom.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Are you still working?
Go to bed.
I'm getting a call, bye.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
I got a call from there
this evening.
They want you to start tomorrow.
The old suit is too small, isn't it?
That will be better.
That's the best suit
among your dad's.
Just wear it for today.
I'll buy you a new one.
Buy a cheap one.
Of course.
A cheap new suit.
Be confident.
You're super smart.
You were the top in your class.
You thought way
ahead of your peers.
Don't think I bribed them.
Nothing like that happened.
Mom.
Spell "bribe."
Does that start with a "v" or a "b"?
It's ok.
Sungwon's CEO wouldn't
have given them...
...your referral if you weren't good.
I'm sure they checked
you out thoroughly.
So be confident!
Hey, come here.
Yes, here it is.
Look at this.
Do a better job.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Yes.
Come out.
Your name was...?
Jang Geu Rae.
R-E?
No, R-A-E.
Your age?
26.
You only got your GED.
Yes.
Did you drop out of
high school or something?
I didn't go.
Why not?
Any work experience?
Any foreign languages?
No.
I have a CA license.
Computer application?
Yes.
Good job.
That's it?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Ok.
I'm Kim Dong Sik
in Sales team 3.
Assistant Manager.
Let's go.
What did you do for 26 years?
You can't do anything?
That's rare these days.
Let's go.
I know.
What did I do for 26 years?
Amazing.
You ok?
You choked yourself.
I can't watch this!
Ouch.
It's ready.
Ok.
Must we do this?
You think this is
the only way, right?
Yes, that's what I think.
I think differently.
The Lux & Rich CEO might not
like you approaching like this.
I'll give it a go.
You wore that.
Breast pads…
Amazing.
I'll be right there.
Ok.
Good job.
She took it out right away.
You sure she's only an intern
who's here 10 days?
She's the best intern.
Erase the visuals from
your head, ok?
Of course.
I'll delete that from my memory.
Please send it to me, sir.
I'll check and confirm right away.
Thank you.
Bye.
Thank you, One Inter…
Hi, sir.
Did you get home ok last night?
Yes.
Of course, I'm fine.
Mr. Oh will be here tomorrow.
The company wanted to
know how much...
...stock will be necessary
for next month.
Please check and let me know.
Thank you.
Where was it?
Why are you standing around?
Ok.
Catalog…
There it is.
What?
This is the only brochure?
Geez.
This is Dong Sik.
How come you sent
just this brochure?
Yes.
There's no inner paper.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
You should have in
come today, boss…
What?
Why do you keep moving about?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
Go make copies.
Sure.
I'm sure you've made copies
in the past 26 years.
Uh, is this the copy machine?
Over there, that way.
Ok.
How many copies?
One each.
- Thank you, One Inter…
- It's me.
Did you get the extra help?
No?
Oh, HR said they'd
send him over.
Yes, he's here.
Yes.
Yeah?
From where?
Who is it?
From the "strings" team.
As in he pulled some of them.
What are you saying?
The intern used his connections.
An intern?
Yes.
He's one of a kind these days.
Yeah?
Don't you think the HR
team is going too far?
[Error]
[Add paper]
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
How do I add more paper?
Open the cabinet down there.
Thanks.
Uh…
There's no paper.
Then you can get it
from the supply room.
Where is that?
Turn right, go straight,
then to your right.
Thank you.
Sure.
Hello.
That must be him.
What do you mean?
Connections.
No wonder.
You're taking all day.
Where are you?
Why are you bringing all that?
Move.
Thank you.
- Give it to me, I'll do it.
- I will.
No, I'll do it.
Then do it.
Why'd you put in your hand?
It's ok.
I said I'd do it.
Just bring that.
What are you doing?
You're driving me nuts.
You haven't made a single
copy for 26 years?
I'm sorry.
You're An Young Yi
in Fabric 3, right?
Yes.
This is Jang Geu Rae,
a rare intern.
Have lunch with him.
I have to go out.
Have him meet the other interns.
Ask her any questions you have.
Get familiar.
Clear that away.
Yes, sir.
Product... backship... is requested…
Will you answer that?
Hello?
I'd like to speak to Mr. Kim.
He's not here right now.
Then give me Mr. Oh.
Huh?
Isn't it Sales team 3?
It is, but Mr. Oh…
Hold on, please.
Who's Mr. Oh?
Over there.
He's on a business trip.
Mr. Oh's on a business trip.
When will he be back?
Uh…
- Just a moment.
- This is annoying.
Hello?
Hi, this is Yuri
Chossudovsky of Cell Bio.
Hello?
I've called regarding
the germanium dishes.
Let me talk to the person in charge.
Huh?
Can you answer that?
There's a call and
I can't understand.
I don't know anything
about Sales team 3.
Ask someone else.
Um…
Please.
Sorry, Sales team 3…
I'm sorry.
Yes, but the person in charge
has stepped away.
Germanium dish samples…
Yes…
Yuri Chossudovsky of Cell Bio.
Yes, we'll get back to you ASAP.
Thank you.
Give this to him when
he comes back.
Um…
Thank you.
I thought that was the end.
But it was only the beginning.
Hel…
Tha, thank you, Sales team 3.
- Hello, Mr. Kim?
- Here
I don't know.
Hello?
Answer me.
Huh?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's English this time.
Self-esteem.
Saving face.
Pride.
These are not the issue here.
I have to swallow all that.
I'm a duck.
Ducks…
Ducks think the first thing
they see is their mom.
Is that true?
Did you feed them?
I'm a duckling.
That's enough.
I'm busy with my work.
I'm sorry.
If someone calls, just tell them
they're away and get their contact number.
- Is that ok…?
- Yes, it's ok.
- What about foreign calls?
- Foreign calls…
Just hang up on them.
Hang up?
Yes, just hang up.
Check today's data and
send me the report.
The updates are late.
You know me.
- Mr. Ha.
- Yes.
What's with this email?
Oh, that.
Cameroon's complaint.
I know that.
But isn't it from last month?
What's wrong with you?
Shall we go for a smoke?
Why, you!
I finished the presentation
material.
I sent it to your emails.
Already?
What presentation?
About the African resource
development investment business…
He said he was a presentation
pro in college.
I saved it as PPTX and
PPT files just in case.
I sent it as a PDF file too,
for your convenience.
[African resource development
investment business]
Size 14, Gothic font.
The subtitles are
size 15 Malgun Gothic.
Let me know if you don't like it.
I like it.
He's useful.
How about noodles for lunch?
Sure.
Shouldn't you make
reservations for eight?
I made reservations for
Shinae and Shiheim.
Which would you like?
I overheard them talking
and called them.
I'll cancel one after you decide.
Baek Ki, you'll fit in great here.
Pass the intern presentation
and come to our team.
So, that's him.
Mr. Oh's intern.
I don't know who he is,
but he used connections.
Someone made it into an ivy league...
...school by writing to the president.
The desperate reason why
he had to get in moved him.
You know what happened?
He dropped out after a semester.
Why?
Because he couldn't keep up.
He only has a GED
and no experience.
How do you know?
HR.
Treat him well.
He won't last long anyway.
Uh…
Yes.
I usually eat lunch alone.
I see.
And…
Young Yi.
I heard you pulled it off.
You're really racing
ahead of us.
I'm Jang Baek Ki.
Resource team intern.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
Please excuse me.
Uh…
You joined late.
We started 10 days ago.
I see.
It…
…just happened that way.
Ask me if you have
any questions.
Like where the paper is…
The whereabouts…
You saw me.
You see everything here.
But they can't tend to it.
Everyone's so busy.
Yes, I've learned that.
But…
…you must be nervous.
You can take off your jacket.
I forgot.
Yes.
[New product]
Who is it for, ma'am?
How much is this new one?
$824 for the whole suit.
Is that made with gold thread?
There's no difference from this.
The brand doesn't matter.
Let's go for lunch.
- What shall we have?
Pasta?
No way, bean paste stew.
You always have that.
Yes.
Aren't you going for lunch?
Oh, I'm not very hungry.
Are you a mama's boy?
You can't do anything
by yourself?
You can't eat alone or…
I'm not that stupid.
I'm really not hungry.
I guess I'm nervous.
Come in.
Thanks.
Sorry, no room.
Go ahead.
It's him.
He must have great connections to
have become an intern without a test.
He must have a great resume.
Maybe he went to
an ivy league school.
Ivy league schools must
be easy to get into.
Anyway this is unfair.
It's not fair at all!
Hopefully they won't give special
treatment to full-time employees.
Young Yi is already enough.
Speak of the devil.
Geu Rae!
Come on over.
- Bon appetite.
- Thanks.
I'm Kim Seok Ho in
the team next to yours.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
Hi.
Geu Rae.
Come to our intern study group.
Oh, sure.
Why would he join us?
Huh?
Yes, Young Yi doesn't come either.
No. 1's don't need study groups.
Where did you go for college?
Harvard?
Stanford?
Or maybe your family is rich?
I'm a curious person, you know.
I only have a GED.
That's shocking.
Our company doesn't care
about educational backgrounds?
You're late, Young Yi.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Today's kimchi stew is
really good.
I'll have pollack stew.
So that's why he
kept following her.
Can I have a seat?
You eat well alone.
Sorry about before.
Sure.
Huh?
People usually say "It's ok."
You say "Sure" when
no wrong was done.
I'm so mad.
We studied so hard to
make it in as interns.
We busted our behinds.
No, Baek Ki?
Huh?
You're right.
To improve our resume.
You said so too.
You were a senior when
we were freshmen, right?
Yeah.
A lot of us are from the same schools.
Mr. Lee in IT is from mine.
I wonder what his family is like.
He doesn't look all that rich.
Anyway, you can
tell his face value.
Do companies still have
preferential hirings for the poor?
This may sound arrogant...
...but I feel cheated.
Why did I join a company
that would hire someone like him?
Maybe our school is a bit tough to
get into, but isn't this too much?
Hey.
You are being arrogant, alright.
Just treat him well.
He can't stay here much longer.
There's no position for him.
But I feel so cheated.
We really busted our behinds.
Cheers!
There's no position for him.
A road opens as
you travel along.
A road that doesn't
open isn't a road.
Roads are open to everyone.
But not everyone
can have the roads.
You didn't think it's because of this?
I mean the reason you keep failing
the contest with your great skill.
Master.
Quit your part-time job.
I know you're poor and
your dad is sick.
But you can't make it like this.
This is your last year as
a Korea Go Club student.
It'll be harder for you if you don't
make it this year either.
So quit your job, Geu Rae.
[Mom]
My road ended there.
[107th Student Championship Contest]
It's not because
I lacked skills or luck.
Or because I had
a part-time job on the side.
Or because my parents
couldn't support me.
Or because my mom
became bedridden...
...after my dad passed away.
That would
be too painful.
So I want to think I didn't
work hard enough.
I want to think that way,
even if it isn't true.
I ended up here because
I didn't work hard.
I was abandoned because
You'll have to wear
that one more day.
I was too busy to buy one.
Take your time.
Why are your eyes red?
I couldn't sleep because of you.
You were tossing and
turning all night.
I couldn't sleep because
of your snoring.
Bye.
[Employees emergency contact number]
I'm used to the lobby already.
Hello.
I was ready for the rat race.
How about you?
Yes, Mr. Oh arrived
at the airport.
Now?
Ok.
I'm going nuts.
Henry said he would come
tomorrow, why today?
Hello.
Call Mr. Oh.
You don't know.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Right, I told you.
Hello.
Hey, man.
I said I was coming in today.
Why'd they send him today too?
There was a miscommunication.
9:30, Kings Hotel café.
I can't make it!
It's rush hour!
I was told you have to be there,
no matter what.
I have to leave soon
because of the...
...squids and come back tonight.
Bye.
Traffic report in the morning.
Today's traffic is heavy.
The 405 is extremely jammed.
The right side of Olympic Highway is...
500 meters in 30 minutes.
Huh?
Oh, no.
It's taking forever!
Where are you?
Dong Sik.
We have to get accustomed
to the unfamiliar.
That way we can have
a new experience.
We should move a step
away from the fear.
Sir, I was told you have to be on
your toes or you'll be fired.
I'm currently moving 12km/hour.
8km away from the meeting location.
I need 50 more minutes.
I'll be 30 minutes late
for the meeting.
30 minutes?
I'll hang up for a minute.
Bye.
What's the department
manager's number?
Where is it?
Here you go.
Ok.
Department Manager...
Hi, this is Dong Sik.
Mr. Oh will be 30…
Huh?
But…
He doesn't know anything.
Yes, sir.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
You have to go.
Huh?
Crazy, huh?
But there's no other way.
Ok.
You have to be with him
until Mr. Oh gets there.
Here, ginseng…
Ging…
Ginseng sample rice cakes.
Here.
Show them you're useful even if
you weren't for the past 26 years.
Go.
Ok.
Show him the…
Never mind. He can't.
What?
Yay!
Never mind.
What's good?
Maybe I'll write letters
of apology in advance.
For me and Mr. Oh.
I'm in deep trouble.
It'll help if I write proper letters.
I knew it.
Would I…
You have to be with him.
…have a solution?
Hey!
How could you send him?
Dang!
He can't even speak English!
He already left with the car,
the rest is up to fate.
Bye.
Let's see if he pulls it off or not.
What's he doing?
Quiz?
Go, sir.
Go?
Go, right?
No, "baduk."
You taught him go?
Yes.
You're good?
No.
I know up to here.
That's only thing I can do.
I was saved by the bell.
Interesting kid.
Ok.
I understand you have a GED.
But you can't speak any foreign
languages or have any skills or specifications.
That's rare these days.
What did you do
before you came here?
Nothing, sir.
So you want to start now at 26?
Yes.
You know you're really lucky?
Huh?
I wouldn't have let them hire you
had I been there.
Even if you were Obama's son.
I need someone to get the
buyer to sign a contract now.
Someone we don't have to teach.
I'm sorry.
I can have you fired right away.
Mr. Oh.
Captivate me.
Huh?
Sell yourself.
What have you got?
My something.
My one thing.
Nothing?
Something I'm good at.
- Nothing, right?
- Effort.
So…
I've never worked hard,
so my effort...
...is unused and
ultra brand new.
Say what?
I'll work hard.
I'll do my best.
I'm not buying you.
Hi.
Hi, Dong Sik.
It went fine.
It worked out.
Regarding the complaint
from Malaysia…
We can't pay for that!
What?
It was that contract.
I'm right.
That was sufficient, you know.
No, it was their fault,
so we won't pay.
Who do they take us for?
Yeah.
Bye.
You know why I'm not buying?
Hard-working guys are
everywhere at work.
So you're no different.
My effort is different.
Yeah?
How so?
The quality.
Huh?
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Quantity too.
Ok, let's see how
different you are.
This is our team's data.
The folders are there,
so organize it.
Yes.
Can you do it?
Yes, sir.
- Go on.
- Yes.
Ultra brand new effort with
high quality and quantity?
It's a new product, right?
Yes, it is.
You can pay in 6 months'
installments.
I don't have a credit card.
You're sure it's new?
It's all mixed up.
But…
…even that could come in handy.
Decide on a topic first...
...and add the content as you go.
There are some iffy files...
...which don't belong to anywhere.
Mom!
What brings you here?
I'm busy now.
Change into this.
Mom.
You'll see when you
become a dad.
When your kid suffers,
you can't stop crying.
I'll get going.
Take a taxi.
Yeah, right.
Have you eaten?
Of course!
Young Yi.
She gave it, huh?
Hi.
Your team pulled it off.
- Mr. Oh.
- Just sit down.
Thank you for this.
No problem.
You have something to say?
Nothing.
- Hey.
- Yes.
- You know what team I'm in, right?
You know we do
everything, right?
You can learn a lot.
Yes.
Keep that in your mind
when your internship ends.
Think "I want Sales team 3."
So long.
Bye.
When your kid suffers...
...you can't stop crying.
How are things going?
You even know what you're doing?
I'm doing my best.
That's for school.
Here you just bring the results.
Yes, sir.
Dong Sik.
We'll have to check
the fermented squid.
Why?
They mixed octopus in again?
- Yes, there's a problem here.
- Again.
They might have mixed
in frozen octopus.
Why, those octopus idiots!
They're denying it, but
I think they are pranking us.
We need to check it today.
Ok.
Tell them we're manually checking and if
it's mixed, we'll stop working with them.
Ok.
Huh?
Manually?
There's not enough people there.
- I'll tell each team leader, don't worry.
- What? But...
Why, those octopus idiots!
Is the manager in now?
Shall I call him?
He's connected.
Hi sir, this is Sang Sik.
Where are you?
I have to tell you something.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
I saw the request for help
with the octopus case.
- Squid case.
- You must be so busy.
You just came back from abroad.
I'm on my toes already.
How come you have to cover
for all the employees?
Aren't they hiring more people?
Oh, they hired someone, right?
Yes.
Send me someone good.
We're going to send fermented
seafood to the U.S.
If frozen octopus is mixed in,
is it fermented squid or octopus?
It doesn't matter which
is more expensive.
The purity of the product is key.
If octopus is mixed in, octopus
would embarrass One International.
Find all the octopus.
What's with you?
I didn't ask you to sell
coolers in Siberia.
Yes.
Baek Ki.
I'll call the factory, so proceed.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, I'm confused.
Is this our job?
I heard you help when
they lack manpower.
Yeah, one guy requested
to work at a site.
But not a fermented
seafood factory.
But Young Yi doesn't have to go
since she's a woman?
Her team leader had them go.
See?
There are other kind of people for this.
Yes, sir.
Alright.
Bye.
What's this?
Mr. Oh.
Geu Rae.
What's with this?
Where's the one I made?
I made it different to
organize the iffy files.
Will that be ok?
No.
You have no friends, huh?
Huh?
It looks like a diary for yourself.
I didn't have high hopes anyway.
Geu Rae.
Let's go.
Sorry we lack work uniforms.
We can't work like this.
Why'd you come then?
Make sure to keep it clean.
It's cold, so you'll need your clothes.
Follow me.
There's no time and
we can't help it either.
There are three 3.5-ton
and two 4.5-ton trucks.
Go in pairs and check
for them inside.
Do it ASAP before
the seafood goes bad.
Get into pairs.
Come on.
It'll be tough by yourself.
Go on in.
There are fewer here.
Come on.
It's freezing.
It stinks.
I didn't study TOEIC to do this.
I know.
I don't like this company.
Let's take our time.
Octopus.
Geez.
Hello?
Hi, Mr. Oh.
Yes, sir.
I'll do that.
Let's go.
Huh?
The Chinese company admitted
to their wrongdoing.
Sales team 3 will treat
us for the hard work.
We better hurry to the sauna.
I'll tell Geu Rae…
- You don't know the sauna, do you?
- No.
Tell Geu Rae and
come in that car.
Me?
Man…
He's working so hard.
He should at least work hard.
Geu Rae…
Hey.
Let's go, Geu Rae.
We called you.
Let's make an unforgettable
memory for him.
Where's Geu Rae?
He's still working.
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
He won't pick up.
Please leave a message…
I'll call the factory.
We shouldn't have done that.
You thought Baek Ki
wouldn't know?
Huh?
You're still here?
Hey!
Oh, my!
Yes!
Didn't you hear the news?
Look.
They're all gone.
Why are you still here?
Gone?
They left long ago after they heard
they don’t have to do it.
Gosh, all the cars are gone too.
How come only you're left here?
We have no cars and it's
hard to catch taxis here.
How come only you're left here?
Geu Rae…
Hello.
Hello?
You're still working?
Come on.
Geu Rae's here.
Oh, put him on.
Here.
Hello?
Why didn't you pick up?
It's Geu Rae.
Geu Rae.
He must've made it.
Yes, it so happened.
The factory owner told you?
It was a prank.
Sorry, Geu Rae!
Newcomers go through that.
Come with Young Yi.
Can I talk to her?
He must've been
searching till now.
He's a fool.
Hello?
Yes, I know.
He said, come together.
You want to go?
Yes.
I'll see the end of this.
Oh…
You stink.
Geu Rae.
You should've washed up.
Did you get some for the pay?
Why didn't you pick up?
I called so many times.
Where's Mr. Oh? I have to report...
He'll come back soon.
You stink.
Go wash up at a sauna.
What's with him?
But your clothes stink.
Why'd you work so hard?
You should've been
smart about it.
I guess you'll have
to work hard at least.
Keep working hard.
Let's go in.
I have to go since it's late.
I just came to say bye.
Mr. Oh.
Hi.
Hello.
Good job.
I'll get going.
Bye.
Hello.
What's with you?
Something happened.
What?
I have to wrap up
some work too.
I came to say bye.
What do you have…
You're going for that?
Yes, I'll redo it since I messed up.
You can do it tomorrow.
So go eat or go home.
Don’t go back to work.
It's ok.
It'll be ready for tomorrow.
You say I work hard?
No.
I'm here now because
I didn't work hard.
I was abandoned because
[Misaeng]
You know whose
connections he used?
Who?
Let's go it.
Executive director.
Did you decide on your partner?
You have everything
other interns want.
You're popular.
Make sure you know
who approaches you.
I'm Han Suk Yool of
the Fabric team.
We got in trouble
because of that!
It feels weird watching that.
It makes me want to do well.
Then what should I do?
You can teach me.
Give me a chance.
I don't support a world where those
with no basics get on the escalator.
Get out, dude!
I'm alone here too.