Not Yet Alive
Hello.
Baek Ki.
Have you seen Geu Rae?
No.
Have you heard about Mr. Park?
I guess you haven't.
Geu Rae…
Geu Rae, what happened?
Thank you.
I didn't do it for that.
What, what?
What is it, what is it?
The Audit team is here.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 11]
Mr. Oh, we'll take
Mr. Park's belongings.
Yes.
Go ahead.
What will happen to Mr. Park?
Apparently, it's the biggest
scandal in the company's history.
What will happen to... Mr. Kim?
The concerns became reality.
Mr. Jung of Resource 2 Team
was called as witness.
Mr. Park's bosses at the time,
Mr. Cho Won Jin and Mr. Shin
Jae Min were called as well.
Mr. Kim Suk Man was audited too.
And…
…Mr. Kim couldn't evade
responsibility either.
Please forgive me this once, sir.
Jong Sik.
Yes, sir.
That was nothing, right?
A trading man could become
a conman or gambler at times.
Yes, because
you have to make things work.
Thanks for my daughter's wedding.
Excuse me?
Don't mention it.
You came straight from the airport.
I remember you out of breath.
I hurried over from a business trip.
Yeah.
You were that type of guy.
A bit late, but you always made it.
But this time… you're late.
Too late.
I heard Mr. Kim Suk Man
already resigned.
[Personnel appointment: Kim Suk Man,
Cho Won Jin => Assigned to Fabric Chemicals
Kim Boo Ryun => Aluminum, Shin
Jae min => Distribution Center]
This is demotion.
Yeah?
Wow, half of Mr. Choi's
men are sent away.
Sir.
I'll contact you when things get
settled. You can treat me to soju.
You…
You and Jang Mi.
I heard you're getting married.
Yes.
-Ok, see you at the wedding.
-Thank you.
You should get married soon too.
Thanks for everything.
Mr. Lee.
Geu Rae.
Hello, I'm the new employee
Oh Sang Sik!
I'm Kim Boo Ryun.
Yes.
Thank you, sir, thank you.
I'll ship the product right away.
Yes, yes!
Thank you, thank you!
Wow!
You're the best!
Thank you!
Let's go hiking,
Mr. Choi will come too.
I forgot I have a get-together
on the weekend.
If you can't take what's given to
you, are you not willing to change?
What are you doing here?
Why'd you hit him?
What will you do?
Tell him I don't care.
Sang Sik!
Hey!
Ok, sure.
Go with the complete item.
Sang Sik is creating a business now.
Let's encourage him.
I've been to your kids' first birthdays.
Get funds and find a big
item for the Middle East.
Wait.
Take this.
I bought dried eel for buyers.
Take it.
It was so unfortunate.
When you lose in Go by
a move to prevent a tie,
you wonder what all
the moves were for.
Even if you win in
a small battle or war,
if you end up losing,
it was all seemed useless.
If you win by a
move to prevent a tie,
you can see a different world.
I was grateful to the stones in the war,
enabling the victory of that move.
Every single
move seems precious to me.
Doing your best in
every moment makes
the victory of that move possible.
Missing a moment…
means losing the whole
and eventually failure.
When did you start losing the moment?
Mr. Choi.
Sales Team 3…
Oh.
Hello.
Oh, sir.
Sir.
Yes.
I got the report.
Your team did a great job.
Thank you.
Here.
It's a special incentive.
He prepared it himself.
Thank you.
How long have you been a manager?
Seven years, sir.
You better hurry.
You're really late.
-Oh, Dong Sik.
-Yes.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
What a surprise, sir.
Oh, Mr. Choi.
They did a good job.
I'll award those to deserve it
and punish those who need it.
That's my job.
Yes.
Geu Rae.
I heard you played a big role.
No, sir.
Instead of getting off work as soon
as you can, look around one last time.
Then you can minimize your mistakes.
That's been my habit
since I was new here.
Thank you.
Mr. Oh.
Yes?
You'll be promoted next year.
That's nonsense.
Promote Mr. Oh to
Deputy Head of 2 years.
Yes, sir.
I'll do that right away in
the first half of next year.
When's the personnel appointment
of the latter half of this year?
A week later, sir.
Let's do it then.
Employees can only be compensated by
their salary and timely promotions.
Oh, sir.
Hi.
You're in charge of Sales until
Mr. Kim's successor comes?
Oh…
Yes.
Ok.
Bye, sir.
Sir.
Kids, dad will be promoted!
Really?
-Really?
-Really!
Hey, do you even know
what promotion is?
Nope!
He'll become Deputy Head.
Be quiet!
Hey!
You even know what that is?
Nope!
Then why get excited?
You feel great!
Yeah!
So we feel great too!
Freeze!
Sit down!
Yeah!
Oh yeah, this…
It's our team's special bonus.
Special bonus?
Sit down.
Okay.
There was that much to spend?
Since the kids are growing,
there are things to do.
Give me your wallet.
Why?
Use it wisely.
I can use my credit card.
You'll have to pay for
others' cab fare.
It doesn't look good
when a guy has no money.
Thin wallets are popular now.
No one carries cash with them.
Ok then, give it back.
No,
I don't go with the trends.
Let's see how much there is, wow!
Shall we order pizza?
Yeah!
[Personnel appointment]
[Oh Sang Sik:
Manager => Deputy head]
Geu Rae.
-Did you complete the registration?
-Yes, I did.
If you didn't, you won't get
compensated for accidents.
-Got it?
-Yes.
Let's go, Mr. Deputy Head.
After I finish reading this
report from the research center.
Manager Oh…
I mean, Deputy Head Oh seems
easy-going but meticulous as always.
Our team was calm.
No one mentioned Mr. Park's incident.
Everyone was silent.
It was probably because our team's
accomplishments brought
unfortunate results.
So I think they're escaping to work.
Deputy Head Oh is especially quiet.
So all he can do is work.
Mr. Oh and the rest of our
team can't feel the change.
But you can feel how they see us
differently in the hallway.
We didn't just scold
a negligent team member.
We removed an infection of the company.
But our team members were
viewed as whistle-blowers.
'Why couldn't you take
care of it internally?'
'Why pursue profit betraying
your colleague?'
'Are you all innocent?'
You can see online comments pitying
18 02//[Personnel appointment
notice is up, is this fair?]
transferrees and Mr. Kim who resigned.
No one denied the fact
that they should take responsibility.
Mr. Oh called us to talk in private.
Oh.
It will get more uncomfortable.
Don’t get stirred up.
The important thing is,
you did what you needed to.
Don't ever miss that.
Mr. Oh created a guide for us.
We agreed to it.
We just have to hang in there.
Hey, Mr. Ha.
I heard Young Yi was trying to move
the whole load herself that day.
How did you know?
Suk Yool is telling everyone now.
Badmouthing you…
Geez.
I told you Young Yi is scary.
I actually feel proud of…
You're good at Russian.
You take charge of the certification
issue in Russia.
Excuse me?
I've never met anyone
as tenacious as you.
If I leave you alone, you'll disgrace
our team creating
accidents everywhere.
Thank you.
I won't let you off easily
just because you're a girl.
I'll work hard.
Why are you looking at the T/F report
that was already approved by Finance?
Is something wrong?
It's a bit long.
It needs to be more concise.
Long?
Yes.
In what way?
There are many nonprofessional terms.
Above all, if you thought you'd
lead it, you would've
taken full charge.
That way, you could
lead the sentences.
Otherwise, they become
long and clunky.
I get it, sir.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm sorry.
Summarize it.
What does he mean, long?
I think they're the same.
Where are the nonprofessional terms?
I've been trained that much.
[The special notice about
the Middle East course]
The special notice about
the Middle East course.
Notice.
About.
Middle East.
Course.
It's long.
Notice about…
Special…
About the…
Issue?
Middle East course-related issues.
One of the biggest Islam holidays
Ramadan came to
an end on August 18.
Ramadan ended…
Someone will fill in for
Mr. Park soon, right?
Yeah.
A competent person will be
able to change the atmosphere.
I don't know if anyone
will want to come.
Ms. Sun.
Yeah.
Can I have a minute?
Mr. Ma asked me to do something
regarding the fermented bean paste.
-What is it?
-I...
I can't understand what he's saying.
You know…
Don't you need a certification
to export it to the States?
Excuse me?
What certification?
For food…
US FTA…
What was it?
You know.
I can't remember it.
You know what I mean!
You know!
Don't you know?
You don't understand, do you?
Go look it up!
By FTA,
you mean between
Korea and the US?
What kind of certification?
I'm not talking about the
free trade agreement.
How did such a dense guy
join One International?
Which college did you go to?
That's why they should
review colleges too.
You're in Ms. Sun's team, right?
Yes.
That's why a woman shouldn't
become a team leader!
Go, find her!
I don't understand what he wants.
Give me the documents.
I'll talk to him.
Is certification necessary
for exporting fermented bean paste?
Or are you talking about FTA conditions?
You know, conditions or
certification or whatever.
What is the "whatever"
you're talking about?
We need to get food certification
to export organisms!
Organisms?
Is fermented bean paste
octopus or squid?
What?
I'm sure you know since
you've reviewed it.
It's a complete
product that went through
the manufacturing process, ingredient
analysis, fertilizer checkup,
antioxidant use, and
colon bacillus checkup.
It went through
factory and sample checkup.
What certification is necessary and
conditions need to be fulfilled?
If you remember what that
"whatever" is, let me know.
We'll go ahead with the schedule.
Hey.
I kept letting you go
since you're a woman.
You!
You should thank your husband.
For putting up with a woman like you.
Two sexual harassment
won't end with a pay cut.
What?
What did you just say?
Hey!
Why, that…
Mr. Ma will tell you
if he needs anything,
so just proceed as scheduled.
I'll take care of Mr. Ma's
approvals from now on,
so I'll take over anything
he asks you to do.
Yes.
When you spoke with Mr. Oh,
did he mention who
would go to Team 3?
I heard an assistant
manager might go.
Why?
I don't want to go to that team.
I want to work under
you for a long time.
I can't send you.
Ms. Sun.
The person to go has been decided.
[Personnel appointment]
Good news.
Mr. Chun is coming.
What's he like?
Don't worry, he's normal.
He's experienced with the Middle East,
although not as much as Mr. Park.
He used to work for Sales Team 3.
It was his first dept. as
an experienced employee.
I…
became exhausted by a bad boss,
so we relied on each other.
We worked hard under Mr. Oh.
Lots of good memories.
How are experienced positions
and open recruitment different?
First of all, they don’t
have someone like you.
Someone they entered the
company with and can talk to.
Weak support base too.
He wanted to come in this atmosphere.
Maybe he missed old colleagues.
You have a big belly.
Mr. Chun!
You're already here.
Dong Sik.
I mean Mr. Kim.
-How are you?
-Yes.
Hi, Mr. Chun!
Mr. Oh.
I came to say hello in advance.
I look forward to working with you.
Why are you so tense?
Come on.
You're acting weird.
He's a newbie in our team.
Hi.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
Nice to meet you.
You came to say hi and
organized your desk?
Boxes…
You want to sit here?
Then I'll go say bye
to my previous team.
Mr. Chun Gwan Woong, age 37.
That's my desk.
He organized his desk
as soon as he came.
All the items were in place
as if they belonged there.
I thought the man taking Mr. Park's
place would make
things relatively easy.
Instead, he created
a tense atmosphere.
-Dong Sik.
-Yes.
Go to the Life Supplies team
for some samples with Geu Rae.
Yes.
Sir.
What about the polyester case?
Why should I do that?
Wasn’t a half-day off enough,
why are you still upset?
Didn’t I tell you that's your job?
Come here, Suk Yool.
Is that right?
What is it?
Instead of a banker's usance,
you wrote a shipper's usance!
[Banker's Usance: the importer pays the draft interest till the maturity date]
[Shipper's Usance: the exporter pays the draft interest till the maturity date]
There are specific instances to use
these terms in the polyester case!
If you had trained as I asked you
to, you wouldn’t get this wrong!
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'll fix it.
Fixing it won't do.
Listen carefully.
People learn from mistakes.
I want you to know how I feel.
Read some self improvement books.
See what kind of seniors are good.
Don't get confused again.
Banker's, shipper's.
You're not going to pay the interest.
It's bigger than a month's salary
and I don’t have money.
Banker's, shipper's, ok?
Banker's usance is
paid by the importer
and shipper's usance, by the exporter.
Suk Yool met his match.
Mr. Sung won't be easy to beat.
What?
How do you memorize
trade terms so well?
AOG.
The starting or payment
expiration point
for a discount is when
products arrive.
No hesitation, you're like a vending
machine and I pressed the vending
It's easy to memorize
if you associate the terms.
It's just like playing Go.
According to you, you should
understand the core of proposals.
If you connect the dots, you can find
out the company's size
or characteristics.
But you never get it
and ask me again and again.
You're like that.
Do a good job, vending machine.
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
Huh?
Mr. Kang asked him to do it too.
What?
Making sentences concise.
He always trains newbies like that.
After that, the reports
become much easier to read.
What?
Why didn't you tell me
how reports can improve?
Don't worry, I'll make you
throw up while writing reports.
Are you Vladimir Michailovich Andreyev?
The report you sent is
different from our request.
It's meant to set the emission
quantity by ton of CO2 equivalent.
The unit used is different
from what we had requested.
Did you make a mistake?
Yes, I'd appreciate it
if you'd revise it.
-Young Yi.
-Yes.
Go bring my shoes on the way.
A pack of cigarettes for me.
You know what I smoke,
you bought peppermint
instead last time.
How could you ask her to do that?
She has to send the mail.
Can I go after making some copies?
Why, that…
Oh, Young Yi.
Geu Rae.
Your fly's open.
Thanks for bowing.
You're so cruel.
How can you laugh when
I'm sinking in a swamp?
-How?
-Suk Yool.
What are you doing here?
What are you laughing about?
Huh?
I'm not that happy.
Shall we have a drink tonight?
A boss torments you in your face.
A boss treats me like trash.
A boss…
You know what's
the worst type of boss?
Bosses that use juniors.
Bosses that slave juniors around,
give you their work,
and take the credit.
But you know what's worse?
He… doesn’t know what he's doing,
I mean he's feigning ignorance.
I think he's feigning ignorance,
but everyone falls for him.
How does he do it?
Is everyone pure?
Especially Mr. Moon.
Is he blind or deaf?
Geez.
Answer your phone.
Answer it.
Hello?
Suk Yool.
Han Suk Yool.
What?
I was wrong.
I've been thinking a lot.
You must have your reasons
for acting this way.
Sorry for not being considerate.
Let's have a drink.
I mean let's have a serious talk.
Now!
Hey, man!
Suk Yool!
Where are you now?
Go.
Why are you drinking
alone looking pitiful?
Suk Yool!
Sit down.
Come on, sit.
Gosh, Suk Yool…
I know.
-Shall we leave?
-Huh?
Yes.
Geu Rae.
Your fly.
You can't fool me again.
It's true this time.
Thanks for bowing.
Let's go.
Why, that…
I'm a guy,
so I try to be understanding like
a guy when you ask me to do stuff.
Newbies should do everyone's work.
It's all your work, Suk Yool.
So I'll do what you ask me to.
So it's all your work.
Not mine, but yours.
So you're making me
do stuff to train me.
I understand that.
So I'm telling you now,
it's not my work, but yours!
Your work.
You're a total sociopath, aren't you?
Repeating the same thing
over and over again…
Sociopath?
I'm a sociopath?
So I…
I wanted to be mentored
by you and learn
properly like the other newbies.
So Suk Yool, that's why
it's all your work.
Not mine, but yours.
I'm not saying I won't do it,
I will, but…
But you can't take
credit for what I did.
I think you should be
considerate about that.
Suk Yool.
Yes.
You're a real sociopath.
Please listen to me, Sung!
Did you just call me by name "Sung"?
No…
Why, this…
You're not a sociopath,
but a psychopath.
Psychopath?
I can't drink with you.
I don’t feel like drinking anymore.
Geez.
Sir.
Please pay.
What?
$570
Why, that frigging jerk!
That frigging jerk!
Sorry about that…
Dang.
It's cold at night now.
You want my jacket?
It's ok.
Thanks.
You'll be happy with
your future girlfriend.
Come on.
Don’t be so bashful.
I'm not bashful.
I'm just hot.
Fall and winter will pass by soon.
Spring will come soon.
Then it'll already be a year for us.
What?
Because of "us."
Our kid got in trouble because
yours made a mistake!
He called me "our kid."
"Our kid…"
Last spring, I wanted to
hear that word.
It'll be spring and already a year.
For us.
I'm hot.
Your ears are red now.
-My ears get red when I'm hot.
-I see.
It's true.
Oh.
-Hello, sir.
-Hi.
I'm in your team from now on.
Hello.
Hi.
Geu Rae?
Yes.
I'll probably give you the most work.
I'm not uptight, so you can relax.
We can get used to each other.
-Yes, thank you.
-Sure.
And…
Uh…
What will you do about your hair?
What?
It's too long.
I think you can cut it so it
doesn't touch your collar.
Your bangs too.
What do you think?
I'll make my hair look neat.
You mean you'll cut it, right?
Cut…
Why are you acting like
the dean of the students?
Like back in school…
Yeah.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes.
-Let's have a briefing.
-Sure.
Let's go to the meeting room.
I can do it here.
We can catch up too, come on.
I know what you're doing.
You want to check out
our team, right?
Come on, I know Mr. Oh's
style, why should I?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Are you kidding me?
-Excuse me?
-You think work is a joke?
Am I your friend?
No.
You should be tense around
a new person.
Yes.
Leave our tough, but fun
memories of three years ago behind.
Don't take them with you
forever, it's pathetic.
What?
Yes.
Uh, Mr. Chun.
You didn't come to our team
for other reasons, did you?
Not me, at least.
Though I don't know what
the sender was thinking.
I'm sure no one's criticizing
your team,
but you should know
they're watching.
They're staring.
If you suspect me, it won't be
good, so perish the thought.
You guys didn’t do anything wrong.
You did well.
But having people like that
around is suffocating.
Nothing's happened yet, but if
they need me, they'll call me out.
Anyway get used to
the circumstances.
Why…
…did they send you?
I'm going nuts.
What?
It's because we're close.
If they send someone who's not close,
who knows what your filtering will do?
Let's make it work out.
Hello, sir.
Oh, hi.
Let's look at the work
progress, Mr. Kim.
Yes, I'll send it right away.
Who was in charge of this?
Our team, sir.
This is the Jordan case.
The one where Mr. Park got in trouble.
Oh, there are reasons…
Let's see the documents
again in the afternoon.
-This won't do.
-Oh…
-Sir.
-Mr. Chun!
Yes?
You're funny.
Work since you're at work.
Don't influence others that way.
You know why people
get addicted to games?
Excuse me?
It's because they play games.
If you play games at work…
…you'll get addicted to games first.
Let's go for a drink after work.
What is this?
Yesterday's receipt for the drinks.
Why, you…
Suk Yool.
I want to say something to you.
I was going to tell you, but I
didn't want to hurt your feelings.
What is it?
You have to change your
personality for social life.
I won't repeat myself,
so listen carefully.
Yesterday…
…you seemed like a sociopath.
Fix it.
Sociopath…
Above all, if you thought you'd
lead it, you would've
taken full charge.
That way, you could
lead the sentences.
Lead the sentences.
Too long. Make it short.
Course…
Make this sentence connect with this…
Like that…
It's ready,
so you can dip
it into the cheese.
Here's the liquor.
It was just the two drab guys and
now there are pretty boys with you.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Do you still drink alone
after work, Mr. Chun?
Sometimes.
He was famous for drinking so
much and drinking more at home.
Even if you love drinking, if you
keep drinking for other people,
you'll want to drink on your own too.
Right.
Since you like drinking, everyone
wants you to come and
you go with the flow.
You start to miss drinking
alone in your underwear.
Right, drinking beer in your underwear
and watching baseball is the best.
My hopes aren't even that high.
I just want to get off work on time,
order fried chicken for the kids,
and just drink beer with them.
Let's toast.
Welcome, Mr. Chun.
Yes.
Let's enjoy our work.
-Like the good old days.
-Like the good old days!
-Yes.
-Like the good old days.
I'm sorry for having various
thoughts before joining the team.
I'll work hard as a team member.
Drink up.
Geu Rae.
Any questions or requests for me?
Just ask me.
Do I have to cut my hair?
What?
Cut it.
If he doesn't reply, it means cut it.
He told me to straighten
my hair before.
Cut it.
You straighten yours.
Yeah, man.
You're joking, right?
No.
We should think of
visual images too.
I'll start combing my hair too.
For our team's visual image!
Cheers!
Hey.
Hi.
I just came.
Are you going straight to bed?
What's with you?
You always drank when
you came home.
I drank today.
You must like your new team.
You were worried about the
personnel appointment.
What?
Yeah.
Hello.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Hi.
Mr. Oh.
We'll have to prepare next
year's business proposal.
Yeah, you guys have time this morning?
-Let's have a meeting.
-Yes.
I didn't know Geu Rae
would take part
in next year's business proposal meeting.
We'll be having non-stop
meetings from today on.
Be ready.
Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
-Hi.
Hello.
-Hello.
The whole company will create
next year's business proposal
and prepare the budget, operation plans,
performance-related goals at this time.
Since a single business item is created
through many teams' cooperation,
you need to hold many meetings
and write out numerous documents.
We look at new items and old proposals,
but it's not a simple job.
Dinner delivery.
-Let's eat first.
-Let's eat.
Any update?
I thought about it and I think an
investment business
will be a good idea.
Sales Team 3 has been
working late for days.
I'm so tired.
How many days has it been?
My brain stopped functioning.
You want me to tell you why
your game isn't improving?
You're too hung up on rules
and previous examples.
Obviously you should
learn and study moves,
but how can the game survived
only through unchanging truths?
Then what should I do?
Break the formality.
Be radical.
Radical?
If you don’t break the formality,
you can't become a pro.
What do you think of
the Jordan business?
What?
Geu Rae.
What did you just say?
Redoing the Jordan business.
You mean Mr. Park's…
by the Jordan business?
Yes.
What are you saying?
I guess you don’t know as a newbie,
but you shouldn't take
others' businesses.
Don’t even bring up Jordan.
For the time being.
If you exclude the corruption,
I think it's a good business item.
The meeting froze at a fast pace.
Why do they look so serious?
Hello.
What's with Geu Rae's expression?
Getting told off big time…
Why'd you get told off?
I wasn't.
Weren't you?
Mr. Kang.
Good.
Hold on.
Big news about Geu Rae.
What, what?
I asked a hundred times.
How could Geu Rae think of that?
He just doesn’t get it.
Doesn't he know what the company
thinks of Sales Team 3?
They think of them as informants.
No one's comfortable.
He likes adventures.
Adventures?
He seems so at times
though I don't know why.
You fell for him?
What?
Young Yi.
You're overestimating him…
-Are you jealous?
-What?
What's wrong with him?
-I'm going to criticize everyone.
Got a problem?
I'll have a twisted
attitude from now on.
Anyway, Mr. Oh isn't
going to approve.
He shouldn't.
Come over.
Our team's meeting came to a stop.
We can assume the anticipated
debates and misunderstandings,
and unexpected damages.
But no one could easily reject
the newbie's radical idea.
Even if I'm merely a newbie,
they need a just reason
to reject my idea.
That's what a team is.
But this proposal was…
…a bit unique.
Do you not want it?
Is it just bound to fail?
Is it something we shouldn't do?
Or is it something we
can do nevertheless?
It's something you shouldn't
do nevertheless.
Everyone knows there's
leftover business.
But no one's saying they'll do it.
They don’t want the misunderstanding
of getting credit
from a different team's work.
Yes.
Even teams that have
nothing to do with it.
But your team…
that was involved in it
wants to do it.
Right.
Are you crazy?
That's wrong.
Then you guys do it.
What?
How did the newbie's
words influence you?
Then should I abandon it?
Yeah.
You should.
There are lots to do aside from that.
Can I do it if there aren't?
Are you playing games with me?
Don’t do it.
You have a weak cause.
Yes, it's a weak cause.
If you must do it,
you need a just reason.
A higher value than the fact that
it will bring in high profits.
I need a just reason?
Yep.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
Let me ask you a question.
Are you going for the
profits of the Jordan case?
Is that why you don't
want to miss it?
That's not all.
Though I do think it
was a good business.
Then why must you take
over this business?
I don't think our team's
work is done there.
It's not done?
I think we were insulted.
Insulted?
Our company was
insulted by Mr. Park.
I don't know if just
reporting him was enough…
You don't think it was enough?
I think we should wrap it up.
Wrap it up?
We should utilize the
company's manuals and
systems to make the biggest profit.
We must make the business
back to what it was.
We were insulted?
Our company was
insulted by Mr. Park?
If we eliminate the corruption…
Yes, it's a good business.
Since you're a newbie…
Only a trading company's
newbie could think of it.
That's a trading man, alright.
Ok.
Let's do this business.
Let's do it.
[Misaeng]
Why'd you send me to Sales Team 3?
You still don't get it?
Hey, you wanted to do it!
What happened to Mr. Oh?
Take it as work.
I'm not ready yet.
-Aren't I better-looking?
-What?
He's like a daredevil.
It's like Mr. Choi's cause.
When were we too scared
to do daring things?