Not Yet Alive
I was the first person to arrive at work.
It felt great to
be the only one there.
It was because it felt
like I opened the door.
A stationery shop owner from
when I was a kid always…
...opened the place
and cleaned the front.
Hello.
- Hi, going to school?
- I loved how the clean alley felt.
I started the day going past it.
It felt great opening the door
and start the day like him.
I checked various notice boards.
I read news articles of various
themes through the Intranet.
There was an appropriate amount
of tension and ease of mind.
It was just like a stylish drama scene.
Oh, it's not that data?
Oh, we sent the wrong one.
Until my immediate
boss came to work.
I have a file in Excel, so
I'll send it right away.
Bye.
Mr. Song.
I'm working on the report now.
I'll call you back.
Sir.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Wait a while for now.
This is urgent.
Hold on, let go.
You did well.
I'll put him on.
It's thanks to you.
I'll treat you when you come to Korea!
Yeah.
So the Uzbekistan case
finally worked out?
Yes!
This is totally worth it!
Congratulations!
You said that tie was from your
kids and it's really amazing.
You owe it to that.
Hey.
I'll treat you to a cup of coffee.
Let's go, Geu Rae.
Gosh.
- Hey.
- Hello.
I knew he was referring
to this as a "treat."
That's why I'm making it myself.
This is a golden ratio, you know.
Thank you.
We just have to take
care of Wilmart now.
Yes.
Here, it's hot.
Be careful.
Drink up.
Why can't you come when
you passed the cycle test?
The data isn't that hard to receive!
I think...
...the cost is a bigger issue.
Did you show them
the appropriate price?
If you consider the production cost and
general expenses, that's reasonable!
Yes, but they think it's unreasonable.
Hey!
I told you to fix your attitude.
We can't sell anything like that.
What can we live on if we
satisfy all their needs?
You have a problem.
Will you be on our side?
Why always work on theirs?
I'll keep an eye on the Guam one.
Geez.
Why'd you have to
ruin the mood here?
That's Mr. Park in IT
who's a nice guy.
Of course.
He's a great employee who
cooperates well with the client.
You two go for job training
to that team, don't you?
- Yes.
- Oh, yes.
Mr. Lee who just left will lead us.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 6]
What?
Rubber trees?
This is about Siberia's forests!
Dang.
Do rubber trees grow
in freezing Russia?
You copy/pasted the
Indonesian document, right?
I used Mr. Ha's document
for an MOU.
I got it mixed up with
the Indonesian one.
- I'm sorry, I'll redo it.
- How?
How will you redo it?
The Legal team is done reviewing it.
Why?
Will you go to Sales Team 3 to ask
for the Legal team to review it?
Tell me.
Aren't you going to respond?
I heard you told them about the B/L.
If you did, you ought to have
been quiet as an apology.
What?
"I told them"?
Are you kidding me?
You think that'll change anything?
Do you any good?
That's why I don't trust women.
Hey.
You don't even need to be here.
Go back to your seat.
Now!
Hey!
Take this.
You should revise your mistakes!
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Gosh, Young Yi is in deep
trouble because of the B/L.
She's a cool woman.
I don’t know if she's loyal or not.
Anyway…
…she's like me, something else.
Right now…
Man, I can't believe this…
Hello, my senior.
What's with you?
You learned at Ulsan and
I learned at Jeonju.
We have nothing to
do with each other.
We have different academy owners.
Do we really have to do this?
Why do we always have to suffer?
Are you talking about
the Wilmart ramen case?
They said if Sales Team 3
solves that...
...Sales Teams 1, 2's work
will go smoothly.
That ramen case doesn't really
help Sales Team 3's performance.
Sales Team 3 suffers and Sales
Teams 1, 2 gets the credit.
Yet, you have to pull it off.
It's discouraging, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-There's no word from Wilmart.
Is there anything you don't know?
- No, there isn't.
- Suk Yool.
Get going.
Ok.
Alright, see you later.
Geu Rae.
Oh!
It's here!
- Wilmart contacted us?
- Oh, yes.
Mr. Oh, it's here.
They want to meet.
They were so fussy, but
it's appealing, I guess.
These guys cause trouble
even after meeting them.
[Byun Hyung Chul]
Good-for-nothing Byun!
- You know him?
- Yeah!
He was a classmate!
I'm impressed!
He failed the college exams three times,
served in the army, and studied abroad.
Wow, things worked out for him.
- Were you two close?
- Yes, super close!
We used to steal our dads'
cigarettes and smoke them.
It's a done deal.
- Wow.
- Really?
Oh!
You're here again?
Yes.
Young Yi.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Samples?
It won't be easy to
move them alone.
Mr. Ha is going to come,
but he's running late.
- He'll come soon.
- Yeah?
Good luck.
Let's go.
Huh?
Go ahead.
Are you okay?
Yes, I can handle it.
Not this.
Go ahead, I'm fine.
Shouldn't we help her?
We're running late too.
She ended up like
that helping us…
Mr. Ha is going to come.
There he is.
If he sees us helping
her, he won't like it.
Hi.
What?
You should've asked for help.
They really owe you big time.
What?
Got ignored?
Why should I ask for
their help when you will help?
- I'm in Resources.
- Then why'd you do that?
What's in your brain?
You know what our boss said?
He said this is what adultery
probably feels like!
- Sir.
- How dare you yell at me?
Do your work!
Sir…
What?
Nothing.
So many problems…
Go to the medical office.
- I'm ok.
- I said go!
I'm sorry.
Is she doing that on purpose?
Why is she taking that?
Why'd I bring this?
I'm an idiot.
What's with your foot?
It's nothing.
Baek Ki, give it to me.
Come on.
I told you it'd be tough.
Give it to me.
Weren't you going to
the medical office?
I can go by myself.
Please leave those on my desk.
[Medical Office]
Korean time, dude…
He hasn't changed.
Korean time?
Don't they say that these days?
This dude…
He's always 30 minutes late.
Hey, dude!
Sang Sik!
Hey!
Hyung Chul!
You haven't changed at all!
It's been ages!
I can't believe we're
meeting like this!
I recognized you right
away when I saw the news!
What did I say?
You looked old when you were
a kid, so now it's all good.
No worries.
Hey, this face…
…is his face from high school.
- Hello.
- Our newbie.
Nice to meet you.
Sang Sik, wait a bit more.
- I'll go approve it now.
- Sure.
Sorry.
It's ok.
Dude!
Take your time.
Wow.
Gosh.
It's great to see him.
It seems like he took
a time machine.
Feels great.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- One time…
…a tough fighter fought with him...
...and the dude was
about to hit him with a chair.
I just kicked it!
Huh?
I don’t know why I did that.
"We're friends."
That's how things worked.
Wow.
Friend?
He's crazy.
Why am I his friend?
Shall I call him?
It's been over an hour.
It's ok.
He must have a lot to approve.
I'll call him.
Hi!
You came?
Busy, huh?
I didn't wait much.
Shall we start?
I reviewed the data.
It's so lacking.
The facilities, and
profits are ambiguous.
Hey.
So I made these changes for you.
Facilities, types of ramen
and earnings sharing ratio.
And this…
I don’t have time now.
No, I'll explain them to you.
It won't take long.
- Sang Sik.
- Huh?
- Oh Sang Sik.
- Yeah.
You think it's going to be easy?
Mr. Oh Sang Sik.
I'll review the validity
and contact you.
Ok.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Byun.
You have an executive meeting.
Ok, I'll be right there.
Mr. Byun, you're not
wearing your tie.
The executives won't like it.
Here.
Wear this, sir.
You told me your kids saved money
to buy it as a birthday gift.
How can you give him that?
Hey, I can use it as
an excuse to come back.
You're back, sir.
Hi, Geu Rae.
I'm working on the first order sheet.
Shall I put in 100,000?
The dept. manager kept asking.
I think Sales Teams 1, 2 were told,
there's no question about it.
Right?
Yes.
Why?
You went to get approval.
What's this when you
said it's a done deal?
I told you it's important.
You're aware of that.
You said he's your friend.
Why couldn't you pull it off?
- Oh Sang Sik.
- Yeah.
You think it's going to be easy?
Mr. Oh Sang Sik.
I'll review the validity
and contact you.
[Good-for-nothing Byun]
Hi, Mr. Byun.
You went back ok?
Sorry about before.
I had so much work
and I was in a hurry.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Buddy, it's been a while.
Shouldn't we go for a drink?
Yeah…
I'm free this evening.
Of course…
Yeah, sure.
Uh…
I'll decide on the place.
- Ok, bring that newbie with you.
- Oh?
Geu Rae?
Ok.
See you later.
Dude…
I knew it.
Dude!
Now that's more like it!
- Really?
- Yeah.
Then I better make reservations.
Where?
- Oh, Famous Pigs' Feet…
- Yes.
Call them.
He loved pigs' feet.
They're popular, so I hope
I can make reservations.
Hold on.
- Geu Rae, find it and make reservations.
- Sure.
He called Geu Rae too, so they
must be wrapping things up, right?
Then I'll have the contract ready.
Ok.
[Famous Pigs' Feet]
It's really famous.
We can't make reservations
on the day, but we begged.
- Let's go in.
- Are you kidding me?
Oh, you don't eat
pigs' feet anymore?
I do, I like it.
I don’t want to eat this now.
Oh, ok.
It's crowded here, huh?
Let's go somewhere else.
Where shall we go?
Hello.
Welcome.
Hey, come on in.
Give them some slippers.
Change into them.
Say hello.
This is Yun Soo, the owner here.
Hello.
Can you please excuse us
since we need to talk?
Sure.
It's ok.
She can stay.
You want the alcohol
you kept here?
Just keep it.
Let's open a new one.
How's that?
Sure.
Bring it.
Come on.
What, are you uncomfortable?
This doesn't suit your taste?
Come on, I like it.
Where did you go for
college, Geu Rae?
Oh, I…
He has a GED.
GED?
You guys don’t care about
educational backgrounds?
That's a great company!
Of course.
They recognized an elite.
Thanks.
Here, let's have a drink.
Fill up your glass.
Fill it up.
Nice to see you.
Come on.
Is your liver ok?
I can drink alcohol when I want, but
you have to drink when others want it.
Dude, how could it be ok?
My gall bladder's messed up too.
Man.
I thought you'd succeed as
you were such a great student.
Look at yourself now
at a trading firm.
What fulfillment do you get there?
Our trading firm is proud though.
There are only two jobs that
end with "man" in Korea.
Stocksman and tradingman.
They both have to kiss up to others.
Sometimes others kiss up to us.
- Sometimes.
Hey.
- Turtles…
- What about them?
You know how they roll?
I'll pour you a drink.
Yeah?
You're good-looking.
Does your company hire by looks?
Then how did this dude make it in?
Oh, come on.
Look at him.
Come on, I used to be…
Don't forget, I'll be
waiting for your call.
Don't worry, buddy.
You can trust me.
Oh, Mr. Driver…
Here you go!
Ok.
Hey!
Here!
Oh!
Bye!
Shall I catch a cab for you, Mr. Oh?
Yeah.
Come on.
Gosh.
What do you think will happen?
I think it'll work out.
Let me know when they call.
Wait!
We need the hangover tonic!
Yeah.
So…
…how much do you need?
Does he want it or do
you want him to do it?
It seems he wants to
copy his friends.
$150 three times a week
is $600 a month.
I know it's not a waste.
Sir.
I'll try contacting the
pipe exporting companies.
I told you there's nothing
you can do.
- I'll try it first.
- How?
- I'll search…
- I don't need your help.
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Park.
The electric wheelchair one…
Why'd you discontinue it?
I said I'd review it if you could
get accurate profits calculated.
Not this company.
It's a small company...
...but R&D is under way,
so if you work…
We can't connect clients
not knowing...
...the profit-to-investment ratio.
I told you many times.
Still, you know…
I'll call the company again.
Ok.
I'll return some books.
Return mine too.
Mr. Park.
- Yes.
- How's that case going?
What did they say?
Don't you know the buyer
is bugging me?
Yes, I'll call them again.
You keep calling with no results!
I'm sorry.
Don't be on the phone
all day, run over there!
Resolve the issue.
Yes, sir.
Oh, sorry, Mr. Park!
I was about to call you.
You didn't have to come here.
Sun Young, coffee.
I'm sorry.
When will the delayed item
issue be resolved?
We're securing goods in
stock, so wait 2-3 days.
You said that last time.
If you say that again,
I'll get in trouble.
- I'm sure you have your reasons but…
- Sorry.
Actually, my daughter
got into a car accident.
Huh?
Was she hurt badly?
No.
She was, but she'll be ok.
Anyway, I'll do my best
to resolve your issue.
- Sorry.
- Well.
I'm sure the shipping
issue will be resolved.
You didn't do it on purpose.
Anyway, I'm worried
about your daughter.
You must be concerned.
Yeah…
Yes, sir.
I just met with him.
He hadn't checked the
items for Guangzhou.
They're securing goods in stock.
So?
I asked them to hurry up with it and…
What's wrong with you?
If you went all the way there, you
should have brought up freight compensation…
...so they can understand this issue.
Don’t come back until
you resolve it!
Yes.
- How did it go?
- I heard it went smoothly.
Then why is there no call?
Don't worry, he's his friend.
He said to trust him.
Don't you think this is too much?
You made us become scapegoats.
Stop bugging us.
One International,
Jang Geu Rae speaking.
Wilmart Purchasing Team?
Hold on.
I'll put Mr. Oh on.
Oh Sang Sik speaking.
Yes.
Ok.
Dude…
Friend?
I thought he was your friend!
You shouldn't have said it, then.
We would've made a different
strategy if you hadn't.
You totally ruined it all!
What are you going to do now?
You said we can trust you!
You said we could have trust.
You said he's your friend
and we could have trust, no?
What's this now?
Mr. Oh, say something.
What's the reason?
You don’t like the delivery
conditions?
No, those are great.
Our company never had
intentions to begin with.
We thought it lacked marketability.
Then why'd you waste
time if that's the case?
You used to take
my side dishes before.
What?
I'm just kidding.
You have something against me?
No, we're not kids.
I used to a long ago.
So…
…what about the past?
We're not kids.
I'm not going into that.
I'll say it so you understand.
You might not know, but
I used to kiss up to you.
What?
So I just wanted you
to kiss up for once.
What?
See you at the class reunion.
Bye, buddy!
Dang!
He must be so disappointed.
You know when it's toughest
when doing sales?
When?
Having to entertain someone
you know personally.
What's tougher is…
…having to entertain a friend.
Entertaining...
...someone inevitably
happens in a vertical dynamic.
It's more embarrassing
since it's your friend.
Then you wonder if it's all worth it.
Honey.
You know, right?
My college friend, Sung Sik.
He quit...
...went to graduate school,
and now works for a good company.
Maybe I should…
What?
Huh?
You already registered?
Geez.
I wanted to talk with
you about it first.
Me?
Oh…
I'll have a shot with
Sung Sik before I go.
Yeah.
Ok.
Sung Sik.
Do you like working there?
But...
...what did you do...
...about your place when you
were preparing for grad school?
Living expenses must
have been tough.
If you want to do something,
just think of yourself.
There's no choice that
will satisfy everyone.
Take responsibility for your choice.
I'm happy…
I'm happy but…
I don't want to go home.
It's stressful…
…at home.
Ok.
Call me when you resolve it.
Mr. Park.
Yes, sir.
We're in charge of newbie training.
There's a subcontractor trip
set up, so you take charge.
Huh, me?
It's Mr. Park now?
Ok.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
We can't sell anything like that.
Geu Rae.
Go clear away the paper
on the rooftop.
[Resignation]
[I would like to resign, Park Yong Gu]
If you want to do something,
just think of yourself.
Oh.
Hello.
Hi.
You're Mr. Park in IT Sales, right?
Yes.
I'm newbie Jang Geu Rae
in Sales Team 3.
I'll be going to the
subcontractor trip with you.
I see.
Gosh.
Unlike other bosses...
...I won't be of much help.
Mr. Oh said I can learn
a lot from you.
He said you set a great
example with the clients...
Me?
What else…
…did he say?
Huh?
You're considerate of the interests
among companies.
He said…
...an iron hand in
a velvet glove.
That's essential for sales.
Yeah?
Then shall I tell you
about sales on the way?
Huh?
There are many funny stories.
I said I'd drive.
It's ok.
It's best that I do it,
I know the way.
Where was I?
Sales are like a war.
You need guts.
You should think you'd
lose if you get behind.
There are tons of painful and...
...victorious experiences.
Once, the client couldn't
meet the delivery deadline.
All the upper management
came and pleaded.
"If you overlook it, it
will be fine, so please."
And?
I said firmly.
"Let's do it by the book."
You're a true business man.
Yeah.
Maybe that was too big of a lie...
...but I feel great.
[Yeong Seong Industry]
It's our client and they're working
with a Chinese semiconductor firm...
...but some problems have
occurred recently.
What's that?
Delivery keeps being delayed.
They said they don't
have goods in stock.
Maybe they have another client.
Usually, the existing client
thinks they're safe.
No, not this firm.
They've built trust with me.
We need to visit once
in a while...
...for good tension.
We're busy now, so leave
One International for now.
They're new, so manage them well.
Try to hold out...
...with One International
on the phone as long as possible.
Mr. Park?
He's soft, so he's not
much of a problem.
Geez.
So I'll carry on with that.
It'll be awesome.
Mr. Park.
So they think of us as a pushover.
Mr. Park, we'll go back to the office.
Oh, ok.
Sorry.
Geu Rae.
I'm sorry.
Go back.
I'll stay a bit longer.
Geu Rae, let's talk.
What?
Geu Rae, I think we should go now.
Mr. Park was so perplexed...
...and the training isn't over.
There's nothing we can
do for him here.
The site trip is meaningless too now.
Do whatever you want.
I'll get going.
I'll get going, Mr. Park.
Sure.
Yeah.
They think of us as a pushover.
Me and…
…the company.
I wasn't cut out for
this work to begin with.
Mr. Park.
Are you done talking?
I better resign.
Why didn't you call me
in advance?
- Where did the other man go?
- He had to go back to the office.
Yeah?
- Let's go in.
- Uh…
When will you resolve our issue?
Right away!
Of course!
I talked with you on the phone!
I'm a fool.
Yes, you're right.
We talked on the phone.
Sorry.
I was going to resolve it first...
...but choices increased
because of new businesses.
Let's leave.
You're considerate of the interests
among companies.
I said firmly.
"Let's do it by the book."
Show him what you got.
Show him.
It was all lie though.
There's no choice that
will satisfy everyone.
Take responsibility for your choice.
Did I want to become a nice
guy who never complains?
Did I ever take responsibility
at the workplace?
- Sir.
- Mr. Park.
We made a mistake.
We'll take care of it now.
- Ok?
- Will it be ok…
…to do it by the book?
If I don't do it now…
…it'll be the same wherever I go.
I have nothing to say, Mr. Park.
I'm really sorry.
I'll fix it today…
…and make sure it
leaves Incheon tomorrow.
I told you we'll do it by the book.
Mr. Park.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
We've worked with One
International for years.
Mr. Park, we go way
back with your boss.
We have a long history.
Wouldn't it be a waste for
that trust to be broken?
Let's keep things positive.
Let's make things smooth.
This is how they treat me.
I was such a pushover to them.
You've already embarrassed
me enough.
How low will you drag me?
Mr. Park.
I'm sorry.
Despite our long history,
we made a mistake.
You wanted to do it by the book.
What do you mean by that?
Contract termination
or compensation?
I'll…
…discuss that with the headquarters
and let you know.
Why are you so foolish?
You wanted to make a few bucks.
So you become enemies
with our old partner?
What will you do?
Because of me…
…a partner relationship of
10 years is going to break.
I should have just overlooked it.
We're about to lose a precious
client because of you!
Uh…
- Today.
- Sir…
I've never been this
embarrassed in my life!
A move you make when
things don't look good.
Are you crazy about money?
The move you make to turn the tables…
- You love money?
- …is called a clever move…
…in the game of Go.
- Geez.
- If the clever move was brilliant…
- I'm sorry.
- …it proves they had the upper hand.
Calm down.
Mr. Park didn't think
it would come to this.
The reason they were shocked and
continued to persuade him…
…is because Mr. Park
wasn't like this before.
It's like they're looking
one way or another.
He's looking at them, but
he's criticizing Mr. Park.
- I have no choice.
- Please, sir.
I should go beg myself.
Mr. Kim, please call me.
- Please calm down.
- Let go!
We'll take care of it now.
Let go!
Sorry, the company is calling me.
- Ok.
- Let go.
It's so late now.
Oh, dear.
What if you get in trouble?
No, I came for work.
Also, I'm with you.
Yes, Mr. Kim, we're here.
Yes.
Hello?
You can't hear me?
When are we coming?
I think it'll take a while.
There's a problem here.
The president will visit
us and explain himself.
Clever moves are…
He said so himself.
…dealt with by proper moves.
I'll report to you when we're done.
Yes.
- There's an issue with Yeong Seong?
- Yes.
I got a call from Mr. Park...
...and the president
and employees are coming.
I checked and there
were delivery problems.
What's this?
There are so many.
Call the risk management,
inspection and business teams.
I'll report this to the
executive director.
- Hey.
- Yes.
Come over here.
Organize these.
Did you call the forwarding agency?
This is the IT Sales team.
Our Guangzhou case…
Please get the contract ready for us.
Don't forget the data on
shipment dates and schedule.
There was a problem
with Yeong Seong.
Check the accurate limits now.
Isn't it a reliable company
with a good history?
Can you prepare a file
on what happened?
Oh my.
Coming…
Hello, Geu Rae.
What's going on?
Which floor?
Hello, sir.
Oh, Mr. Kim.
I'm so sorry.
Please wait in the guest room.
Take him there.
You go with me.
Who are you?
Jang Geu Rae in Sales Team 3.
Sir.
Can he go with me?
How could I…
It'll be a good learning
experience...
...and he played
a big part at the site.
So I'll need him.
Baek Ki.
Yeong Seong or whatever
is here now.
Our risk management and
legal teams are all there.
I'm surprised.
He didn't seem that brave.
It's a big issue.
Geu Rae went into
that big meeting.
What?
Young Yi.
Gosh.
There was a big issue today.
Geu Rae is going into
One International's big meeting.
How could a newbie go in there?
He might get promoted
before us all.
What is it?
GED legend.
I don’t know how he's
going to be any help.
They must've taken him
in since he's some help.
Baek Ki is being patient too.
Experiences of such meetings are
very helpful for newbies like us.
Baek Ki…
…why'd you come back?
I didn't think I should be there.
Honestly…
…he's not like you, right?
Right, you know…
Yeah, he is indecisive.
He's not strong-willed.
Clients don't prioritize him either.
Geu Rae stayed there
until the end.
Maybe it's being nosy.
Anyway, Yeong Seong is
in big trouble.
It's over for them.
Well…
…it depends on Mr. Park's testimony.
I think they'll
probably just let it go.
People like him just
avoid problems.
He doesn’t have...
...what it takes to solve them.
Were there similar cases?
Yes.
There was.
They weren't situations to secure
products from other locations.
There no were penalties,
so the loss wasn't huge.
The items didn't require prompt
treatment, so the risks weren't big either.
Regardless of compensation,
contract review is inevitable.
It's been seven times.
It's not worth a case.
Why did this happen?
Mr. Park will explain
since he's in charge.
I'll…
…explain.
Mr. Park was overwhelmed
by the gravity of the case.
He's concerned about the
other company's crisis.
That's foolish.
Mr. Park.
For your reference.
Thanks.
I'll tell you what hap…
The secret is to…
…scrap unnecessary
things when in a crisis.
Become irresponsible!
Scrap it.
You can't take care of everyone.
You need to survive here.
I'll report…
…what happened.
I'm sorry, sir.
We were wrong.
No, it's my fault.
There were seven freight delays.
I found out the cause today.
Yeong Seong was focusing
on other transactions...
...while increasing clients.
Our shipments were
delayed in the process.
I found out about it today...
...and asked about
the responsibility.
You found out because
you went to the site.
Yes, you should always
check with them.
But…
…there are some
problems regarding this.
While those issues occurred...
...I didn't do anything
about it as the one in charge.
The fact is we didn't realize
how serious this was in the beginning.
Also, I wasn't...
...confident about my work.
I'm the one to blame here.
I'm the one...
...that made them think it was ok.
I didn't take responsibility.
I'm the one…
…who's responsible.
When the industry increased shipment
costs with oil cost increases…
…our company decreased them.
I couldn't pursuade them as
a company representative.
That's why they looked
for other profits.
I just thought about leaving...
...with frustration about work.
I think I'm at fault for this.
I'll take responsibility.
Save…
…them.
Keep the contract.
Don't…
…penalize them.
When did you start working here?
Huh?
He's been here for four years.
You're a romantic guy.
Would we abandon a 10-year
partner because of this?
Who are you?
Why should you take responsibility?
How will you?
You should think
about now, though.
It'll be bad for you, your
family, and the company later.
It's a good thing,
so keep thinking.
Wrap it up well.
It was more miserable
than any Go game.
Everyone has their own game.
How could I…
…dare to…
…teach him anything?
Baek Ki.
Yes.
It worked out.
What?
IT Sales, Mr. Park.
Yeong Seong was saved and he
didn't get in trouble either.
The meeting went really smoothly.
I heard Mr. Park was great.
Oh…
…why are you telling me?
You're curious, no?
I thought you were super curious.
- Suk Yool.
- Yes, sir.
That?
I have to go.
Suk…
Why are you so down when
Mr. Park's case went well?
I heard you went in too.
Something wrong?
I couldn't be of any help.
What's with you?
Now you realize that?
We can't do anything, yet.
Geu Rae.
Thanks, Geu Rae.
You helped remove
my unnecessary traits.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yeong Seong will...
...sign a new contract
that works to One International's benefit.
Mr. Park will find the issue and...
...write a report on
how to prevent it.
I thought Mr. Park
would get in trouble.
That's how it's like here.
We can't help from
having various risks.
No matter how you prepare,
accidents happen.
You can't ask employees to
take responsibility each time.
So the company focuses on...
...finding solutions
for these issues.
When you were
punished last time…
That's why it's nonsense.
Even if the firm protects
you, you suffer.
If you don't write
a thorough report…
…they could ask you to take
responsibility if something similar happens.
Mr. Oh, shall I write the
Wilmart process report?
It's ok, I'll do it.
Ok.
[Wilmart Ramen Import: Frigging,
frigging, frigging…]
[Wife]
I sent you an email, so read it.
Geez.
Thank you.
Next.
What's a tradingman?
Tradingman is the ultrabest hero...
...in the world.
He buys products for...
...everyone on earth.
They make poor countries rich.
While supplying water
to those without.
He beats...
...Spiderman,
Batman, and Ironman.
Don't lie!
I'm not!
Liar!
I'll tell my dad and scold you!
Hey.
Stop it!
He's a tough one.
- Have him work as one too.
- Yeah.
Do it!
Now!
You!
Totally like you!
Yeah, this is why I work here.
- Totally like you!
- Right.
Everyone has their own game of Go.