Not Yet Alive
[2013 One International New
Year's Kick-Off Meeting]
Episode 14
We had a new year's쟪ick-off쟭eeting.
It was a huge scale with all
employees participating.
There was an introduction
and awarding for the team
with the best performance last year.
We heard about the other
teams' performances.
Moments of embarrassment, we had
high hopes about the Jordan case.
Good job.
Thank you.
You realize you're just
a small part of the whole,
not the whole itself.
[Misaeng]
Regarding the stainless coil
you asked about in December,
I'd recommend stainless steel grade 444.
You can use it for water tanks,
feed tanks, and water heaters.
We'll send you a brochure, so
if you decide on the quantity,
we'll send you the quote.
We'll make it suit your needs.
Thank you.
Bye.
Baek Ki.
What?
The "w" in German should ring
more than the "v" in English.
Don't bring the sound to the front
of the nose and mouth like the "v,"
but make it sound like you're gagging
from pushing your toothbrush
too deep in.
Repeat after me.
Come on.
That's it.
I majored in German Lit.
- Sir.
- Yeah?
Resource has approved the
additional Norway business.
Yes.
Then proceed with Norway.
- Now help with Canada organizing.
- Yes.
Mr. Yoo, have you looked
into local finances?
I'm still on it.
It'll take time to select a constructor.
If you're talking about solar
energy and wind power regarding
complex developing district businesses,
I have a constructor list.
Ok.
Then you take charge of that.
Yes, sir.
We'll send a citron rice wine
sample, so please review it.
Yes, I think there's no plan
to release low-alcohol.
We'll check and contact you again.
I appreciate it,
thank you.
Bye.
They want low-alcohol rice wine, but
why drink it unless
you want to get drunk?
In Japan, they like mixing soda in
whiskey and juice in vodka nowadays.
I think the trends are changing to
low-alcohol and beer-flavored drinks.
Geu Rae.
Have you been receiving tutoring?
You have a Japanese girlfriend?
Look.
The number of orders has
dropped, you got to save me.
I don't know?
You haven't received tutoring.
You haven't received...tutoring.
No.
Hello, Mom-san.
Blind date?
Come on, I'm so busy, there's
no time to get married.
Is that why you called?
Is she pretty?
Send me a picture.
I have to go now.
Yes, I'll call you later.
Bye.
I'll go to Finance now.
Yes.
Where's Mr. Oh?
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm Mr. Ham of IT Sales.
Hello.
He's in a meeting.
Gosh, this is urgent.
I'm working on last year's accounts.
A few of your team's data is missing.
I need the purchased
amount of nuclear energy
for the T/F case with our
team in the 2nd quarter.
Can you find it?
Yes.
Here it is.
Would you like a copy?
This is it.
Yes.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Uh, I heard a newbie thought
up the Jordan business.
Is it you?
Yes.
Yeah?
You look like a smart worker.
Thank you.
Mr. Ham, hello.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
I came to your team for something
and he took care of it.
Yeah?
- See you around.
- Bye.
-Geu Rae.
-Yes?
He didn't say anything much?
No, he just talked about work.
No way.
He used to be in Planning.
I'm sure he's really upset now.
He applied for more employees
since his team needs more.
Anyway Geu Rae,
rumors about you have
spread and people
will look for you for various reasons.
Someone like me?
They'll want the newbie
the CEO complimented.
And they'll think there are no
worries even when you become useless.
I'll do the coffee.
Here.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
They'll want the newbie
the CEO complimented.
And they'll think there are no
worries even when you become useless.
Since I'm a temp.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
Did Mr. Ham just come by?
Don't share files when the
person in charge is away!
You shouldn't do things you
can't take responsibility for!
Yes, sir.
Dang.
How dare he come to my team and?
I'm back.
Something happened?
Oh?
Mr. Ham came to feel Geu Rae out.
They need more employees.
That's rude to think of stealing
our people in the new year.
Yes, you'll have to wait a bit longer.
What?
We need to check the amount
and I can't make time.
Yes, sir.
I'll send it by 5:00, I mean 5:30.
By fax, bye.
Mr. Oh.
What brings you here?
I got the files I needed just now.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes.
You're really busy.
We need more employees.
You should tell upper management.
I can't get through to them, you know?
-So you're lurking around my team?
- What?
What are you saying?
No way.
Don't come near Geu Rae.
Yes.
It means you'll offend me.
I'll get going.
Yes.
What happened to this employee?
The company didn't renew his contract.
What's the use of training people?
You have no choice if the company
doesn't renew the contract.
- Here's your coffee.
- Put it there.
Mr. Jung!
Yes.
What happened to the Tunisia bid?
We lost it to Samjung, right?
Uh?
Don't you know the resource HQ
executive director is
a college friend of mine?
I'm so embarrassed, I want to hide.
We didn't lose it, the Tunisia buyers?
Hey!
You're just full of excuses.
You just keep going on and on.
A trading man should just show me
the contract, not talk non-stop!
Make it work out now!
Geez, he gave me the info so late.
What am I supposed to do?
You know what he's like.
I just hate how he pokes you.
I wasn't even treated
like that in school.
Let's have some coffee.
Would you like some coffee?
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks.
Here.
New employees, come to the 5th floor
meeting room by 5:00, from HR.
Young Yi.
You have good news?
Yeah, everything's been
ok since my attack.
He was acting macho-like,
"I'll show you responsibility,"
but still hasn?t yet.
- Hello.
Did you meet with Ms. Ha?
Why should I meet with her?
Oh, Baek Ki, did you hit on
any girls at the ski resort?
I'm not into that stuff.
Didn't you spend the holidays with her?
Young Yi.
You're supposed to hit
on girls at ski resorts.
That's nonsense.
- Look!
Sure.
You must've been out for work.
No, I had a visitor here.
Are things going smoothly
with the Jordan case?
Yes, thanks to you, we're
preparing for shipping.
I heard your newbie worked hard
regarding the Mr. Park
and Jordan cases.
Yes.
He must be bright and full of vigor.
You're lucky to get such employees.
You had an eye for people.
See you later.
Don't be too concerned
about the Mr. Park case.
That was reasonable.
Thank you.
But
couldn't you have told
me in advance about it?
That's not too much to ask for.
It's not too much.
That would've been nice.
Last year's welfare points will expire,
so use them all.
Your annual leaves too.
You know volunteering is reflected
in your performance, right?
I like volunteering,
but I'll only give blood.
We don't count blood
donation more than twice.
You'll have education
mileages starting this year,
and you need to take at least 30 hours.
That will include English,
trade, and data processing.
You need a minimum 80% attendance
rate and test score.
If you don't pass, the education fee
will be deducted from your salary.
English?
It's ok, they have easy classes and
don't worry since there
are many executives.
Lastly, you can look at your
contracts on annual income.
Your names are on the envelopes.
I'll get going.
The HR team?
What's with them?
Mr. Hong, have you finished
your annual income contract?
Don't look at it.
Mr. Ha and Mr. Yoo, submit
your signed contract today.
- Yes.
They set annual incomes
and pay raises in January.
Of course, that doesn?t
apply to temporary workers.
It's applied the moment
the dept. head's evaluation
and the team manager and
employee's approval are complete.
I'm not part of the A/B/C evaluation.
How much is your incentive?
So tiny, not even $10,000.
You had a great performance.
Yeah, but what can I do if the boss?
I want to be one of them.
Dang, I work hard, but the company
doesn't acknowledge it.
Why don?t we get a break?
My family wants me to get married.
I don't want New Year's or Thanksgiving.
I have another blind date this month.
I wonder why you get
rejected all the time.
Can you research it and
send me a Powerpoint file?
Look, seems feminine, right?
Wow, she's pretty.
- Seems feminine.
- Nice.
Who got the highest incentive?
After Mr. Kang, I mean.
It's me.
Geez.
Like them.
- You got married?
- You can't get married this year either.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
The HR team presentation ended
long ago, so where were you?
I'm sorry.
Where's the file
I asked you to organize?
What are you doing?
Don't act like you
finished something big.
Work like you normally do.
I'm sorry.
You saw in
the Kick-Off Meeting, right?
What we did was
a normal performance.
Of course, it was tough,
but snap out of it.
Work as usual.
Mr. Oh.
What?
I just have to work like
I normally do, right?
As usual.
I'll become a full-timer
like this, right?
No, you won't.
It's what the data is about.
There are many college graduates
who studied abroad.
They're struggling without a job too.
If you think of the money
and effort they put in,
it might be natural
they get in first.
They want elites, so they look at
education, GPA scores, and talents.
Then they add points for
special skills to be fair.
They compare everything.
The company's manual is very strict.
There won't be any room for you.
Mr. Oh, what are you doing?
Hi.
Let's get off early today.
Early?
I thought it was my infrastructure,
but it was just borrowed for a while.
Geu Rae?
What are you doing?
Nothing, taking off for the day?
Bye.
We got off early.
Shall we have a drink?
What?
It's ok.
Do you know
what I enjoyed most about work?
I don't know.
Learning how to drink.
I could forget
loneliness and tough times.
I could also lick the
boots of people I hated?
?all thanks to alcohol.
But what I regret the most?
?is also learning how to drink.
I don't think I was able
to enjoy everyday life.
Neither did I enjoy leisure or a break.
Thanks.
Drink slowly, sir.
Enjoy alcohol.
It could become poison.
Cold mind and warm heart.
If it's cold, raise it,
and if it's hot, lower it.
Have a cold mind
and a warm heart.
Alcohol can raise the heat.
Cold mind and warm heart.
That's a familiar phrase
for those who play Go.
Have a cold mind
and a warm heart.
As of today,
I'll stop drinking.
What?
Thanks to you,
I enjoy working after a while.
I've felt my heart beat that
I didn't feel for a long time
Don't mention it.
I know you went through
a lot because of me.
I didn't even get to apologize,
because I felt so guilty.
Having lots of work isn't suffering.
I sent you to work.
Help them out and bring
success to Sales Team 3.
Do you think I should take out
this cavity or treat it?
I just have to work like
I normally do, right?
Like I normally do?
I'll become a full-timer
like this, right?
Really?
Is she pretty?
Of course, I'll go.
Mr. Sung.
Talk to you later.
Yes, sir.
-There's a 9:30 meeting tomorrow, right?
- Yes.
Get the files ready so
I can go right in.
Yes, sir.
Suk Yool, you heard that, right?
Get it ready by tonight.
What?
Check if the research
center's data is ready too.
Check for overseas
news and KOTRA's data.
Add the credit check reports
from the trade insurance corp.
Make it within 15 pages in this
order; news, KOTRA, trade insurance,
research center, our report, got it?
Take? re? spon?
si? bi? li? ty.
When will he do it on his own
if you teach him everything?
Don?t overdo it.
Yes, but if I don't keep my eye on
things, accidents happen like last time.
Suk Yool is still a newbie, you know.
I'll take care of him for
now, so please understand.
And I'll take off after
I check the final file.
Gosh, you're so meticulous.
- Bye.
- See you tomorrow.
It's Oppa.
[Oppa: Older male or older brother]
Sorry, I have to work
late and can't go tonight.
Sorry.
I'll treat you big time.
Ok, bye.
What's up?
You're still at work?
Jae Yun is treating us today.
Yeah, got to hurry.
To have a drink
See you where we always go.
Bye.
Text me when you're done, Suk Yool.
[Sung Joon Sik]
You can take off.
If I'm about to fight with a filthy dog,
I should be ready to get filthy.
[Would you like to delete
the "meeting file"?]
[Yes]
I said there's a 9:30 meeting.
What time is it now?
I'm sorry.
Suk Yool.
You haven't made the meeting files?
Didn't you hear there's
a meeting in the morning?
Oh, I made it.
He said he made it.
Why... didn't you tell me?
You texted me to take off.
You should've uploaded it.
I couldn't because of the
intranet checkup time.
You should've printed it out!
The printer's broken.
But why isn't it in the computer?
What?
It's not there?
The system was so unstable yesterday,
I guess it didn't save it.
What?
Don?t worry.
I have a backup file.
So you didn't check it yesterday?
Sorry, I had a sudden visitor.
I was away for a minute.
Geez.
Why'd a visitor come at that time?
Check the file and send it to me.
Yes, don't worry, sir.
This isn't right.
Suk Yool.
-Did you look at this?
- What?
What's with the spacing?
What would've happened if
you had just submitted this?
You still don't have it down?
This isn't right.
Sir, I'll redo this ASAP.
Ok, and submit a written apology
for being late, Suk Yool.
I'll go into the meeting.
Yes, see you later.
This isn't right.
Email the file to me ASAP.
Fights start with waiting.
When the opponent is strong?
"Strong" my foot.
There's a Jordan buyer
meeting today, right?
Is it at the company?
Yes, 4:00 after a visit to the embassy.
At 5:00, domestic companies
will be introduced,
and then we'll go for dinner.
Foreign Investment is
joining tomorrow's meeting?
Yes.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
How much of the file is ready?
I'll finish it by this evening.
Mr. Chun and Mr. Kim.
Yes.
Go to the Foreign Investment
meeting by 2:00.
Yes.
Tell them not to be
fussy about...weird stuff.
Mr. Oh hasn't been in
a good mood today.
Here's a picture of
this week's blind date.
She's pretty.
I hope you get married this time.
Yeah.
My job is fine, height
is fine, weight?
Maybe it's my weight?
Maybe it's your hair?
Maybe it's my voice?
It would be nicer low like this.
I'm doomed.
I made a reservation
with Summerset Golf
for you and Samjung's Mr. Lim
for the Netherlands case.
I never heard of that place.
You're sure it's not a lousy place?
You know how extravagant
Samjung was last time.
It's the hottest country club now.
When the Thai prime minister
came recently, they went there
with the invited employees.
Yeah?
I've prepared an environmental
gift with a marker.
I chose it for its nice green image.
For the course?
It's all unnecessary, we
just need pretty caddies.
That way, things will go smoothly.
Yes, but since important
business will be discussed,
I've requested neat and calm caddies.
But Young Yi.
What's your relation
with Samjung's Mr. Shim?
I went to the Korea
Economic Association.
They kept mentioned you guys' names.
Be careful with your body so that?
That question is unrelated to work.
What?
Why, that?
Hi,
coffee, sure.
Why, that dang?
Young Yi.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Mr. Ma?
It was nothing.
Hey!
Young Yi!
Hey.
You get a kick out of
talking back to your boss?
And you're giggling
with a guy now?
That's why I told you to
be careful as a woman.
I'm just telling you not to get
involved in rumors as your boss.
How could you talk back to me like that?
You think you could
even get married like that?
I'm just worried since you're
like a daughter to me!
Be careful with your body.
Why am I your daughter?
What?
Hey!
Then are you a son?
What a psycho!
What are you looking at?
What?
You want to report this
as sexual harassment, too?
Why'd you jump in?
You should stand aside
when a boss is talking!
It's because you talked back to me!
Hey, Mr?
Are you ok?
Shouldn't you apply some
ointment at the medical office?
I'm ok.
I'll be right back.
Wipe yourself at least.
I'll get going.
I'll wash it off.
What are you doing?
You wanted to go for lunch, mister.
[Mr. S stands for Satan?]
Suk Yool?
[Would you like to move this to
the "Anonymous Noticeboard"?]
[Yes]
"Strong" my foot.
What do you think of this kind of boss?
Ok.
Let's go eat, buddy.
Where's Young Yi?
Call her.
Hello.
Young Yi.
Is your neck ok?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Suk Yool kept looking for you.
I heard you were supposed
to have lunch together.
Change into this.
It was my fault.
How much was it?
It was a bit expensive.
Yes, how much was it?
- $50,000.
- What?
Thanks for before.
This is what love for
your colleagues about.
No, you won't.
There are many college graduates
who studied abroad.
They're struggling without a job too.
If you think of the money
and effort they put in,
it might be natural
they get in first.
The company's manual is very strict.
There won't be any room for you.
Mr. Kim.
It's Saturday, what are you doing?
I'm just home.
You have any plans for today?
No.
Nice, stand by.
What?
I have a blind date today.
I'm sure I'll get rejected again.
Imagine what that New Year's
gift would feel like.
- That won't happen?
- What, what?
You said I'd get rejected
again because of my hair.
That was?
Just stand by for an hour.
If I don't call you after an hour,
you can go and your
bro will get married.
"Bro?"
Shall we go eat?
No, maybe next time.
Shall I set a nice date for next time?
No, you're not my type.
I'm sorry.
What is your type?
I have to lose a bit of weight.
I'm not a dandy dresser.
Oh, right, I should straighten my hair.
That's not it?
My voice would sound
better low like this.
My colleagues teased me before.
Uh?
I don't like how you
don't seem selfish.
What?
I think people will say you're kind,
but it'll be tough for your family.
You don't know what you're saying,
I'm actually very selfish
and self-centered.
I was chosen as #1 selfish guy.
I'm sorry.
My dad is like that, so I
know how my mom suffered.
It's just about me, I'm sorry.
Uh?
What?
It wasn't my weight, hair, or voice.
You don't like me because
I don't look selfishness?
I see selfish-less could be
a reason to be rejected.
He must be doing fine.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
Yes, sir.
Take your time, I'll be right there.
It seems you're buzzed
already, ok.
Bye.
I didn't ask for the location.
Which bar is it?
Wow.
Are we finally drinking together?
How'd you know I'd call you?
You were playing hard-to-get, right?
You were waiting for my call, right?
[Oh Bong Ja Salon]
What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with not being selfish?
Come on, oh, what's her name?
Ms. Ha.
Men who work at conglomerates
used to be #1 groom material.
Now, men and women
are both cunning.
Old virtues don't work anymore now.
No, they don't.
As male chauvinism decreased,
sacrificial minds have too.
Now they don't want
girls to rely on them.
As more girls started to work,
they won't open their hearts
when they think
the life won't be easy with him.
How good a person he is
doesn't matter anymore.
What do you think, Geu Rae?
About what?
Your view on marriage.
I'm just a temp.
Thanks for the good news.
Cheers, cheers!
Cheers!
Here.
Yes.
I should take the
express bus, not the train.
I couldn't reserve tickets
as work was so busy.
I can get there by bus.
Yes.
Don't worry, I'll go.
Good night.
Bye.
[Express bus?]
Mr. Sung?
Isn't he talking about
Sung Joon Sik in Fabric Team 1?
Mr. Sung?
I'll get you embarrassed in public.
I'm Sung Joon Sik in Fabric Team 1.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
It's my fault for not training
a new employee properly.
You were wrong, newbie.
You should resolve it within the
team even if you hate your boss.
He lacks the basics.
Who is the newbie in Fabric Team 1?
- Fire him.
- Many guys would want his position.
You want to fight?
How will a newbie fight?
Shouldn't you wait for now?
Fighting starts with waiting.
When the opponent is strong?
Hello.
What's with your expression?
Are you sick?
Hello.
Today we're getting our New Year's gift.
I just gave my Thanksgiving ham set
to Mr. Sung, I wonder why I did that.
I wonder why, why, why.
Have you seen the noticeboard?
Who is Han Suk Yool?
Mr. Sung's Fabric Team.
Gosh.
Newbies these days are useless.
They're so gutsy now.
He's not gutsy, he's brainless.
He thinks the "Anonymous"
is really anonymous?
Mr. Sung is too nice.
He's actually indecisive.
If it were my team,
I would've just? dang.
How long do you think
he'll hang in there?
Shall we make a bet?
Hello.
Another gift when we still haven't
finished our Thanksgiving one.
Gosh, it's the same
cooking oil every year.
They want us to fry their ham?
It's ok.
[Cooking oil]
Many temps didn't get anything.
Let's go.
See you later.
I said don't ask for too much.
Hello.
Don't ask for too much.
Must I get permission
just to ask for things?
What?
It's not an issue of full-timer
and temp positions.
It's not that.
Then?
I just want to continue working.
With our team I've worked with.
Us
together
always.
How was your blind date?
Well?
You should've done well, geez!
Did something happen?
Nothing.
Oh, it's ham!
It's not that.
I just want to continue working.
With our team I've worked with.
Us
together
always.
- Mr. Oh.
- What?
You did this when
I didn't even ask you?
You taught me everything.
Not everyone gets
what's taught to them.
Anyways, it's thanks to you.
Thank you.
Wow.
Hopefully I can continue working
if I keep this up, right?
What are you doing?
Hey, hi, hi.
- Hello.
The meeting will be held early,
so buy a gift for them.
Buy it during lunch since
it's for the evening.
- What should I buy?
- Red ginseng, of course.
Bring back the receipt.
Yes.
Shall I go with you during lunch?
Will that be ok?
Yeah.
Geu Rae can't you even buy
a buyer's gift on your own?
Uh I have to buy
them for my team too.
I think this is best
considering the price.
It's nice.
It's recommended for foreign buyers
since it has a strong Korean image.
Whose gift is Baek Ki buying?
I don?t know, his parents?
We'll get this.
- You can wait at the counter.
- Okay.
What would you like to buy?
Uh? something healthy
and easy to take.
All of our products are
healthy and easy to take.
Let's go if you're done.
You're here.
Yes.
Good job.
Let's take off early today.
You're going to King's Steel, right?
Say hi for me.
Yes.
Come here, Geu Rae.
Here.
Have a good holiday.
I'm good.
You should say "thank
you" and receive it.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Is this the New Year's bonus?
They give it in envelopes
these days too?
No, Mr. Oh gave it to me.
How gracious of him.
You thanked him, right?
Yes.
You should massage me harder.
Like a man.
I said don't ask for too much.
Don't ask for too much.
Must I get permission
just to ask for things?
What?
It's not an issue of full-timer
and temp positions.
It's not that.
Then?
I just want to continue working.
With our team I've worked with.
Us
together
always.
Tomorrow, it will get
loud with the guests.
So get some rest somewhere.
What?
My mother gave me freedom.
When I gave up on playing Go,
she yelled at scolding relatives.
How will they hurt her
feelings today?
How I ran away to my first
workplace, then the army?
How I'm a 2-year contract worker?
Holidays can be
ruthless time your family
can hurt each other.
I felt bad about leaving
my mom alone
but I think it'll be
better I stay away.
But
there's nowhere to go.
How did I live such a pitiful life?
I realized I didn't even
have a friend to
enjoy a cup of coffee, a movie
nor a riverside walk with.
Where should I put this?
Here.
Take this first.
Is there anything I can help with?
You're Geu Rae in Sales Team 3, right?
Yes.
Why'd you come on a holiday?
Don't overwork yourself
when you're a temp.
They won't make you a full-timer.
Dang "temp."
There's
nowhere for me to go today.
I think I was wrong.
I wasn't thinking.
I shouldn't have left
my mom alone.
My Geu Rae showed promise
ever since he played Go.
- He?
- Please.
Don't make excuses for me.
I knew he'd make it big long ago.
He always comes late since
they need him all the time.
This higher-up came to visit
him when he was working late!
So many people would visit
him when he played Go.
People would come
left and right, gosh!
You know how good he looks in suits?
He even looked great
in his dad's old suit
that doesn't even fit.
He looked like he was born
to work at a company.
And is it just a normal company?
It's one of the top
5 trading companies!
Sis-in-law, ok.
You're so proud when he's a temp,
imagine when he's a full-timer.
Hey, you think temps are for everyone?
My Geu Rae suffers so much?
Sis-in-law, don't cry.
I only smiled as I didn't want to
discourage him after he failed in Go.
Now he's smiling at us
when he's suffering inside!
That's how Geu Rae is like!
Ok, have a drink.
Let's not forget it.
I'm my mom's pride.
I'm not a disappointing son.
Hello.
You had an eye for people.
Mr. Oh.
Shall we have a cup of tea?
Geu Rae.
I'm going to get coffee,
you want a cup?
I'll make mine.
Ok.
You better start the new business.
Yes, we're working hard.
Is he on it again?
Jang Geu Rae?
Sit down.
It's interesting.
Interesting, indeed.
He's just focused on work without
any concerns or calculations.
Like a daredevil.
Like you-know-who.
Actually he reminds
me of you, Mr. Oh.
It's fun when you decide on an
item and learn the business.
You remember then?
When we were the first to secure
germanium in the East Sea.
We were running about looking
for refinery facilities.
We worked on many cases
without insurance.
After we heard that company
couldn't go manufacturing,
they wanted full compensation.
So a few were fired to
take responsibility.
We got through that too.
You know, Mr. Oh
I mean Sang Sik.
Sometimes
I wonder why you
grew distant from me.
We were tight like comrades in war?
The only person fired was Lee Eun Ji.
Who?
The one who died.
I think she did something wrong.
Now I see why you're still
like this in Sales Team 3.
You fool.
You bent over backwards
to protect temps then too.
Will you do that this
time too with Geu Rae?
I'll drink the tea next time.
Didn't you say
you'd take responsibility then?
Didn't you?
Did you say you wouldn't
take responsibility?
I can't remember.
If Lee Eun Ji can't,
will you take responsibility?
Will you take responsibility?
Take a deep breath.
Mr. Choi
couldn't remember Eun Ji.
He's just acting like he can't.
No, he really can't.
Since she's not worth remembering,
that's the way he works instinctively.
He perfectly erased himself
from that incident.
So perfectly that
he could fool himself.
It's his instinct, not intention.
That's why he's a scary man.
He used to tell Eun Ji every day
what you'd see in self-help books.
"Go to night college."
"Dream big."
"Effort will pay off."
"Work hard and you'll see a road."
She was smart.
She'd be alive if
I had known my place
She would've worked comfortably,
met a nice guy,
got married,
and lived happily, right?
Since she's a good girl.
She told me with smile,
"Thank you, Mr. Oh.
I just have to continue
working like this, right?"
Geu Rae asked me
the same thing.
I'll become a full-timer
like this, right?
I said he can't make it.
Mr. Oh.
Times are tougher than Eun Ji's.
Empty hope
and irresponsible
consolation are useless.
It's scarier we live in a world
where irresponsible
consolation and empty
hope can't be given.
Since there are so many who are
desperate for that
empty hope at least.
Still
he won't make it.
[Misaeng]
I can't even drink
water in front of you.
Do it over.
Mr. Oh's treating Geu Rae
differently this year.
One of us were sacrificed for him.
What a tough life.
If you have time to think about
others, work on your weak points.
If I get a step closer, I'm two
steps further the next day.
- Geu Rae, $100?
- Probably?
Tell him to take Baek Ki.
You said you'd sell anything.