Not Yet Alive
Episode 10
-Hello.
-Oh.
Hi.
Gosh.
You're enjoying coffee
amongst yourselves?
Coffee served by women taste the best.
Right?
Come on, in this time and age?
I can't drink this.
Ms. Shin.
I'd appreciate a cup from you.
Sure.
Thank you.
Great shape.
What?
I mean this car.
Nice shape.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Useful.
Useful engine.
Come on, give me some coffee.
Come on, hurry up.
When will I ride a useful car like this?
I'll report him for sexual harassment.
What's going on?
Ms. Sun.
Mr. Oh!
Oh!
Keep an eye on your subordinate.
A team leader shouldn't let
Mr. Park act like that.
What's going on?
The stock market's always crashing.
I can't work with you
like this anymore.
What?
[Misaeng]
You've become
a part of the team and I
[Episode 10]
wanted us to work hard
and be successful.
But I was hoping for too much.
What are you talking about?
I'm not getting it.
I'm saying let's just work,
but not as a team.
Suit yourself.
I'll put up with negligence at work.
Verbal abuse to the weak,
and sexual harassment of women
I won't let that happen.
I won't let it go.
Sexual harassment?
Ms. Sun came and told you?
The first draft was made for the Halal
item, so Geu Rae will wrap it up.
[Halal: Products consumed
and eaten by Muslims]
Since you've adjusted to the
team, do your thing now.
Decide on a good item.
Geez.
Gosh.
Then I'll continue with
my Jordan used car item.
It brings in the profits.
Ok, then expand it.
What?
You're only looking at
used automobiles, right?
The future of Jordan construction
looks bright too.
Expand into heavy equipment.
-Expand it?
-Yeah.
First, send the materials
so we can share them.
Mr. Kim!
Hi.
Is that coffee?
Yes.
Why didn't you ask someone
instead of coming yourself?
Your coffee used to be awesome.
It was thick and sweet.
It was like my tonic for the day.
I heard you're going to expand
the Jordan used car business.
Yes, I'm reviewing the documents.
It's not a bad idea.
You can bring in bigger profits through
products including tires and batteries.
Yes, a market is being formed as they
sell them to surrounding countries.
See?
Mr. Park is useful to the company.
You can get credit thanks to him.
Young Yi, clean this.
Yes.
-Over there too.
-Yes.
Also, organize the supply box.
It took a while to find a pen.
Yes.
Young Yi, coffee.
Why do you keep giving me coffee mixes?
I want mine black.
Don't you know that by now?
Yes, sir.
[Jordan business income statement
(Requested by Sales Team 3)]
Is that the Halal contract?
Oh, yes.
What's with your expression?
Nothing, sir.
It's strange, isn't it?
What?
You want me to tell you what's strange?
You can't see the selfishness
of a big company.
What?
It's?
like that? here.
What are you doing?
You were so deep in thought?
I told you you should've
come to our team.
You want me to trip Mr. Ha again?
No.
What's your concern, Mr. Oh?
You know, thinking about the next item.
I'm thinking of expanding
Mr. Park's Jordan used car business.
I saw the proposal once.
Yeah?
Yes.
What did you think?
What?
You thought it was weird too.
Yes, I knew you would've noticed.
Mr. Oh, excuse me.
Ok.
That guy?
Isn't he Mr. Shim at Samjung?
You froze when you saw him
in the lobby and ran away.
No, sir.
I caught on.
Why this newbie was so talented.
I don't know what?
-Please excuse me.
-Go ahead.
Why'd you want to come out so far?
Mr. Park's Jordan used car business...
Have you seen it?
No.
I was going to.
The documents won't have any issues
since Legal and Finance
have reviewed it.
If you read it carefully though,
you'll see? something
you can't understand.
What's that?
Their company's profits are set so high.
That's true.
Their size and performance suddenly
excelled around the contract period.
The special profit share
among the net profit
on the financial
statements are too high.
Mr. Park got that kind of company
and their profits are set too high.
Then?
You get it, don?t you?
He gets a back margin?
Mr. Park?
Who knows?
So let's find out.
Whether our team member is a lazy pig
or a troublesome mad dog.
I shouldn't have bought this one.
I'm glad I bought you at least.
Yeah.
What's with the atmosphere?
It's just so weird.
Excuse me.
Great acting.
How dare he?
Twenty 1Bs.
Give me a 3D pipe.
Here you go.
What's with these storage samples?
Pipes of different sizes are mixed in.
I've told you many times.
How can you find anything when
you need something urgently?
I'll organize them now.
Leave it.
I'll do it.
You can go work on
the contract, Ms. Shin.
Yes, sir.
I could hear you get
told off from outside.
It seems you're using my method.
Acting as a servant.
Did you give up on yours?
Hello, Ms. Lee.
Yes.
I decided to stay at my company.
Will you have a sandwich
for dinner again?
What?
Let's have dinner.
I'll treat you properly.
Since you'll be staying?
Why don?t you treat all the newbies?
No.
I don't want to announce
I wanted out.
I'm regretting telling you big time.
Come here, Suk Yool.
Suk Yool.
I can put up with incompetence,
but I can't put up with
rude subordinates.
You didn't greet me once today.
Suk Yool.
Is something wrong?
Tell me if something's troubling you.
Sir.
You really don't know
why I'm like this?
How should I know your
personal affairs?
This isn't right.
You're at work now.
You don't take work back home.
You shouldn't bring personal
stuff to work either!
I don?t know what's going on,
but get a grip.
Also, organize the polyester item soon.
Mr. Sung.
What?
I'll take a half-day off today.
I can't sit down because
of my headache.
Hey, did you have a meeting?
You should clean up if you're done.
Where's Young Yi?
Young Yi, clean this.
Yes.
Oh, right.
Young Yi.
Go get my shoes from
the repair center.
Also, get me liquid digestive
medication on the way back.
-Shoes and digestive medication.
-Yeah.
Buy me a pack of cigarettes.
You know what I smoke, right?
Yes.
-I'll be right back.
-Ok.
Mr. Yoo, what are you doing?
She said she'd run my errands,
not clean up after you.
I just?
Don't you think it was too much?
We just?wanted to help you.
Dang.
Hey.
I'm suspicious of his intentions
regarding Young Yi.
What?
Intentions?
He really?
I think he thinks of
her as a personal maid.
We're trying to train her officially.
He just slaves her
around personally.
That's not right.
He shouldn?t do that.
Sir.
Why, that?
Young Yi.
Go to Pyeongtaek now.
What?
Make sure the fertilizer in the
Seobu Chemicals storage room is sent
to the container yard in Incheon
Port by tomorrow morning.
That is set to take off in five days.
Just do what I say.
We should move them when there's time.
It's the container yard free demurrage
period, so take care of it.
[CY free demurrage: Free-of-charge
period to store containers]
Shall I call Seobu?
I already told them we'd
go anytime this week.
Yes, sir.
You don't have to come back to
the office after that's over.
Where are you going?
Oh.
It's the completed
report for the TF item.
Decided to stay?
Mr. Kang is a good guy.
Do a good job.
Yes, sir.
[Jordan used car export project]
-I'll get going.
-Sure.
You told me to give you what I have.
Why is there no comment on that?
Do you want to do it or not?
I'm a meticulous guy.
I created everything, why
read between the lines?
You should make progress
when you should.
That's why your team
only does little jobs.
Come out now.
Hey.
What is it?
What are you talking about?
You guys are trying to
ruin mine, aren't you?
What is it?
Tell me.
You're just Sang Sik's boot licker.
Would you die if he asked you to?
Don't trust him too much.
He ended up killing a female
employee who liked him.
He keeps hypnotizing himself
that it wasn't his fault.
When everyone knows about it.
How could you say that?
Look at you talk.
Look at your real side.
Now you're taking his side?
You want to use his connections?
Get on the side that will help you.
You should get with
either the president
or the executive director.
That fool, Mr. Oh is nothing.
He's just useless.
You know what I'm saying?
You don't know anything, dude.
If you understood, go tell
him to hurry with it.
I'm on my way to Pyeongtaek for work.
Let's have dinner next time.
I feel like I can breathe now.
Why are you coming along?
I like being at sites.
Close it or dust will come in.
Yes.
Strike?
Why didn't you call before coming?
We called, right?
Yes, no one answered.
There was no time, so we just came.
I'm sorry.
The office must have been vacant.
We're so busy too.
What should we do?
Hold on, please.
Please leave a message?
Resource Team, how may I help you?
Mr. Yoo, this is Young Yi
and I'm here at Seobu.
I couldn?t reach Mr. Ha?
Mr. Ha?
He's in a meeting.
He probably can't talk, why?
What?
Strike?
Yes, apparently the freight
strike started today.
Mr. Ha told me to get it done
by tomorrow, what should I do?
What can you do?
It's a strike.
Just come back.
If you were a guy, we'd ask you
to rent a truck and bring it.
-What?
-Just come back.
I'll tell Mr. Ha.
He said, just come back?
Let's go, we can
eat on the way back.
I know good restaurants in Pyeongtaek.
You have a small truck
in the factory, right?
What?
What are you going to do?
You want us to move them?
Yes.
Us?
400 bags of fertilizer
on a 2.5-ton truck.
We need to make 3-4 trips.
3-4 trips.
Yes.
I'll see it to the end.
Will it really be ok?
It's ok.
We'll return it tomorrow afternoon.
Ok.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Let's go.
What?
Take it.
I can't.
What?
I don?t have a license.
The exam period?
I missed it as I was
busy preparing for jobs.
For that long?
I thought I was fine.
Come on, 40km?
They're ditching
because you're so slow.
You said you have five days.
That it's not urgent.
I got the order from Mr. Ha.
He said to move them
by tomorrow morning.
You're so inflexibe, I didn't think
you were like this, Young Yi.
We don?t know when
the strike will end.
We don't want problems
with the shipment.
Will you move it?
Everyone's going ahead.
Be quiet.
Geez.
Catch on?
No, he'll think he's just an outcast.
You really think he doesn't
know we're secretly on this?
We can't do this for long.
I think Mr. Oh will
make a decision soon.
[Stock market]
[2012 Jordan used car export]
Why'd you review it for so long?
How big should I expand it?
Make it as big as possible?
Isn't it weird?
What?
The subcontractor seems
to be taking so much.
What are you on about
when it's all over?
You said you were going to expand it.
They're not taking much.
Come on, the data tells it all.
It's not a lot considering
this business.
Their performance isn't great,
but they became independent
from a big firm.
The infrastructure is solid.
That's the problem with big companies.
They only look at the files.
They think it's all good if
it looks good on the outside.
Big companies miss the details
and that's a problem.
I feel uncomfortable about this.
Let's just forget it.
You want to pry
into others' affairs?
Move.
Will it end like this?
Mr. Kim.
Yes.
Meet with that company.
Record what the person in charge says.
It should be accurate since
there will be an internal audit.
Internal audit?
Geu Rae.
Go with him.
Yes.
Internal auditing will be involved too?
It's a possibility, you know.
Can we go to the company
without calling?
They could be contacted by Mr. Park.
This is tough.
What if the situation gets out of hand?
-Then Mr. Park won't just?
-Geu Rae.
Listen to me carefully.
We're trying to find out the facts now.
Whether it was done by
the right procedures.
Even if the contract seems too much,
it could be just for
the people in charge.
Whether it was done by the
right procedures is key.
The procedures might be more
important than you think.
Whether he gave damage to
the company for his own performance
or for personal gain.
Whether the company selection
was unfair, those are the issues.
The company will judge
the results, not us.
We're not trying to
ruin someone's life.
All we can do is work on the process.
The results aren't up to us.
Mr. Park overdid it to try
and control the results too.
Let's go.
-Hello.
-Hi.
How's it going?
Are you getting along with Mr. Park?
Yes.
Treat him well.
Don't treat him poorly just
because he was with us before.
Let's go.
What?
Strike?
Yes.
It doesn't have to be
done by tomorrow, right?
Right.
So I told her to come back.
That's ok, right?
Yeah.
So why'd you send her on
an unplanned business trip?
You clearly told her to come back?
Yes.
I made it clear a female
can't do anything there.
Oh gosh, let's just go.
Oh man.
Let's just go, ok?
[Proposal by Park Jong Sik]
[Approval by Head
of Dept. Kang Boo Ryun]
Dong Sik and Geu Rae are
checking with the company.
Mr. Oh.
You know we're going through something
that's been taken care of?
Yes.
Then it might not end with one person.
Things could get out of hand.
It has to do with everyone
who approved it.
I know.
Nothing's for sure yet.
I'm just telling you the situation.
If that's the situation,
it's usually right.
Individual reasons are just added.
According to my experience,
rumors don't just end as rumors.
Be careful when you
question others' errors.
Don't hate the person or you won't
be able to focus on the errors.
Disregard the person
to look at the errors.
That way you can question
them and get honest answers.
-Ok?
-Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Excuse me, we're from
One International?
What brings you here?
Don't hate the person or you won't
be able to focus on the errors.
One International must be very
interested in this business.
Sit down.
No.
I'll go out.
You shouldn't barge in like this.
You should keep your
manners around them.
You must have many questions
about the Jordan item.
Let's go, I'll explain
everything so come.
We came because we can't
find out that way.
Hey.
Businesses are told through documents.
I went through all the procedures.
What more do you want to know?
I need to know what
the procedures were.
Are you on the Audit team?
Who do you think you are?
Just make it official.
You've never done it before.
You don't know what's going
on in the actual business.
"Procedures" my foot.
Come out.
What are you trying to do?
Hey, Mr. Oh.
What did you talk with Mr. Kim
about in the meeting room?
You guys have been tight
and I'm getting jealous.
Yeah, right.
Now you get the importance
of connections?
Good thinking.
Sir.
Did you arrive?
Yes,I'll be right down.
Yes.
Hi, Mr. Oh.
Let's withdraw.
Mr. Oh.
I think you should withdraw?
I'll call you back.
What?
Mr. Oh said something?
He wants you to go back, right?
Geez.
Gosh, of course it ends up like this.
Mr. Oh isn't totally out of his mind.
Gosh.
I'll drop it.
I think that's the right thing to do.
For you, I mean the company.
I'll take care of it within my team.
Regarding Mr. Park's
Jordan used car item,
I'll have him submit a proper proposal
with the correct profits.
But please send Mr. Park to
a different team for
the proposal issue.
Just do it.
Go with the procedures.
Where shall we go for golf this week?
Where we went last time.
Hello?
Yes.
Yes, sir.
We'll go with the procedures.
So the Audit team will come soon.
Hey, Mr. Kim!
Why make such a fuss?
I said I'd explain it!
Explain to the Audit team.
Come out!
Come on!
-You stay here, Geu Rae.
-Yes.
Please don?t touch the documents.
-Come out, ok?
-Sure
Come on.
It's me.
Is the general manager in?
Did he go somewhere far?
You can't contact him?
Do it, it's urgent.
[Audio recording]
Yeah.
Sir, this is Mr. Hwang.
One International wants
to send auditors suddenly.
You'll have to come.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Also, One International?
I'll send a text.
Bye.
What?
What's the problem?
There won't be any problems if
we check and everything is fine.
Hey.
No man is infallible.
Especially with big cases
like the Jordan one,
what happened could be
interpreted differently.
You know?
You said the Audit team was coming.
You were joking, right?
Sorry, I don't like playing games.
I'll call just two people right now.
The head of the dept.
and the general manager.
Dang.
Must I do this?
I could kill all you
guys by one phone call.
Mr. Oh and all his subs as well.
You know?
You?
Mr. Oh will be with Mr. Choi right now.
Hey!
You?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you doing this?
Hello?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Sorry, I need to send an urgent fax.
I sent you a fax.
Please send me a reply.
Yes.
It's time to react to the
trouble the opponent is giving.
In such crucial times,
we need to risk our lives too.
The side who makes
a mistake first loses.
Who are they?
It's an important time.
One must not be rash or hasty.
If we're to proceed, we
must not make any mistakes.
The results are clear.
If the opponent doesn't die,
we'll die.
[Baekjin Trade]
Submit all the documents, please.
Yes.
Here.
Each side's documents and
account books were compared.
Don't you think this company's
profits are set too high?
Here.
This is a fax that
just came from Jordan.
As you can see,
the Jordan company chose ours.
We can ask for a high profit, right?
That's true.
From that perspective, the judgment
can be up to the persons in charge.
I understand for now.
You shouldn't treat
me like this, Mr. Oh.
What is this?
In front of a client?
There must have been
a misunderstanding?
What's this move that I want to
make though I don't have conviction?
It's me.
-Is the general manager in?
-What is this?
We'll take care of this soon.
Yes.
Excuse us.
It's ok.
Good job.
Thank goodness that
fax came from Jordan.
Good job.
Good job, everyone.
Whether we win or lose, the
move we want to make?
I sent you a fax.
Please send me a reply.
?is always made somehow.
You spoke with a company
in Jordan, right?
You're right.
They have Koreans too?
You spoke in Korean.
Let's take another look at the fax.
Ha.
-Show it to them.
-Yes.
They sent it from Jordan.
Ha.
There are Koreans in
the Jordan company?
It's a huge company and
they work with Koreans,
so I'm sure there are Koreans there.
I see there are no Koreans there.
Muhammad Indira.
He appears in contracts most often.
Is he an executive?
- He's their general manager.
- He's the marketing director.
It's their representative number,
you can talk to Muhammad.
Gosh.
Hello?
Is this ICV company?
Yes, it is.
I'd like to talk to
Mr. Muhammad Indira.
-Who?
-I'd like to talk to Mr. Muhammad Indira.
Muhammad?
Hold on.
Hello?
Are you Mr. Muhammad Indira?
Yes, I am.
Are you Korean?
Who is this?
Where are you calling from?
This is One International from Korea.
Did Jordan employees
sign the last contract?
I can't answer that,
the executives will come?
What's your Korean name?
I'm Park Sang Joon.
What's your position, sir?
I'm the marketing director.
The documents say you're
the general manager.
The documents are correct.
I got promoted recently.
Please send us an executives'
list including the CEO.
Not the attachments to the documents.
Please don?t hang
up and just send us a fax.
What's wrong?
Are we obligated to do that?
I don?t think we can?
This is the confirmation process
before legal procedures.
According to our reviews,
ICV company consists of locals.
According to the
corporation register too.
Wait a minute, please.
We need to check the Jordan company.
Who's in the Amman office?
Call him and tell him to go
to the address I sent now.
Ok, bye.
Our dispatched worker
will go there soon.
Please explain it to them.
[Jang Geu Rae]
Resource?
Hello, this is Sales
Team 3's Jang Geu Rae.
-Is Young Yi?
-She's not in.
Can you look into it?
Baek Ki, please.
Ok.
I'll ask the Audit team.
Thank you.
Are you a Jordan citizen, Mr. Park?
No, I'm not.
Then why do you use a local name
and you signed the contract too?
Can we consider this forgery?
How could you all say this?
How?
Yes, I set their profits high.
It's my responsibility and mistake.
I'll take responsibility.
Ok?
I'll take responsibility
by a pay cut or whatever.
Mr. Oh.
Will you leave them out?
A move?
This is so embarrassing!
?is decided by the previous move.
Businessmen have to save face!
It's all because I'm lacking!
Ok?
In order to understand
why this move was made,
you must look at the previous move.
This could happen
during business?
In order to understand why
the opponent is resisting,
you must review the previous moves.
We always do business?
What might have looked like a small
problem, might not be at all.
Give-and-take, we need to give first?
That's what was going on.
Then they'll give to us too.
I'll write a statement to explain this.
Then that will solve the problem.
Mr. Park was revealing it all.
Let's go to the company.
James.
The man named James
at ICV company?
?is Mr. Park.
James Park.
Mr. Park Sang Joon in
Jordan is your cousin?
What's going on?
What happened?
It's his son.
Every crack is completed
by the internal conditions.
Right?
Mr. Park.
Geu Rae.
You jerk...
He would've thought
of it as compensation.
Park Jong Sik!
In 2008, a $0.12 mil. export
contract was sealed.
Steel accomplished the
biggest deal by itself.
Mr. Park was in charge of
communication with the locals.
He solved every single problem and
helped the contract to be signed.
Ok, ok, what is this?
It's the general manager's
company card!
Let's party tonight!
Oh, thank you.
Come on.
You should be enjoying the night.
What's with you?
You should go to the end.
Right.
Go until I die.
Please sir.
I'll treat you to a drink.
This is no fun.
They get all the money.
I just get a salary?
This won't work, sir.
Excuse me?
Mr. Park.
What are you doing?
You can't do this.
It must have started like that.
He must have thought, "This
is how you get compensated".
You can send 20% here.
[Dongyang Bank]
He would come to ask for returns.
You should work on a big scale.
Just take over an old local company.
Get some reliable men in there
and you'll rake in money regularly.
Whatever sales profits
come in are yours.
You should get paid for your sweat.
Don't you think?
He must have opened his eyes
and started to see the world.
Mr. Park.
Where's the boss?
I don't know.
Why act busy like that?
Right?
Everything must have
seemed silly to him.
This apartment is much cheaper
than the market price.
Nice location.
He must have started to think
life was easy and natural.
Then everything became nothing.
How will it turn out?
I don't know.
From an outsider's point of view,
the good triumphed over the evil.
Company rules work differently though.
Company rules?
Let's just be satisfied
that we did what we could.
How did you think of finding
out Mr. Park's English name?
Yeah.
When I checked the fax, there were
many Parks among the executives' list.
When I asked what his business
card said, it was James Park.
Auditing team?
When Baek Ki asked the
Audit team about Mr. Park,
the names of Mr. Park's father and
this company's CEO were similar.
How did you know he was
Park Sang Joon's cousin?
Mr. Park only has one older sister.
His father has only one brother.
So I assumed it must be his cousin.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
I think it's his cousin.
Wow.
Make sure no other
companies suffer damages.
Yes, sir.
[12:22AM]
I'm tired.
You clearly told her to come back?
Yes.
I made it clear a female
can't do anything there.
Yes.
Where are you?
[Ha Sung Joon]
Mr. Ha.
Are you home?
No, I'm driving now.
I heard it didn't work out.
How could you just go
home when things changed?
I told you to go straight home as?
What?
What are you talking about?
So don't worry.
After I go to Incheon Port,
I just need to make two more trips.
Everything can be
completed by tomorrow.
You fool!
You idiot!
Are you trying to screw me over?
You crazy witch!
How could you do this to me?
You moron.
You don't have to do it by
tomorrow, so come back now.
I'll get someone tomorrow,
so come back now!
Mr. Ha is so mean?
How could he curse at you like that?
Young Yi.
You still want to work here?
Why must we get treated like
this after working so hard?
Where is the justice?
We really worked hard.
Are you ok?
You frigging witch, do you want to die?
What would you have done if
you got into an accident?
You know how bad an industrial
accident is to the company's image?
I'm sorry.
Get out of my face!
I'll just park?
Beat it!
-Hello.
-What's this?
Sorry.
Bye.
The level of responsibility
differs upon position.
The head of the dept. and general
manager will have it tough.
Especially tougher if you're higher up.
Especially tougher?
You'll be relegated to a petty position.
If the police investigations prove
the case to be bigger,
you'll have to leave.
People think we just wear neckties
and work like a block in the wall.
We think our actions won't
affect society or the company,
but work is our life.
It's still a game of Go.
Eventually.
That's what Cho Chi Kun said.
Succeeding at a game of Go
doesn't affect the world.
You're right.
It's still a game of Go.
Regardless of the world,
it's still my whole life.
What's wrong with you?
So pathetic.
Why is Sales Team 3 involved
with Resource team's business?
It's such a pathetic game of Go.
I found out the reason today.
It's just a game of Go after all.
Because it's still Go.
My game of Go.
Because it's my work.
Because it's
the world given to me.
[Misaeng]
Don't be suspicious.
Just focus.
You didn't come to our team
for a different reason, right?
Giving rewards and
punishments is my job.
Mr. Choi will be in trouble.
It will get uncomfortable.
You could become a conman
underneath the boss.
If you play games at work,
it won't be good.