Not Yet Alive
- Bring the files now.
- Yes, sir.
[Episode 17]
Payment slip, Mi Ra.
Is the T/C ready?
We need to send it over.
You can't press me when you
give the files so late.
- Only I would do this for you.
- Ok, hurry up.
Sir, the T/C…
Sales Team 3, Jang Geu Rae speaking.
The SMC water tank meeting?
The time…
I'm sorry, but the person in charge
has changed due to internal reasons.
To Mr. Kim Dong Sik, sir.
The first digits are
the same, ext.1216.
Yes.
Thank you.
Bye.
[Misaeng]
Is it really the market price
in Turkey now?
Yeah I know, but it's kind of difficult to follow
for us to accept the price you offered.
Oh really? Including that one too?
Okay, I see.
But I'll need to take this matter for
our internal discussion and
we'll come back to you shortly.
Is that okay with you?
Just a second.
Baek Ki.
Bring the Turkey budget.
Yes.
I told you many times you
can't be doing your work only.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at multi-tasking.
Sorry. I have a few more questions
on the cost you're talking about.
I've printed it out.
Mm-hmm.
Even a simple printout from
you looks professional.
Is that so?
Yeah, it's neat and smart, just perfect.
Now you see that?
I like your jokes too, Young Yi.
Yes, I'm studying them hard these days.
Yeah?
Are we allowed to act like this?
I don't know.
- I selected the subcontractors.
- Mm-hmm.
They'll manufacture what Ulsan
couldn't within two weeks.
The contract is complete.
They've been on it for
three days so far.
Sounds good.
I feel relieved now.
The Ulsan factory also said they'd
work hard to minimize our losses.
Sounds good.
You take charge of communicating
with them from now on.
- Yes.
- Good job.
I'll go have a cup of coffee.
Sure, sure.
How about Saturday, friends?
I'm not interested.
Come on, stewardesses, I'm saying.
They're smart, kind, and hot.
So we should go on group
blind dates for work…
Why should we go on group
blind dates for work?
What are blind dates?
It's the only way to meet girls,
the way to confirm your love for
co-workers and an opportunity to exhale.
We need to hibernate.
Are there any girls around us besides
transvestites or handsome Young Yi?
What?
What about me?
- Hello.
- Hello
Hello.
The arrival is tomorrow, right?
What time?
4:00, sir.
Oh gosh, he should just give
up if the company opposes.
I need to finish the Vietnam
case and Ms. Sun is too much.
It's just too much,
I mean think about it.
We'll start working late tomorrow.
We'll have to be prepared.
She went to Pakistan on a business trip.
She asked our team for help too.
I guess Sales Team 1 isn't too excited.
Yeah, and the company
isn't really either.
There was an earthquake
in Pakistan last month.
The Pakistan government
requested for assistance.
If we can lower the price and
payment won't be immediate.
But Ms. Sun just accepted that.
From a humanitarian standpoint.
So much work, no effective results
and the team isn't backing her up.
Ms. Sun will suffer on her own.
She seemed to be exhausted.
But
why were you talking about me?
Better go.
Suk Yool, those files from Fabric…
Oh, regarding those…
Don't you know what I mean by,
go do it since I chose this item?
Is this item from Mr. Choi?
Yeah.
It's a solar energy development
business for China.
Mr. Choi worked on it for a whole year.
If we make the contract
it's $0.5 bil. business.
It won't be as hard as you think.
Since this will back it up.
[Solar Panel Export]
It's all set up, so you just
need to get the contract signed.
What do you mean, this will back it up?
Is this the first time
doing business with China?
Are you talking about connections?
Solar energy development businesses
are national projects in China.
I thought nothing was
decided with Poshin.
Look.
They'll get this business.
Mr. Choi's judgment is good
enough to say that will work.
Think it over this week
and let me know on Monday.
Hi, Mr. Chun.
Mr. Choi?
Why?
Why's he giving us such a big item?
Take it.
If we pull it off, it'll be worth
2-3 years' performance results.
I don't feel good about it.
It's not like us to use connections.
Didn't we do whatever we could?
If we don't do this, they'll
say we're totally incompetent.
Also, using connections
is normal in China.
So what's there to feel bad about?
Yeah?
This isn't about good will.
What?
Using connections is normal in China.
But in many times, it's not legal.
We could get in trouble.
And the bigger issue is, the
connections for this are strong.
[Solar Panel Export]
Failure to obtain the order of the
solar energy business despite the connections,
could get our team
who's in charge blamed.
And Poshin obtaining this solar energy
development business is
out of our hands.
Everything is possible if
only they get this business.
Should I treat this gum disease
or just leave it?
But
I like that about Mr. Oh at times.
This isn't about good will.
Failure to obtain the order of the
solar energy business despite the connections,
could get our team
who's in charge blamed.
Mr. Chun.
Hi.
I'm good.
I don't know what's going on.
What's with Mr. Choi?
How do you really think?
You really don't like it?
You want me to be honest?
Mm-hmm.
To be honest,
I want to do it.
If it succeeds,
our team will really become huge.
We'll be able to move
away from the bathroom.
Poshin has always been in the business
in China, so it's likely they'll get it.
It's also a big company.
But
I don't know why Mr. Choi…
It's important for him too.
He could become vice
president by its success.
Vice president?
But backup is necessary too.
To prepare for the 1%
possibility of failure.
I'm sure he wants to use our
team as his bullet and shield.
That's all the more reason
Mr. Oh won't do it.
There's no reason to at all.
Mr. Choi's intentions are obvious.
It's totally different
from the Jordan case.
No need to stick to it.
I guess.
But I still want Mr. Oh to do it.
Since it's much more likely
it'll succeed as you said.
If only we make it, we'll…
Are you done?
What?
You didn't go for the demonstration?
The China electronics researchers are
coming for product demonstration.
- I told you yesterday.
- Oh, right, geez…
Did Mr. Oh leave?
Yes, he did.
He looked miserable with worries
as if it was the end of the world.
But he made it there?
He said he needs to go to see
if there's anything to sell.
He's coming now.
The blabbermouth
factory manager too.
Oh, Mr. Ko!
- How are you?
- Good.
- Take care.
- Sure.
Oh, you're so good-looking.
Hi.
Oh, my, you keep getting prettier.
Hello.
Oh, our ramen hair Mr. Kim,
nice to see you.
Take the jade cushion back.
It hurts my bottom.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You need to get over that, the
same thing happens with medicine.
You're all talk.
Sir, why didn't you send us the
report after the claim was resolved?
I asked you a few times.
I'll tell them to send it right away.
You really don't need anything?
No.
- What about a jade mat…
- I don't need it.
- What about a jade pillow…
- I don't need it!
Mr. Kim is so diligent.
You work so hard.
When will you get promoted?
I've only had this position
for three years.
Then won't you be
promoted next year?
Then Mr. Ramen-hair will
be Manager Kim.
But
it took years for you
two to get promoted too.
Drop it, will you?
Oh, not you, Mr. Ko.
You can't just make
it by putting in time.
Right, Mr. Oh?
Hello.
Who's this?
I've never seen him before.
This is our new employee.
He's the China factory
manager, Mr. Seo Jin Sang.
He sits there, Jang Geu Rae.
Hello, I'm Jang Geu Rae.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Seo Jin Sang.
Your team must've really grown.
With these visually outstanding
new employees and all.
How many new employees are there?
Excuse me?
Have you heard of Baekdusan deer honey?
Here, come on.
Ok, ok.
You know about sanghwang mushrooms.
They're effective and expensive.
Deer on Baekdusan eat none
other than those rare mushrooms.
Then they poop.
The round droplets fall.
Then flowers bloom from the poop.
Then bees work hard to make
honey from those flowers.
That is Baekdusan deer honey.
- Poop?
Imagine how rare it is.
Flowers don’t always
bloom from deer's poop!
That's ridiculous.
It's good for men's stamina.
It's so good and…
I can't explain it.
I didn't make it to sell it.
You can tell by the packaging, right?
You can leave since
it's good for men.
It's useless for women.
It's great for men only.
I guarantee that.
But it's good for the skin.
This?
You should all taste it.
Here.
Here, take it.
Here, here.
You should all taste it.
Don't waste it.
Don't be greedy.
Yeah.
Geu Rae.
What?
What's the staring?
You think this is fake or something?
No, sir.
Ok.
I have a small inn in
a Gwanghwamun alley.
I'll give you my contact info.
Call me if you change your mind.
Inn?
They all think you're in a hotel.
Oh, I can't stay at hotels.
I can't sleep with
the commotion and all.
Even when I go abroad,
I don't stay in hotels.
Isn't it a waste when you're
only sleeping there?
This is how I roll.
I'm frugal.
And I'm showing you this valuable…
You know what I'm saying?
Even rich people can't
buy this rare stuff.
You don't know what I'm saying.
Ok, good day.
Have three spoonfuls a day with meals.
Geez.
She acted like a smart one alone.
I'm surprised you're
really naïve, Young Yi.
What?
No.
I like it, great.
- Three spoonfuls a day with meals?
- Yes.
I'll take it regularly.
Thanks, Young Yi.
This is just sugar water…
Be quiet.
I don't want it.
Hey, it's Baekdusan deer honey!
Have a spoonful a day
with breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
- Baek Ki.
- Yes.
You've been duped.
Excuse me?
Thanks, anyway.
Deer honey?
Good for men's stamina
and women's skin?
I'm giving it to my mom.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
She'll hit you with the fish tail.
- What?
- Oh, nothing.
Just help him out since he's needy.
He's a good guy deep inside.
What?
Mr. Chun.
You know Mr. Seo too, right?
Yes, we know he dupes us.
Dupes us?
It's weird, where did
my fountain pen go?
I'm sure it was here.
It's so weird.
This is how I roll.
Oh, it's deer honey.
Yes!
What?
I'll be stationed abroad!
Where, when?
- Singapore, next May!
- Show me.
Great!
You know how hard I tried
to send you, right?
Of course!
That's great.
Yes.
-What's this?
- What?
Mr. Yoo in Resource Team 2 is going too?
England?
When he only had his
position for a year?
That's too soon.
Their team is just on a roll.
Gosh.
Mr. Hwang.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Good job.
Shouldn't you give your family a call?
- Yeah.
- Call them.
Great.
- So many people go this time…
- Yes.
We'll miss you.
It'll happen next year.
- Mr. Hwang.
- Yes?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Honey!
We're going to Singapore!
I told you I'd go!
Of course!
Yeah!
Gosh.
Mr. Hwang sure is lucky.
Remember all the trouble
he overcame last time?
- Yeah, Mr. Ko worked so hard then.
- Yes.
I had high hopes to be honest.
Mm-hmm.
With Mr. Park's incident and
the Jordan case and all.
Though I don't have to go.
You should!
Working abroad is the highlight for us.
I think I should've gone to
Congo when they told me to.
After I rejected that,
I haven't gotten any offers.
I don't even hope for
America or Europe.
That one refusal must've
made a bad impression.
I'm sure that's not why.
I'm sorry.
What?
No!
Come on.
What are you saying?
I'll go get some air.
Can the San Paolo items be
delivered by the deadline?
Yes, we'll check the process
again with Chungsol.
- Chungsol?
- Yes.
Ok.
Tell Chungsol's Mr. Lee to
meet the deadline this time.
It was delayed last time, right?
Was it?
Yes, I'll make sure he meets
it this time, so don’t worry.
Ok.
What?
You know Chungsol is always
late on deliveries.
- So what do you want me to do?
- We can't work with them.
There are other companies.
Geez.
I didn't want to get you in trouble.
I think Youngmin will be better.
Who do you think you are, jerk?
What do you know about that
company to say such crap?
Crap?
Oh, right.
Your nickname as an intern was Dog.
Stop acting like a crapping dog.
You pulled one thing
off and got arrogant?
I think working with a lazy,
irresponsible company
like Chungsol is worse.
What, jerk?
Stop calling me "jerk", sir.
I have a name.
You should appreciate how
I didn't embarrass you.
Don't get emotional,
but look at the facts.
Be rational and reasonable.
Are you related to Chungsol
by any chance?
What, jerk?
You didn't embarrass me?
Yes, sir.
No, sir.
I'll be right there, bye.
You sociopath jerk.
You want to have a go?
Ok, go ahead.
Let's do it, jerk.
Let's see if you'll leave
or I will.
Dang, that hurts.
Oh…
Smoke.
Is Dong Sik
ok?
You know…
Gosh.
The company's so mean.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
Thanks.
I hate work because of the sociopath.
Shall I apply to work abroad too?
Mr. Hwang should treat you to drinks.
He should.
Are you putting it off
to get married first?
Yeah, that'll be more stable.
Dong Sik got screwed again.
I don't think Mr. Oh cares about
others when he's focused on work.
If you work like a dog anyways,
isn't it better
to have the results that shows?
He doesn't have a luck for a boss.
He always looks for work.
Why, that…
But their team gets along.
Is it a Meetup to get along well?
A boss who procures items
with results is preferable.
Of course!
Good for him and myself.
You get promotions and incentives.
People badmouth them, but
actually want such teams.
Sales Team 3?
They keep asking for trouble.
Let's go.
Why listen to nonsense?
Come on.
When will he get promoted if the leader
keeps bringing unprofitable work?
Is he his slave or what?
He's so not helpful.
Mr. Kim is a fool to cover for him.
Why, those, I'll just…
Come on, don't be childish.
Why, those…
Let's go.
I'm so mad.
This is Kim Dong Sik.
Have you read my email?
Yes, I called to check the costs.
There's a difference from what we sent.
Can we call you back after a meeting?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hello, this is Kim Dong Sik.
The freight criteria must've changed.
Yes, please adjust the costs.
Mr. Hwang.
Come here.
We heard you guys talk outside.
Why blabber about it so much?
So, watch what you say.
Geez.
What?
Sorry, we were careless.
I didn't think he would've heard us.
This is crazy!
Why, those…!
You jerks!
Hey, what do you know
about my boss?
You think you can do
as much as Mr. Oh?
Mr. Ha.
Mr. Yoo.
Do you guys have a right to say that?
What?
Who do you think you are?
Come on, sit down.
Stop it.
Can't you see he's drunk?
Don't aggravate him now.
Guys.
You know I hate cursing, right?
I'll say one thing today.
You ****ing jerks!
Have you been told off like us?
I was told off so much,
I can't lose weight.
It's because I keep
drinking from stress!
- Let go!
- Let's go home.
Let's go home now.
You rude jerks!
Dong Sik is a sociopath too.
What is the world coming to?
What are you saying, jerk?
Why'd you ask me to come
when I wasn't even there?
That's what colleagues are for.
Remember when we were new?
The four of us couldn't handle
Dong Sik when he got drunk.
I know, even all of us isn't enough.
Hey, Resource Team started it!
Why, you…
Hey, can't you see I enjoy the work?
How dare you ***ing
say that about Mr. Oh?
I'll say this, how dare
you **** around?
Hey.
You, hey.
Stop it.
I'll rip your mouth
if you say crap again.
What?
1, 2, 3.
Hey, let's go.
You ****ing Mr. Sung!
You ****er.
One more soju, please.
Dang.
What?
Geu Rae.
Yes.
What are you doing?
You have lots to do?
No.
Why aren't you leaving?
Since you're not leaving.
Go.
Uh, Mr. Oh.
Is something wrong?
No.
Go.
Ok.
You know,
the people you meet
can change your life.
If you follow a fly,
you'll end up near a toilet.
If you follow a honeybee,
you'll end up in a flowerbed.
So that's why I'm in a flowerbed.
Yeah.
When will he get promoted if the leader
keeps bringing unprofitable work?
Is he his slave?
He's just not helpful.
Mr. Kim is a fool to cover for him.
[Scary wife]
Hi, wife.
This isn't your wife.
Dad, it's Joon Woo.
My little one!
Ask him if he drank again.
Did you drink again?
No.
He said no.
Big bro came in first for Taekwondo.
I got 100% for my spelling test.
Middle bro came in last.
Tell me one thing at a time.
You're not busy now?
You can talk?
Of course, you can.
Middle bro can come in last.
Really?
Then can I come in last too?
Can you share like him?
Then you can.
Mom said only fools share too much.
You need to be selfish
to become rich.
You know what being selfish is?
Yeah!
I can only be sent to Congo.
So what?
Is that our team's fault?
Is it Mr. Oh's…?
Stop it.
Geez.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Here.
Hey.
You know where Dong Sik lives?
Not my place, my dad came.
My wife is sick now.
You know my house is tiny.
He's too big for it.
I'm staying at my brother's.
No.
Why not?
It's all messy.
Find his home phone no. and call it.
He lives alone!
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Hey.
Gosh, you're heavy!
Wow, I never thought I'd
come here with you guys.
Mr. Sung ran away?
He's amazing.
When did Dong Sik gain
so much weight?
He's heavier than when he started.
I nearly fainted taking off his pants.
His legs
look like an elephant.
That's why I said let's call
his home in the country.
Hey,
we still got together
thanks to him, right?
Yeah.
We used to be close first.
Now it's all about performance
and connections.
Right?
The Resource Team is the best.
Hey.
Come lie down here.
I don't sleep in places like this.
I'm leaving soon.
I'm sorry.
You should take some medicine.
- Sir
- Thanks.
Are you ok?
I feel better now.
See you on the rooftop.
Dong Sik.
Yes.
You want a different team?
What are you talking about?
Our team is difficult.
I heard about yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Don’t worry too much.
I really
don't agree with them.
That's not it…
I'm like that.
I'm here because I want
to work like a dog.
You know,
I want it,
but it's not the case with you.
When I'm working, I forget
about those around me.
- So…
- Mr. Oh.
I like working with you.
That's it.
And I'll take care of myself.
I'll tell you if I want to change teams.
Ok, you're right.
Let's work.
What happened to the Vietnam case?
I got the materials to review,
but Ms. Sun hasn't received the report.
She'll have to come before proceeding…
- Yeah?
- Yes.
I'll get to work within an hour.
Yes, I'll send the report by Tuesday.
Why don't we talk again
after the report?
Yes.
Yes, I already checked the
Vietnam case on the plane.
Yeah.
We just need higher
expenses for manpower.
Yeah, tell Sales Team 3.
Yeah, bye.
Sales Team 1, Cha Gyung Ho speaking.
Yes.
What?
What's going on?
Ok.
Bye.
Ms. Sun collapsed, sir.
- An ambulance came near the airport.
- What?
What are you talking about?
Come in.
Hi.
Is she ok?
She'll need an overall checkup.
The main reason is a sleeping
disorder due to stress from overworking.
She'll need to be hospitalized
for a few days.
With overtime work and
the business trip,
it was too much.
Just think of it as an
opportunity to take a break.
It was too much.
I feel upset and guilty.
I was promoted.
Really?
Congratulations.
But what's with your expression?
Actually, we fought because of that.
I told her to quit since
I got promoted.
She had a hard time.
Maybe I was too hard on her.
So she'll quit?
No.
She didn't want to quit.
It's a big part of her since
she's worked for 15 years.
She said she needs to protect herself
to love her family.
Mr. Oh, we'll get going now.
Ok, I should go too.
I need to pick up So Mi.
I'll call you next time.
Thank you for your time.
Sure, get going.
Thank you visiting.
Mr. Oh, dissuade Ms. Sun.
The Pakistan export
case won't get much
credit and the company doesn't like it.
I can't understand why
she insists on it.
Actually, you two are similar.
Anyway we need her.
Tell her to get lots of
rest without worrying.
Tell her so she understands
since you're close.
Sure.
Get going.
I'll stay a bit longer.
You woke up.
Are you ok?
You didn’t have to come.
Come on.
You're getting up, hold on.
It's going down.
Keep still, keep still.
I'm good.
You scared me.
You'll have to stay for a few days.
Mr. Um and Mr. Cha came.
They're telling you
to get plenty of rest.
They said don't worry about work.
Worry?
You should delay the
Pakistan case for now.
Get rest,
and work twice as hard
when you're out.
Maybe I shouldn’t do it.
I don't think I can do this one.
If it can't be delayed, Mr. Um
and Mr. Cha can do it.
Or
is it because your husband
told you to stop working?
When I was thinking about quitting
because of what he said,
I talked to Mr. Lee.
And he…
Have you heard about Ms. Sun?
What?
She told Mr. Lee she'd quit.
It must've been withdrawn.
What?
Then what about our promotions?
We'll have to wait longer.
I don't want to go to Sales Team 3.
I want to work under
you for a long time.
I thought of them as family and took
care of their personal needs too.
They were only thinking
of getting ahead.
They thought of my resignation
as an opportunity.
They both had high hopes.
Since I'm sick and all,
I don't want to do it anymore.
It's because they haven't worked
under you for a year yet.
Mr. Oh who's working abroad always
complimented you as
an old subordinate.
It'll be different when he comes back.
Just wait.
Hi.
Did you have dinner?
Yes.
I heard Ms. Sun collapsed.
Due to stress from overworking.
I see, gosh.
She should take care of herself.
You had esophagitis
due to stress, right?
You suffered a lot before.
Yes.
Bye.
And about Geu Rae…
I heard there was a switch
in the person in charge.
Sorry, it's the company rule.
I tried my best, but I couldn't help.
No, sir.
The company is tough.
He did so much for it.
So you need to be strong.
It's not good for the company either
if they keep changing contract workers.
You need to keep teaching them
from the start.
Let's get together for dinner sometime.
Ok.
Mr. Um.
Yes.
About the Pakistan case.
You two will continue with it, right?
- Anything I can do to help?
- What?
Sir.
You heard us.
You couldn't dissuade her?
Sir.
We're dying here.
I thought of them as family and took
care of their personal needs too.
They were only thinking
of getting ahead.
They thought of my resignation
as an opportunity.
They both had high hopes.
How's Ms. Sun doing?
She's ok.
We were worried.
- If you're done, you can leave.
- Yes.
I'll get going.
See you on Monday.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
I'll shred this before I go.
Ok.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Did Suk Yool leave?
I don't think so.
Call him for me.
Hold on, Suk Yool.
Hi, this is Mr. Oh.
You know the cooperation request
regarding Sales Team 1?
Yeah, bring that for me.
Bye.
Mr. Lee.
I'll go.
Will you stop it?
I said I'll go.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
See you later.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
I only have one left.
Take it, quick.
Come on.
You won't share?
Oh…
- Suk Yool.
- Yes.
It's Friday and you have lots of work?
Work?
No, I'm leaving now.
Yeah?
- Then have a nice Friday.
- Thanks.
I'll see you at King's
Hotel tomorrow morning.
Excuse me?
What?
[Cooperation request regarding
Pakistan Al Rashim]
You'll make the Pakistan report for me?
Yeah.
It's due on Tuesday, right?
I don’t know the details,
so there will be a limit.
But I'll finish up to 80% by Sunday
afternoon, and you take care the rest.
Mr. Oh.
I need some healing.
I have to think things through too.
How can you heal yourself
by doing my work?
That's my style, you don't like it?
You'll really quit?
- Yes.
- Don't!
If you can't collect the payment,
there are alternative ways to do so.
Do as much as you can.
That way, you won't have regrets.
It won't be easy by yourself.
Don’t worry, I won't do it alone.
What?
Here's the data, oh, and you recorded
the Pakistan buyer's meeting, right?
Of course, you did.
I'm sure it was towed.
My husband couldn't bring it.
Hi.
Young Yi.
Come in.
Hurry!
Geu Rae's here.
Hi.
Hurry!
Yes, Mr. Oh, here.
Mr. Oh called me.
I was free this weekend.
Mr. Oh threatened me.
Yes.
Why must I be here now?
I should be having a
date with a stewardess.
Geez, when would I ever have…
- Hurry up and come!
- Yes, sir.
The sample is here.
I told you to bring many.
Fabric, cotton cost: 2.96.
Cvc 2.53.
Tc 2.1.
Other parts $0.2…
We're selling blankets to Pakistan?
- Yes.
328, so the 50,000
yards would be $150,000.
Isn't that expensive?
It sure is, but I've hidden that fabric!
Geu Rae.
No one took this leftover 47,928
yards which had different issues.
So extra funds aren't necessary.
$1 per each for manufacturing costs.
Our factory guys will
provide any lacking fabric.
Ok.
So now we need a manufacturing line.
I'll take care of that somehow.
Work, Geu Rae.
Yes.
Yeah.
I know it inside and out,
and there you go again.
Still please delay those finished
with the Malaysia case.
Really?
Thank you.
I have seven lines.
Will you do it?
Yes.
I'm a pro with recordings now.
What?
It must be English.
You're right.
I'll finish this first.
Geu Rae.
Ok.
Young Yi.
Hello.
I'm Ji Young Sun from
One International.
Hello.
Pakistan Ministry of Health…
This is Karanshi Kibu.
Karanshi…
- Kibu.
- I'll tell you the spelling later.
- Ok.
I think we should listen to it together.
I don’t know English.
You need to know if it's a girl or guy.
Thank you for coming all
the way to Pakistan.
Thank you…
Have some sandwiches.
- Have a sandwich, sir.
- Yes.
Shouldn't we add info about
the long-term profits?
Oh, by focusing our benefits
when receiving the payment?
Yes, just add that…
Your cost estimate is wrong.
Oh, you're right.
Hold on.
The cost and function…
…should be done by Excel.
Ok.
Good.
He won't like a presentation
with too much info either.
Right!
Yes.
Do you want some water?
Ok.
Where are you going?
I'll get some air.
I'll go with you.
Me too.
Where are you going?
It's cold.
What's that?
Here!
Ladies first.
And then Geu Rae.
And Baek Ki.
Mr. Oh is amazing.
How could he do this?
We're young and we're sacrificing
our weekend for another team's work.
Are we a guerrilla army
or human weapons here?
But
I kept thinking.
If that happened to
me later, would you all
do what Mr. Oh did for her?
Could you?
I'll guess your reaction
according to your character.
Geu Rae.
"Shouldn’t we have cup
ramen for late nights?"
"If you don’t like it,
I'll totally change it!"
Come on.
"Mr. Oh."
Baek Ki.
"I'd like to help, but I can't move."
"The basics are really important."
Suk Yool.
Young Yi.
"I'll drive a truck if I have to!"
"But I'll be moving like a snail!"
See?
Only I'd look bad.
Since I won't go.
Does that make sense?
Talking so much made me thirsty.
Drink mine.
I'm ok.
Let's go wrap up.
Ok, come after you finish that.
Ok, smoke.
See you later.
Baek Ki.
I'm impressed.
Come on, we didn't need Geu Rae!
Alright.
Thanks for the two days.
I'll visit Ms. Sun at the hospital.
Shall we go too?
No, it'll get crowded.
Go home and rest.
I'll treat you to drinks.
- Good day.
- Thanks!
Take care.
Good day.
Let's go.
Ok.
Oh, no!
How can you forget
something so important?
Did you forget something?
Should I get Mr. Oh?
All you care about is work.
We have 5 hours 34 minutes
till Sunday.
Let's spend the next 5
hours like it's 15 hours!
Let's go this way since Mr. Oh's there.
Hold on.
Remember this passionate day.
Let's forget about the past two days.
This is no good.
Work shouldn’t be like this.
Why'd you sleep holding me?
You got into my arms.
Geez.
You slept on the floor?
On the bed…
[Export regarding blankets
to Pakistan Al Rashim]
I can't believe this.
Just thank me.
You wouldn't let me rest
and you want a compliment?
You and I both
rest by doing work.
What?
That sounds like a nightmare.
Don’t say that, please.
Gosh, our new employees
must've worked hard.
Here.
Oh, my!
It reminded me of how we worked
on the China housing construction.
The human mind is so fickle.
You get ignored by team
members you trusted,
find out their thoughts,
get sick,
and want to drop everything.
Then because of these few pages...
Life is all about change.
But
what are you concerned
about these days?
What's your worry?
What is it that you want
to heal yourself with work?
I feel stuffy.
Can you get some air?
Our team is like a bullet
and a shield.
Mr. Choi is really
amazing.
I hate myself for putting up with
him when I know his intentions.
Let me guess
why you're doing this.
What?
You want to see who wins, right?
You think you're at
the point to do that.
Your unscientific views.
What?
You think you're fighting
with Mr. Choi.
If you succeed with the Poshin case,
he will have to acknowledge
you and your team.
Support is necessary since the
vice president position is on the line.
Aren't I right?
Ok.
Then how's this?
One thing is for sure.
With a $0.5 bil. order, promotion
to a dept. head is possible,
and after that,
you get the authority
to use whoever you want.
That's the company rule.
Geu Rae.
You still think he can't make it?
Will I become a full-timer if
I continue working like this?
I told him he won't.
High hopes,
and irresponsible consolation
are all useless.
The company is tough.
So you need to be strong.
One thing is for sure.
With a $0.5 bil. order, promotion
to a dept. head is possible,
and after that,
you get the authority
to use whoever you want.
Dong Sik was screwed.
When will he get promoted if the leader
keeps bringing unprofitable work?
Should I wake the kids up?
Oh, let them sleep.
This is nice.
I'll ask my mom for some
mustard leaf kimchi.
Ok.
That's nice.
Your mom's kimchi.
Don't you hate me at times?
Maybe you always do.
It's faster to tell
you when I adore you.
I like it when you eat my
food without complaining.
Maybe I've changed after
I got married.
Tell me.
What?
You know…
Can I
do something for someone?
butt in about someone
else's life again?
You think it's right to
help others?
You can forget about it now.
Let Eun Ji go now.
Just bury her.
What…
Do it.
Just do it.
Do whatever you want.
You haven't done anything wrong.
That's what I think.
You would do the same thing
if you could do it all over again.
And I think that's right.
Come on.
I'm not that important...
Exactly.
You only think about
what you think is right.
Everything else doesn't
go however you want it to.
You're acting all influential.
You think you'll just be
able to boss people around?
I thought you were
saving the country or something.
The soup is salty.
- Don’t eat it.
- It's ok, come on.
He never gets sick.
He rarely catches a cold.
I can't believe he took a half-day off.
He's has a lot on his plate
these days.
He helped with Ms. Sun's
work on the weekend.
He must've overworked himself.
He'll have to make
a decision by today.
I'm worried.
You only think about
what you think is right.
Everything else doesn't
go however you want it to.
Maybe dad didn't go to work today.
Maybe he slept in.
Maybe he's going in late
since he got promoted.
You can't go in late because of that.
Maybe he'll get in trouble.
Hey, kids!
You should go to school.
What are you doing?
Yes.
- Yay!
- Bye.
Bye!
Come in.
[Misaeng]
Jang Geu Rae!
It's not Mr. Oh's style.
Then why did he accept this business?
Why Sales Team 3?
What else?
Switch to a full-time position?
If I can help with anything…
I'm Young Yi's dad.
Something's fishy.
He got bribed.
Sang Sik.
If he gets promoted, he
can become a full-timer.
Mr. Oh.
I'll make it happen.