Not Yet Alive
Hey.
Are you crazy?
What's with you today?
I said let's revive a project which
was on hold,
not evaluate my report.
That's not what happened.
I analyzed as you?
Right, you "analyzed" it, found
it didn't suit the market trends,
and the research is off!
That opinion just came
out during the review.
Revisions are necessary since
the report was made long ago
and more data is needed?
You're basically saying
the report is good for nothing!
-That's not what I'm saying?
-Shut up!
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Jung is looking for you.
This is no dumpster.
One guy throws them away,
another picks them up.
I picked them up first.
They're mine.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 7]
A meeting to decide on Sales
Team 3's new business item.
The Finance team is for China.
I can see that.
[China rare earth resources import]
Clearly.
The best plan A as well as
plans B and C are reviewed.
I wonder if crude oil import won't work.
It keeps lingering in my head.
Mr. Oh.
I think you should go with
something reliable this time.
It'd be preferable if
we went with plan A,
but it seemed Mr. Oh
preferred an item on plan B.
Things aren't looking good in Iran.
The U.S. enforced an embargo
on Iran's crude oil
and the reason isn't clear either.
Nor do we know when the
embargo will be lifted.
I know.
It's tough.
But I still want to go with it.
I have a good feeling about it.
Go stones hidden in the
palms on one's hand.
You get a feeling after a while.
Just like hood winkers hide
a single card in their hand,
some Go players hide their
opponent's stones in theirs.
Then let's report it to
the Risk Management team.
They can do the final check.
Ok.
Get the materials ready.
I'll pursuade the dept. manager.
Sure.
Mr. Oh won't be trying
to deceive the company,
but he's trying to be
cunning with all number of cases
under consideration.
The reason a newbie
like myself can see that...
is because that prudent
man wasn't able to read
Mr. Kim's unsatisfied face
from ignoring the data.
Isn't the China case safer?
Yes, but the Iran case's
profits are higher.
You know crude oil can
help Chemicals too.
Can you get the approval of
Finances or Risk Management?
It's too risky in this day and age.
Too risky.
I'll do whatever it
takes to get approval.
Mr. Oh shouldn?t be doing that.
Aside from Iran's state of affairs
the dept. manager suggested the
China rare earth resources proposal.
[Rare earth resource: Essential
for high-tech businesses]
He goes against it.
Is Mr. Oh aware of that?
Of course.
Then why?
He thinks easy ones can
be done by anyone else.
So he keeps obsessing
over hard, risky items.
It boils his blood, I guess.
He's very competitive, huh?
Though he can relax a bit now.
Honestly, everyone's
climbing up the social ladder.
He doesn't care about his
performance ratings at all.
What we really need to see
the results at this point.
I mean Mr. Oh needs to be promoted.
What can we do?
-Let's do it well.
-Huh?
He wants to do it,
what can we say?
If he can't, he'll get drunk
and wreak havoc with us.
It's on hold.
On hold?
Our team passed it, but
Finance rejected it.
Rejected.
Also rejected.
Go get their approval.
Huh?
Who knows?
It could get into the next
quarter's sales proposal.
She'll be wasting her time.
Finance will never approve.
We kept submitting revised versions
every quarter and nothing happened.
How can she pursuade them now?
If she pulls it off,
whose business will it be?
Hey.
If that happens, we have
to go jump off a bridge.
Why didn't you give her
the opinion from Finance?
Come on, she should
find out for herself.
If she can't figure it out,
she'll run over to Mr. Oh again.
You frozen or something?
Mr. Oh?
Don't think of reporting anything.
You need to be competent for that.
An incompetent guy trying
to help is the worst.
Submit the Steel data soon.
Yes.
Mr. Oh.
So business proposals can't go
through unless Finance approves?
No.
They're not easy to pass.
Even if the other
team members approve,
half of them are rejected
by the manager.
She's extremely meticulous.
Even if your daily performance
is good, she won't go easy on you.
Unless you're 100% prepared,
you'll be in trouble.
Excuse me.
But I think her way of working
is extremely sexy.
Who are you?
Never mind.
There was an old smiling mask.
I was shocked the moment
she turned around.
It felt like lightning
cracked my head open.
You saw the manager of Finance.
Manager of Finance?
-Yeah, you said smiling mask.
-Yes.
She's not bad.
She's quite practical.
She listens to the newbies' opinions.
In a nutshell, she's open-minded.
- Open-minded?
- Just like?
?you.
Oh, it's falling.
Take care of that.
Ok.
Did you check the data thoroughly?
Yes, I did.
Where's the B/L draft?
Hello, sir.
Yes, negotiations are under way,
but revisions are being made to the documents.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
Mr. Kang.
The documents you requested.
Thanks.
Also, Mr. Kim wanted to ask if
negotiations have started.
That'll be ready tomorrow.
When the invoice packing is
ready, ask Mr. Kim to call me.
Or you call me.
Yes, sir.
Sir, is our team not going
to prepare a sales proposal?
It's under way.
Don't you worry about it.
Why shouldn't I worry when
I'm in the Steel Team too?
Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
You like to make things
bigger than it has to be?
Or get attention?
-Sir?
-What's with me?
I hope this answers you.
I don't think you're fully trained yet.
Huh?
Since you still want to do it?
?do this.
I just gave you work.
Make an Excel chart.
What's with your face?
Have you seen this when you
were working in Resources?
It's about carbon emission rights.
[Carbon emission rights: Right to emit
a certain amount of six greenhouse gases.]
This was on hold.
Yes, I was told to work on it
for the next sales proposal.
I don't know why it's on hold.
So?
You said you'd do it?
That you'd get approval?
I don't think that's what Resources
wanted to hear from you.
Just let them win.
Just say, "Sorry, I can't
do it, I need help."
As far as I know, the business
team approved it,
but the manager of Finance didn't.
Manager of Finance?
The fastest way to get
a reply is to go to her.
But it won't be easy to meet with her.
Just... lose for them.
It looks like it's going to rain.
Yeah.
I think it'll be a quick shower.
You want to have a drink later?
Huh?
Boss badmouthing time.
Dong Sik, did you look
into the Iran item?
They said they'd
review the documents I sent.
Sales Team 3,
is this the Risk team?
Did you check the documents?
Yes, the Iran case?
Give me the documents, Geu Rae.
Yes, there won't be any problems
later as long as we have cooperation.
Meeting at 3PM?
Please hurry and
check your email.
Thanks.
-Dong Sik!
-Yes
One International,
Jang Geu Rae speaking.
The documents are ready.
I'll have them approved
after Mr. Oh reviews them.
Bye.
-One International, Jang Geu Rae?
-It's raining.
Shall about a drink after work?
I'm busy.
Hello, sir.
Victory!
The email we requested?
You should drink and release
stress from bosses on days like this.
Look at our circumstances.
What do you think?
Please leave.
Mr. Oh.
True tradingmen would go for drinks?
-Dong Sik, the Iran data.
-Yes.
Don't you agree?
-Please leave.
-What is it you want to say?
Geu Rae, wrap up and go
drink with him, he's right.
No, sir.
Baek Ki, let's have a drink together.
All the newbies.
Thank you, Mr. Oh.
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
Hello.
Come on.
The two alcohol lovers
won't come, I guess they're fine.
Let's get out.
Why?
This place is for having dates.
It's not a man's place.
Suk Yool...
What?
You said you didn't want to drink.
You should've consulted me
with your concerns, Young Yi.
Baek Ki has his own worries.
How can he be counselling you?
Look at his face.
He looks so perplexed.
He couldn't refuse.
Yet, has nothing to say to you.
You shouldn't give people
trouble like that.
Here, nice.
If I were you?
?I'd go see the Finance manager.
That's not easy.
There are procedures to follow.
She's a difficult person to deal with.
Her face is different
from what you'd imagine from back.
The question and answer
is totally different.
It was just so shocking.
I'm told she's a great person though.
She's practical and open-minded.
She listens to the newbies too.
Mr. Oh also said she's quite flexible.
Don?t be so careless
about others' business.
I understand.
It could be something that can't
be shared with you, Geu Rae.
Procedures could be much more
important than you think.
Since they're a type of promise.
Most people trust in, prepare for,
plan, and execute that promise.
I hope people who rely on
those promises aren't fooled.
Let's do it.
Young Yi.
I'll just do it.
They might like the newbie's vigor.
Ok.
I agree with that.
Here.
Get out.
Huh?
Can't you see I'm working?
I'm sorry.
You're newbie Ahn Young Yi
in Resources Dev. Team 1?
Yes.
I don't know what you
want to ask me directly,
skipping your direct bosses
but that's not right.
Your bosses will get in trouble, right?
I'm sorry.
Get out.
I told you not to go.
Who do you think you are?
You went there looking all proud.
You're not crying, are you?
Hey.
What's she doing?
[You've got mail
from Ahn Young Yi.]
If you're late, you're late.
Why the excuses?
Just forget it.
Come to my office.
Don't say sorry, just
don't make mistakes.
I'm going see the Finance manager.
What?
Come in.
Thanks for the apology
email, that was wonderful.
I like people who acknowledge
their mistakes.
I'm sorry.
You're working on the
carbon emission item?
-Yes.
-Why?
You know Finance has put it
on hold for 1.5 years, right?
Yes, I do.
Did your team ask the
newbie to revive it?
Why?
This is our review data
regarding the item.
Submit a report on why you think
we turned it down by tomorrow.
Why?
I think it's a fair offer for
a newbie who ignored procedures.
Yes, ma'am.
Make sure I can see it first
thing tomorrow morning.
Yes.
From our point of view...
I'll submit a report
from Finance's viewpoint
as well as another report on the issue.
Dang Finance manager?
She must've heard of Young Yi's rumors.
You know what she's like.
I'm sure she's delighted, looking
back on her newbie days.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
I'll take the year's
difference into consideration.
I'll review, edit, and resubmit it.
Yes, I've rechecked it, it'll be fine.
You're working late and drinking coffee?
You should have dinner.
You're leaving for the day?
Yes.
Though it's embarrassing.
It can't be as bad as what happened
to me and the Finance manager.
Wow, so you're doing it.
We don?t know yet.
I can revise it only when
I know why it was rejected.
I still don't know yet.
I bought this when I was
buying hangover tonic.
Since a scar won't matter much.
You'll just scratch the scab off.
Thanks.
Hang in there.
You want to take a break?
Sorry for egging you on.
I think Baek Ki is right.
I think it worked out for the best.
You need to kick the
ball to make a goal.
That's true.
We're both suffering
because of items on hold.
Actually, Mr. Kim dissuaded Mr. Oh.
Since it was decided on by
upper management already.
I wonder how Mr. Oh is
planning on pulling it off.
He wants to visit all the
executives and pursuade them.
Rethink it from the other's point
of view and make it happen.
I think that's his unique strategy.
What?
Your team?
?seems tight.
Rethink it from the other's point
of view and make it happen?
Make it happen?
I was imprudent.
It's not going well?
I have no clue.
I could've written something fancy,
but I didn't want to be deceptive.
I'm sorry.
I apologize again.
I'm disappointed.
I thought since you spent that much
time, you'd come to a fruitful conclusion.
Regardless of not being able to
write it, I thought about something.
Yeah?
I think from each dept.'s point of view,
the interpretation of the
proposal could be different.
When Sales says there's potential,
Finance could interpret
it as needing further review.
Similarly, "positive response"
could be interpreted as "nothing
has been decided yet."
And?
Learning about Finance's mechanism
regarding business budget administration
was the biggest benefit for me.
The abstract estimated
profits in my head
are reevaluated with
solid grounds by Finance.
There are businesses you can
still pursue and others you can't.
Also, the fact that
the judgment is classified.
[On hold]
[Grade A]
[Grade B]
[Grade C]
[Returned]
If my proposals go on
hold or get rejected,
I won't think about what went wrong,
but what I didn't satisfy.
That's better than the report.
You can return.
I'll think about the penalty.
Yes.
What was your major?
Political science, ma'am.
It suits you.
-Did you study accounting on your own?
-I'm studying now.
Ok, hurry up and learn it.
Accounting is a language of management.
Thank you.
I'm impressed.
Baek Ki, is the Excel file ready?
Here you go.
Come here.
Is there a problem?
I did it as you told me with the data?
What's with this new format?
Haven't you been trained
about our format?
If you can check the data,
I'll revise it later?
You know I'm really busy.
Who told you to do as you please?
Baek Ki.
Don't you know the order?
Confirming data?
That's basic and you want
me to waste my time here?
You input data and
then revise the format.
What company uses that process?
You can leave now if you want
to work for another company.
A client meeting
regarding the Iran item.
It started late because
of their team's morning meeting
and there are differences in opinions.
Let's try to make things work out.
I have to make a report
to Mr. Oh by noon
and Mr. Kim has to meet a buyer at noon.
So we're in a hurry.
We just scanned through the points to
check and left the client's office.
Iran's situation is challenging
but I hope they improve.
We need to review the documents
if circumstances change, right?
Why, you think they will?
I don't know.
It is a dilemma.
We're not sure if it's
a positive or negative situation,
but Mr. Oh thinks it's positive.
I hope he has a solution.
I'll get going.
Bye.
I don't have time to check this again.
I'm sure it's fine since
conditions haven't changed much.
You should recheck it
if you feel uneasy.
You felt uneasy during the meeting?
I think you should check
if you feel uneasy.
Just like you had a good feeling,
you should check if you don't.
Sorry, sir.
There's something further to check,
so I'll make a report later.
Yes, sorry.
Nothing's changed, right?
Yes, it's identical.
Necessary changes have been made.
I'm sorry.
I just wasted your time.
It's ok.
You know what's risky
when doing business?
Letting it become a race.
You just keep looking forward.
Then you'll crash into something.
Glad you mentioned that.
-You're still here.
-Hi, Mr. Kim.
Great timing.
Let's go when things are looking good.
Sir.
We'll go make the report.
Bye.
One International?
Huh?
Yes, sir.
It's the Iran employee.
The EU placed an embargo.
Mr. Oh.
You did think the embargo
could be placed, right?
-Yes.
-What about the long-term duration?
Yes.
Then end of discussion.
Forget it.
We can do it.
How?
The risks due to the long-term
embargo are so obvious.
You know there will be bigger
risks and you can do it?
Mr. Oh.
It's not that simple here.
There's no way to bring the oil in.
We can get it in through Turkey.
Where?
It's bordering Iran, they're on good
terms with Iran and not an EU nation.
Iran is importing a
considerable amount of energy,
so it won't be easy to
go with the embargo.
We can buy it through a Turkish company.
There is a company we've
worked with for a long time.
They're in the country.
There are different
businesses with Iran too.
There are circumstances,
but we can make a request to Iran.
Turkey?
What do you think, Risk team?
I like it.
I agree, sir.
We have a solid infra with Turkey.
Cheers!
We just need the executive
director's approval.
-Ok.
-Just the procedures are left.
Good job, guys.
What's wrong?
I? what?
Oh, you don't look too happy.
No, I am.
What is it?
Tell me.
Will the manager be ok?
He focused on the China item.
We didn't order that.
I ordered it.
The results will soon show
if it's good data
or not.
Hello?
Go with the China item.
Keep this.
They're our team's assets.
Yes.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Let's eat meat.
We'll have a burner, please.
This is the norm, so
it's just the beginning.
Up until now, it was a warm up.
Will you leave the theater
only after the trailer?
Mr. Oh.
The burner is hot now.
We should put meat on it.
Just the part of the meat has changed.
Sir, forget about head meat,
please give us premium beef here!
Don't drink it from the bottle.
What was your excuse
for drinking today?
Nice!
You're always happy alone!
Geez.
Yeah.
I was so happy, I drank.
Can't I drink?
I'm going to roast grade A
premium beef from now on.
Drink up.
With this?
Geez, you must be crazy.
Oh, my!
Hey!
Come here!
What's with you?
I wonder how Mr. Oh felt.
The news articles he had
collected himself,
numerous memos,
cutting out the changing
news of the times?
?did he think the same thing as me?
I told them to do it last July.
Mr. Oh started on a new item the very
next day as if nothing ever happened.
Did you check the
circumstances with China?
Yes.
I'll check and let you know.
I think around August.
[Iran petroleum import]
I have a small box now.
Geu Rae.
Did you collect the reports from
the economics research center too?
Yes.
The more my box fills up, the
more I will have learned.
Ok, let's gather up.
This spells trouble.
China's situation is so different
from when we started.
China increased their
importing product line.
They're in charge of 90% of the world's
market with rare earth resources,
so this will make importing hard.
How come other countries
don't go into development?
It can really ruin the environment.
That's why China has a quota system.
If you look at today's
research center report,
it means we should stay low for now.
I think that would be smart.
Mr. Oh.
Do whatever it takes.
I'll back you up.
The situation doesn't look
like that will cover it.
Business isn't easy.
Everything has variables.
With the Iran item, you ignored
the international circumstances.
Why are you hesitating now?
You know it was reported in my name.
Don't whine, ok?
Don't pull pranks because
yours was rejected!
Going forward.
Not yet?
Let's go forward.
Mr. Kim, the report?
Look at this.
They're all saying it's
a super-cycle trend.
[Super-cycle: Long-term price
increase trend of over 20 years]
Things aren't looking good.
We'll have to see.
Set a meeting with China tomorrow.
They can come or we go.
We should recheck it.
Reports keep coming in.
The dept. manager used
to work on this item.
We need to do it and he wants it.
I know, but the circumstances
have changed.
Yes.
A long time has passed.
Since I brought up
the item on hold again.
Whether if it's the dept. manager's
performance results or not,
I'm the one responsible for
delaying the stable item.
Also, worsened situations
due to an aggravated environment.
It's our team's responsibility.
If you can't resolve this,
he'll have a hard time.
We have to do it.
[Progress report]
Honestly, everyone's climbing
up the social ladder.
He doesn't care about his
performance ratings at all.
What we really need to see
the results at this point.
I mean Mr. Oh needs to be promoted.
Let's do it well.
Of course.
Now I should be able to
fulfill one man's workload.
You're alone?
Sir.
They're all out?
Yes, they all just left.
Tell Mr. Oh I want to see him.
Sure.
Hey.
It's much riskier than you said.
Don?t you know China has increased
their business and shifts are being made?
Yes, we're going to supplement that.
I'm sure I told you the warnings
when the first proposal was made.
Among the three items, the one you?
That's not it.
Among the items you brought, I said
"let's try that" about the safest choice.
Oh, but the China item
now was your idea?
It was just an idea.
An idea isn't a proposal.
Is it?
I'll do well so it doesn't
have a negative effect on you.
Hey.
Who do you think you are?
I'm sorry.
Anyway, go ahead with
your item, Mr. Oh.
Make reports right away.
Delete the part where
it says it's my idea.
That's such a minor detail.
Then what about backup
for the China item?
Don't you have hands to work with?
What backup?
The company is backing you up!
Yes, sir.
Come see me.
Where are you going?
The dept. manager wants to see me.
He wants to see the business
data out of the blue.
-Why?
-It's obvious.
He wants to take credit.
You know with our business
from the briefing last time.
He was blatantly claiming
your proposal was bad.
Do a better job.
What?
He said you go a different
direction from what he wants.
Do a better job for him.
You should change things
for improvement.
Kiss up to the bosses too.
I'm too sorry to get promoted.
Yes!
Mr. Oh, I heard?
Get out.
It better work.
Don?t think of the price and look
into all the companies with
quota systems.
Yes, sir.
Geu Rae.
Go with him.
Yes, sir.
We could force it.
But all the companies with quota
systems have different prices.
You could get blamed for everything.
We're going to change our item too.
Non-quota?
No way, it's smuggling.
People with those baits
wouldn't be at big companies.
I'm surprised there's
60% more smuggling.
It's hard to get a big
quantity without smuggling.
Patience is a virtue, but
our team can't afford that.
-What's Mr. Kim like?
-Who?
The dept. manager.
A typical man earning a salary.
That's what I'd call him.
He's perfect for the times.
He's quick and eloquent.
Very sharp.
What can a company employee look
forward to besides promotions?
Do you think that's all
there is to it too?
So far?
Since I haven't found anything else.
Let's save Mr. Oh?
I mean our team first.
So obnoxious.
Hello.
You should watch where you're going.
Your lower body is weak, huh?
A man's lower body is key, huh?
Use the stairs from now on, not this.
Aren't you going?
Huh?
Thanks.
Is your foot ok?
What about my foot?
I told you to come to my team.
You're suffering because you didn't.
The carbon emission item?
I like it.
You can't make it
a national business, right?
Right.
I can't make a profit structure
that Finance will pass.
When did you learn Russian?
You seemed good.
In college.
I was an exchange student for an year.
What about you?
I lived there for 2 years for work.
I learned a lot then because
I always loved Russian.
There's a word for "white
night" in Russian, you know?
You know the ballet dancer
Mikhail Baryshnikov?
I was moved by that movie as a kid
and vowed to go to Russia someday.
You know their famous theater?
Mikhail Baryshnikov is dancing there.
Vladimir Vysotsky sings.
You don't know, right?
He's a famous revolutionary singer.
Like a wild horse.
The Russian culture has tragic beauty.
It's a U.S. film.
-The U.S.?
-Yes.
Not Russian?
I got carried away.
I heard you left the rare earth
resource case with the quota system.
Mm-hmm.
Dang.
I didn't know China would be so fickle.
I go there like I drink water.
I never had a hunch.
We overlook what we think is obvious.
Tell me about it.
We overlook what we think is obvious?
I better go.
Thanks.
Use that item?
Thanks, Mr. Oh.
We overlook what we think is obvious?
[North Korea's rare earth resources:
Estimated at 20,000,000 tons]
Yes, sir.
Something new?
Yes, there's news.
What is it?
I found a solution for
the rare earth resources.
What?
The Korean Resource Corporation is
developing them with North Korea.
Huh?
Estimated at 20,000,000 tons.
It will become twentyfold
once it's official.
Set a meeting with the Planning
dept., your employees should come.
It'll be in an hour.
Yes.
Sir, this?
Work on it and I'll see to it
after I'm done with Sales Team 3.
Weren't you going to
report with our item?
When did I say I'd do that?
It started out with my item
from Sales team 3!
But?
Sir, our manager changed his mind.
What's wrong with him?
I'm going crazy.
It's just procedures.
Sales Team 2's item
will be reported too.
That's not the issue.
It has to be an item backed by him.
Please pursuade him.
I've never had such
a big meeting before.
They're just saying it was for a meeting,
but not acknowledging it officially.
Connect hotlines to the research
centers, government depts.
and the public corporation.
Check and review the content.
The planning team uses
connections to secure the latest info.
Yes.
This isn't the time for management.
Yes, we're looking for
the right timing politically.
The collected info is made
orderly by Mr. Oh and Mr. Kim.
Rare earth resource stocks are shaky.
Of course, all the meeting
content is recorded.
That's my job.
Your team should submit
a progress report twice a day.
-Yes.
-That's all for today.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Sir.
Hello.
What is it?
Do you have time this evening?
You have something to say?
Let's eat together.
Shall we?
I have two hours.
This is too much.
Don?t worry about it.
Mr. Kim was set on our item.
He wants to change his mind.
I mean regarding promotion and
all, it's totally your timing.
This is too much.
-Mr. Lee.
-Organize this.
Don't worry about that.
Geu Rae, get the minutes
ready and send it.
Yes.
How long does it take?
I said use simple keywords!
Sales Team 2's screams were desperate.
What can a company employee look
forward to besides promotions?
Delete this, make it work!
You think this will?
Nothing is simple.
Will you think?
Mr. Kang is good.
The Finance team can't complain.
He's perfect.
Of course, he's great in other aspects.
What?
You want to have a drink?
Aren't you going to leave?
Wrap up now.
Yes.
Check if it's accurate.
Yes, sir.
I can't believe this.
What's with your expression?
Another mistake?
We'll have to add to the
next sales proposal.
So annoying.
What is it?
What is this?
The Korean carbon emission
item with the Russian forest?
Is this possible?
It seems so.
This? sounds ok.
Finance will pass it.
I know.
Now I get it.
You said Mr. Cho in
Fabric is the scariest.
I'm scared too.
I hate it!
Right?
I don't care!
Let's go before we're late.
Yes.
You know where to come to eat, right?
Did it go well?
I think it went well.
The research with the market trends.
-I like it.
-Yes.
The completed item is fine.
I'm saying, let's think
of it as decided.
Mr. Oh is creating a business.
Let's cheer him on.
Sir.
There is much to work on.
Decided?
You should get this
for your business.
Geez.
Sir.
Call Mr. Oh.
Why in the restaurant
where Mr. Ko is eating?
Sir.
Hi.
What?
Your whole team is here?
Here, have a glass each.
Yes.
Let's make things simple.
I'll go with Team 2's item first.
Thank you!
Yes.
We'll increase the size.
Since we have to wait for the outcome
about the relations with the North anyway.
Let's prepare and make it big.
Resource businesses should be huge.
Yes, sir.
Happy?
Yes.
Yes!
Ok, let's drink.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Hurray, Mr. Kim!
Great choice.
Sir!
What brings you here?
Our Resource Development team is here.
Yes.
I heard a familiar voice.
So I peeked in.
We were having dinner too.
What a loud dinner.
Looking good.
Yes.
[North Korea rare earth resources
business - Sales Team 3]
Wait.
Can I see that?
Yes.
Rare earth resource?
Why is Sales Team 3 dealing
with the Resource team's item?
It's the Resource team's item.
-Look.
-Yes.
You mentioned rare earth
resources last time.
Oh, yes.
I was going to submit a proper report.
The Resource team should do it.
Mr. Kim.
It overlaps, so why not combine them?
Yes.
Why suffer when there are pros?
Find something that suits Sales Team 3.
It's on me, so enjoy your time.
Find something that suits you.
Let's go.
Mr. Kim.
Sit over here.
Take your time.
Let's go, Mr. Ko.
Yes.
Sir.
Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
We started eating without a word.
We were suddenly starving.
We had to eat something.
I learned why we had to get drunk.
And?
?I can't comfort anyone,
as a newbie.?
?I'm sorry.
She'll kill me.
She must've changed the number.
What time is it now?
Geez.
Gosh.
Honey, lights. Light!
It's on.
Is it bright now?
Why do you drink every day?
Every single day!
Can't you stop drinking?
No.
Why not?
Because it's tasty.
What?
Do you know that taste?
Dang.
Do you guys know that taste?
Do you?