Not Yet Alive
[Previously]
- How about the Jordan business?
- What?
I think it's a good item if
you set aside the corruption.
How could Geu Rae think of that?
Don't they know how the
employees view the team?
I think the whole company was insulted.
Ok.
Let's do this business.
Geu Rae, this is not right.
Make suggestions you can take on.
Are you capable of
supporting this project?
We set it up and we're not doing it.
Don't you know ethics
or have a conscience?
What?
There will be a company
briefing for your proposal.
It's not convincing.
I think PT shows how it could
be bad for our business.
What do you mean?
When you look at a map?
I would say thinking
north goes up is a habit.
Starting with the outline
is a precedent?
but if you're thinking
of changing the content,
I'm against it.
We only think within the structure,
but he didn't think about the limit.
This is absurd.
But if this doesn?t work out, I think
I'll be really mad at you, Geu Rae.
What have I done?
Mr. Oh.
Why are you out here?
Let's go in, sir.
Ok.
Good luck.
Let's go in.
[Misaeng]
Thanks.
[Episode 13]
Everyone will be imagining an
obvious report in their minds.
They'll be looking for opposing points,
or already be prepared.
We can clearly feel how they
think won't go as expected.
Is Sales Team 3 ignorant or courageous?
You're such a daredevil.
Mr. Park's case was resolved, right?
Then shouldn't they end it with that?
You were promoted with the CEO's
encouragement, so
aren't you going too far?
Right.
Ok,
let's start.
The CEO is coming.
I was curious and I had
some time until my next schedule.
I can join too, right?
Sure, please sit down sir.
Thanks.
Sit down.
It's ok.
Mr. Oh, sorry for interrupting.
You can begin.
The payment for the Russian forest
carbon emission case has arrived.
Please check.
Ok.
- So this business is on.
- Yes.
Good job.
Young Yi is good, isn't she?
Dude.
Sir.
Thanks.
Young Yi.
This is an additional business
for Minerals, so just revise it.
For TC, use your name.
[TC: Trading contract, inputting buyer,
supplier,
Excuse me?
order info in the system
for confirmed contracts]
You take charge of it.
Thank you.
Young Yi, hi.
Hello.
Young Yi, about Sales
Team 3's presentation?
There was Mr. Choi and all
the executives behind him.
The mood was just totally
solemn like I've never seen.
It's like I peed and came out
and it's freezing outside.
It was? so cold.
Will that be ok?
I've never seen this
kind of presentation.
What have I done?
Just watch calmly.
Yes, sir.
Please look at the screen.
It's regarding the '93 Indonesia
natural resources illegal trade.
[Famous Conglomerate Uses
Foreign Branch for $6.8 mil.]
The Indonesia branch manager paid
trade costs with retention money,
Indonesian currency for a currency
margin bringing a big
loss to the company.
Declaration of war.
A battle without guns has begun.
Why bring that up suddenly?
What are you doing?
In 2002, the Myanmar tungsten
export corruption case,
in 2007, the Singapore wine
in 2011, the Russia medical electronics
export corruption case have occurred.
In 2002, the Myanmar
tungsten export corruption case,
bribery with the major
stockholder, ME Holdings.
In 2007, the Singapore wine
export corruption case?
The corruption cases I heard of
during job training and Mr. Park's incident
were dealt with in much more detail.
With this export corruption
case with the double contract,
the commission was divided among them.
And as you know,
recently there was
the Jordan used car export business
commission corruption case.
There was a commotion as expected.
They must have been reminded of the
sorrow of filling in someone's position
which became vacant due to that
case or those perplexed times.
"So what about it?"
"What are you trying to say?"
I could read their faces.
And?
And the company resolved each
incident accurately in a prompt manner?
But there's no stopping now.
They've been resolved nicely.
And they've been erased.
What are you trying to say?
What is it you want to say?
Our company was always like that.
You're so arrogant.
-What are you trying to say?
-It's over.
-Get to the point.
-Mr. Oh!
What are you doing?
Why are you bringing that up now?
We've chosen to walk the path of not
bringing up businesses that had issues.
Do you know?
We're going ahead with it.
What happened to those businesses?
And going on strong.
What is wrong with him?
This is conviction.
What are you trying to say?
I wonder how many mental wars you need
to fight to build such conviction.
Now these are other companies'
performance results
for the businesses we didn?t
even want to think about anymore.
Shinsung earned $300 mil.,
Haesun made $270 mil.,
HW Group $160 mil.,
and Hongjae $130 mil.
These businesses are still stable.
After the cases?
Please look at the expected profits.
...the expected profits for
the businesses were announced.
2.7%. HW Group...
Their approximate
values and accurate predictions.
It's nearly identical
to the expected profits.
Please look at the stock prices
before the business started
and those for two years after
the business started.
They've risen along with the
success of the business.
In the game of Go, when the
opponent disregards me or is greedy?
Should the incidents be forgotten
since there has been punishment?
If you use tricks as if to avoid
battles even when it's important?
We had only revealed the offenses.
...you need to chase it until the end.
It's totally different
from the rehearsal.
If we're not on our toes, we
could totally ruin everything.
He's taking a huge risk now.
From now on?
Changing the tide,
a new strategy will be used.
From now on, we'll
start the presentation
for the expanded Jordan
used car export business.
From now on?
Changing the tide,
a new strategy will be used.
From now on, we'll
start the presentation
for the expanded Jordan
used car export business.
The goal of this business
is to secure 40%...
Mr. Oh came back to the familiar One
International presentation manual.
Jordan is a small country,
you can see they have
a tiny domestic market.
It's in the Middle East,
but they lack resources including oil.
But thanks to a stable
political state and
their location in the
center of the Middle East,
intermediary trade is developed.
We have about 280,000
exportable used cars.
90,000 are going to Jordan.
This is a large amount compared
to Jordan's population.
Because they're re-exported
to Iraq, Saudi Arabia,
Syria and spread to the Middle East.
We'll connect with the branch manager
in Amman, Jordan for current info.
Hello, sir and executives.
Jordan has shown a very positive
response regarding the business.
Having met a few companies,
I know they have been
extremely positive about it.
They have stated they want to do
business together proactively.
You can see the lists on page 18?
As the presentation went on,
Mr. Kim's conviction was
conveyed to the executives.
Regarding the contract and I'm
sure it will be a secure business.
That's it for our team's Jordan used
car export business presentation.
Thank you.
It's not bad.
Yes.
It mustn't have been easy
to take over the subordinate's job
who was punished because of you.
So we tried to focus on the
true value of the business.
It's a well-prepared report.
Were you able to handle it all?
Yes, the Jordan team helped greatly.
I heard the youngest member in your
team proposed redoing this item.
Yes, the new employee,
Jang Geu Rae.
His name is Geu Rae?
Jang Geu Rae?
I'm not sure who?
Where is he?
Hello.
It's him.
You're a daredevil.
Geu Rae?
[Geu Rae: "Yes" is Korean]
Yes.
Why did you think of this proposal?
That's? that's?
?that's? because it's our company.
Our company?
Yes, our company.
Yes, it's our company, of course.
It's obvious but somehow
we feel shameful.
I know.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
I hope you can succeed with the
Jordan used car export business.
Thank you.
Good job.
Mr. Lee, shall we postpone
today's golf to another day?
I want to stay at our
company for a while.
Yeah.
This was totally out of
the box for a trading man.
Didn't you do something daring
like that 20 years ago too, Mr. Lee?
Yes, I did, many times.
Good job.
Thank you.
You too.
What's with you?
Get up, you little fool.
Yes, thank you for your help.
No, you guys did it.
I need to go to Abu Dabi soon.
What will you do about the
contract and schedule?
I'll let you know after
things are discussed.
Yes.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Mr. Chun.
Yes.
Thanks for hanging in there
when it must have been stressful.
You've been a great help.
It's been?great for me too.
Should I send an appreciation mail to
those who were at the presentation?
I'll do it.
You send messages to the concerned
depts. and get confirmation.
Sure.
Where's Geu Rae?
He's still acting like a naive fool,
so I told him to get some fresh air.
Come on, here is Geu Rae.
Tell them.
There's nothing to say.
See, you're all arrogant now.
So you're the first to have
a meeting with the CEO, huh?
Come on.
You started to be arrogant
the moment Mr. Oh accepted your idea.
Congratulations.
I didn't think you'd
pull it off this well.
Thank you.
That makes me feel weird.
It makes me want to do well
so I don't end up like that.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I'll get going.
I have to send an email.
Me too.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Come here.
Aren't you being too greedy?
Are you jealous of someone
struggling from the bottom up
when you have great specifications?
What?
Don't be that way.
Actually their team's
incident isn't normal.
They're trying to resolve
existing issues.
I think working on it so there are no
problems to begin with would be better.
Maybe it's some kind of deception.
Right.
Deception.
We just have to reach it.
See, you're all arrogant now.
So you're the first to have
a meeting with the CEO, huh?
Come on.
You started to be arrogant
the moment Mr. Oh accepted your idea.
[Kang Hae Joon]
Ms. Shin, did Mr. Kang go somewhere?
What?
Nothing.
[Soju]
You want to tell me something?
Uh, no.
That feels great.
Hello.
- You're off?
- Yes.
Good job hanging in there another day.
Hang in there tomorrow
too and keep surviving.
- Yes, thank you.
- Bye.
Shall we go to Yu's restaurant?
Sure.
Let's go for chicken ribs!
Sounds good.
It's not too small a party
for a big success, is it?
We'll make it big.
It's cold.
Gosh, it's cold.
[Mr. Kang Hae Joon]
Are you off for today?
Yes, are you too?
Yes, see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Here, good job.
As they say the
good comes with the bad.
If you get drunk today,
you'll have an accident.
Let's drink too much.
Yes, sir.
Give us another
bottle of soju, ma'am!
Why, you?
It's nice how the table is full
now with these pretty boys added.
Four pretty boys, right?
Enjoy.
The chicken ribs are amazing here.
Eat up.
Gosh, Geu Rae.
Now you get it?
There's nothing we can do yet.
I understand.
You might not be able
to relate, Geu Rae.
Procedures might be much more
important than you think.
Since they're a kind of promise.
Maybe people trust that promise
and prepare, plan and execute.
I hope the people who believe that
promise aren't made fools of.
He really doesn't get it.
Doesn't he know how the
employees view the team?
Baek Ki.
Mr. Cha hates tardiness
the most.
You must be in a good mood.
A first attack, just the thought
of it makes me feel great.
If it's right, it's right, and
if it's wrong, it's wrong.
I have a resignation letter in here.
Hi, Baek Ki.
Suk Yool.
It's me.
I have a favor to ask.
What?
Hello, is this really Baek Ki?
Hurry up.
I can't believe you're
asking me a favor.
Ok.
I like you like this the best so far.
Ok, mm-hmm.
Bye.
What was that?
A secret.
I shouldn't cramp Baek Ki's style.
Cheers.
Hello.
Hold on!
Get in, Baek Ki, I came here for you.
You're 10 minutes late.
The favor?
Thank you.
Take it off.
What?
You can't go in like that.
Take it off and come for it later.
You should ask your
training boss for help.
Can't he do this for you?
It's too awkward for me.
Awkward?
Then I guess you can't share
your concerns with him.
You're right.
That's cold.
Although the psychopath
isn't a good senior either.
- Did you go to a sauna together?
- What?
Then it wouldn't be awkward.
Don't ever go to one
before you become close.
Why not?
You'll die of the awkwardness.
See, imagine you're in a tub together.
You can't get out first, but your
skin bloats just sitting there.
Even when you scrub yourself.
It's weird sitting side by side.
But it's weird? sitting
apart like strangers.
You can't do this or that, and you
can't tell him he has
soap suds on him.
Why can't you?
Then he'll think you were
staring at his naked body.
What?
"What?"
A perfect crime.
You're late.
Uh, yes.
Get your clothes, Suk Yool.
Yes.
I told you many times, the worst
thing for employees is tardiness.
Geez.
It's because you're not good
with self-management, Baek Ki.
Yes, I'm sorry.
We'll have to postpone the 6:00 meeting
30 minutes, I'll be there at 6:30.
Why still here? Go.
Finance is checking the budget and
there will be a meeting
with the Legal Team.
Other meetings are set too.
How about if you participate too?
Sure, and be a bit softer since
opinions aren't all positive yet.
Yes.
Mr. Chun.
This is Mr. Lee Jin Tae and he'll take
care of sales regarding the case.
- Hello.
You know Mr. Chun, right?
Glad to work with you again.
Yeah.
This is Mr. Kim Dong Sik.
Hello.
Your build looks like the dept. head.
Thank you.
This is Jang Geu Rae.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
I know.
Did your team's position
become stable by this?
I'm sorry?
Sir!
Hello, sir!
Mr. Ko, long time no see.
-Hello.
- Hi...
Would you like some coffee?
Get some coffee.
Sit down.
Hello.
Young Yi.
Coffee errand?
Yes.
I came to make coffee for everyone
including the new head of the dept.
Then I'll treat you
to your team's coffee.
What?
I didn't congratulate
Mr. Oh on his promotion.
So I'll do that with coffee.
Tell them it's coffee made by Young Yi.
Americano?
Your team will have
a warm end of the year.
You're right.
Time has flown.
You were so busy working,
you didn't realize that?
Maybe Mr. Oh will get promoted again.
Sir.
Would you like some coffee?
Young Yi, get ready for the meeting?
Sir.
Meeting?
Why should she get ready for it?
Yes.
She'll take charge of the Norway case.
There will be a short briefing.
You don?t want it?
Make a separate briefing on your own.
I don't want make-up smell
in the meeting room.
Young Yi.
I think I really get
tougher with time.
I don't feel hurt at all.
It's quite interesting now.
I'll get going.
Make sure to tell them
I made the coffee.
What is this?
Why do I have to get in
trouble for this?
Suk Yool.
- Yes?
- You did this, didn't you?
No, sir?
It's by fault, I'll explain
so he understands.
No, he?
I told you to delete the account
data since it's hard to show it now!
How strong can he possibly be?
There's a secret to real fighting.
You need to attack first.
You gave it to me and told me to
organize it according to order.
When did I do that?
Gosh, what are you doing here?
Geez.
Then why would I have found the
lost data and put it in there?
Will you continue talking back to me?
It's true, why should I get in
trouble for what I didn't do?
A team is in it together!
You get told off together and
take responsibility together!
Then why do you always get out?
What?
Please take responsibility
for your work.
Let's make it a real team.
Wow, look at you.
Responsibility?
You want to see?
what real responsibility is?
Geu Rae, this is the Jordan data, and
you remember the trade
insurance corp.?
Yes.
- Resend it to them.
- Yes.
But do we need to resend it
though we already applied?
That was for our loss and other
companies could suffer damage too.
- Send it soon.
- Sure.
Hello.
- There's a meeting with Chemicals, right?
- Yes, let's go in.
Yes.
We're about to go in.
What?
Geu Rae too?
Sure.
They want you to come too.
What?
Why when he's not even involved?
You're so popular!
Are you like a celeb?
Gosh.
Hi, Young Yi!
Oh, make coffee only
for me from now on.
Sure.
You have many meetings these days.
Yes.
Why do they keep asking for him
who doesn't know anything?
Dang people.
But he's good at taking
notes and recordings.
His meeting minutes are
perfect, you know.
Ha, geez!
- I'll get going.
- Get in!
Bye.
Young Yi, come here.
Hey.
Wear flat shoes.
You annoy people!
Answer me.
Yes, sir.
I heard you did this document.
Hey!
You drive me crazy.
Looking at your document, I nearly
jumped off the plane coming back!
Resident employees
struggle because of this!
Have you made calls with
our people when doing this?
Did you?
I had asked my boss since
I'm not familiar with them.
What?
You asked your boss?
Look at you.
Hey, is he your secretary?
Sir, I said I'd call them
since I know them?
Is it a blind date or what?
What more do you need besides
name and position when working?
Are you all crazy?
You think think is a game?
Please tell us what the problem is...
How far do you think the Norway
resources project has proceeded?
As far as I know, it just
has to be approved?
Right, it just has to be approved.
But why isn't it being approved?
The additional business you guys
sent messed up the schedule!
Just wait when you have to even
if you have nothing to do.
The local team struggles because
you guys pretend to work.
Do you know what you're doing?
A business game.
A business game!
Dang.
Gosh, I thought things
were going great for her.
They say things don't
work that easy.
Let's work.
Are you ok?
He's too much.
Drink it.
It'll calm you down.
We're not in the position
to be comforting anyone.
So there's nothing to say.
Except him.
Try it.
Just suck it.
Like this.
Hello.
- Hello.
Geu Rae.
Your team was in charge
of the Iran case, right?
Yes.
We're thinking of doing an item in Iran.
How was it?
You think Iran's circumstances
will improve?
What?
I'm not asking for
a professional analysis.
I'm curious what your
next move would be.
I don't know.
Come on, why ask him
that out of the blue?
Let's have coffee later.
My gosh.
I have to organize some
storage samples.
I'll get going.
Indeed, there is no direct
correlation
between your school grades
and happiness.
My gosh.
I'm not asking for
a professional analysis.
I'm curious what your
next move would be.
Are you done?
Yes, I just need to finish this.
Can I leave now?
Mr. Kang got off, so you can leave
as soon as you're done here.
Yes, sir.
Go relax at a sauna.
- Oh?
- You worked hard.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Aren't you being too greedy?
Are you jealous of someone
struggling from the bottom up
when you have great specifications?
We just have to reach it.
I'm like this because
I don't think I can make it.
It's just me who's at
the same point.
Don't ever go to one
before you become close.
Then it wouldn't be awkward.
You'll die of the awkwardness.
See, imagine you're in a tub together.
You can't get out first, but your
skin bloats just sitting there.
Is it hot?
No, sir.
Even when you scrub yourself.
It's weird sitting side by side.
But it's weird? sitting
apart like strangers.
You can't do this or that.
I'll get going.
Oh, bye.
And you can't tell him
he has soap suds on him.
Why can't you?
Then he'll think you were
staring at his naked body.
I never thought I'd see you here.
I usually wrap up the week here.
I got all dusty after
storage organization.
Ok.
I'll get going.
I'll see you on Monday.
Mr. Kang.
Let's go for a drink.
Are you saying you're
not motivated for work?
My colleagues seem to
be accomplishing things,
but I think I'm right where I started.
And that? makes me
think I'm lagging behind.
You won't suddenly feel
like submitting a proposal.
It's not that.
Are you jealous of Geu Rae?
I'm not jealous.
But?
I feel mad at myself.
Especially since you're not
a temporary worker like him.
You work for Steel, right?
Didn't I tell you before?
The jobs for Steel are fixed
within the categories.
You need to check and manage
for smooth operation.
You think fixed businesses
have no work?
No, sir.
You know our team's yearly profits?
How much work the required
manpower and related countries?
A lot to do to ensure things to go
smoothly after signing the contract.
Does that all seem meaningless to you?
No, sir.
It doesn?t matter how
it looks to others.
It's not flashy but doing necessary
work is what's important.
We might not see it?
?but don't think it doesn't exist.
The figures we decide on?
are a big deal to others.
You should motivate yourself, Baek Ki.
It'll be tough to survive
if you can't do that.
Yes.
Geu Rae.
Yo, yo, yo.
The bright season for
company employees.
A service for those working for
salary like us, Christmas tree?
The company does care for us,
mm-hmm.
Any year-end plans?
What will you do, Young Yi?
I'll go drink.
Tough girl.
Baek Ki?
I got season tickets for a ski resort.
Awesome, you must really
not have a girlfriend.
And you?
I don't have one either.
-What?
- A girlfriend.
Ok.
You use Twitter?
No, not really?
Someone wants to
follow you, open that.
[Ha Jung Yeon]
Who is it?
- Stop it.
- You said you have no girlfriend.
- I don't.
- Who is it?
I don't know.
It's Ms. Ha.
Ms. Ha?
Who's that?
Who's Ms. Ha?
So Mi's daycare center teacher.
So Mi who?
Daycare center teacher?
Yes.
How'd she find out my ID?
We can ask her.
Come on, give it back.
How did you find out my Twitter ID?
I always searched for it,
it took a while to find it.
Why?
You think this is a joke?
If you want to know,
treat me to a drink.
She's proactive.
Geez.
Why should I treat you to a drink?
Geu Rae, go for it.
-Hello.
- Hello.
Hello.
-Hello.
- Hello.
Hello.
Hello!
I'm sorry for being late!
You replaced the cartridge.
I was going to do it today.
Mr. Kim.
Yeah.
Ok, it's neat, perfect,
and professional.
Good job, Mr. Kim.
Good job.
Geu Rae.
Shall we have coffee?
Sure!
Water too.
He reacts faster now.
I think it's old maid hysteria.
She only treats me that way.
What can we do?
Just put up with it.
She went nuts today.
Hello.
- Hello.
I'm going crazy.
What happened with the resume?
You have wheels on your feet?
Be quiet.
So what?
He's a temp in Sales Team 3.
They'll hear you.
He'll start sending out resumes
after his contract is over too.
Stop it!
- Oh, dear.
- It'll get cold!
Yes.
Come on.
- Yes.
- Don't do mine.
Ok.
I almost cried.
I was almost disappointed.
I'm pathetic to have
been about to smile.
He still sends out
personal year-end cards?
Mr. Oh is stubborn about it.
It's dedication for those
who help us make a living.
- Give me a few.
- Yes.
Here.
- Thanks.
It's the company envelope.
Write Mr. Oh Sang Sik from
Sales Team 3 right here.
Yes.
Thanks to them, my first
kid is going to school.
My youngest gets new
shoes and warm clothes.
Think you're making
a living thanks to them.
Yes.
[Oh Sang?]
I'm making a living thanks to them.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
The first "Merry Christmas."
Thank you.
It couldn't have been better.
Yes!
Be absorbed.
You should always be absorbed.
It all depends on that.
That's the only issue.
In order not to feel the weight
of time that makes you slump over,
you must always be absorbed.
But absorbed in what?
Either alcohol, poetry or virtue.
That's up to you.
But anyway be absorbed.
And at times on top
of a palace stairway,
or on the green meadow beside a ditch,
or in your depressing
room, you wake up.
When you're not absorbed anymore,
ask.
Ask the breeze, water,
stars, birds, or clock.
Ask everything that passes by.
Ask everything that is sorrowful.
Ask everything that runs by.
Ask everything that sings.
Ask everything that talks,
ask what time it is?
[It couldn't have been better, Yes!]
Then the breeze, water,
stars, birds, and clock?
?will answer you.
"It's time to be absorbed."
Sir.
[For Mr. Kang]
[It couldn't have been better, Yes!]
[Misaeng]
You have a girlfriend these days?
Thoughts on marriage?
Thanks for the good news.
How much is it?
-$50,000.
- What?
You look like a hard worker.
It was a tough job, but
don't let that happen.
I can be become a full-timer
at this rate, right?
I can keep working here
Your names keep being mentioned.
Be careful with your body.
That question is not related to work.
You take this.
Don't hurt Geu Rae since
that's like hurting me.
Didn't you say you'd
take responsibility?
Will you do that to Geu Rae too?