Not Yet Alive
I have a question.
Then aren't the roles
reversed right now?
I don't know how Mr. Choi
made that judgment,
but our company actually
has the upper hand, right?
Mr. Seok.
Geu Rae!
Geu Rae.
What were you thinking?
What did I…
Connect me to Mr. Seok.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 19]
Our youngest one made a mistake.
No way.
We don’t think so at all.
I told you last time it's
to make things clear.
Don't worry.
Recording?
Come on, I already deleted it.
Yeah.
I'll treat you to soju
when you come to Korea.
Have a good day.
Mr. Chun and Mr. Kim.
Leave the room.
You couldn't believe me till the end?
- Mr. Oh.
- I told you I'd take care of it.
Geu Rae.
Listen carefully.
What you did today could
actually put the team in danger.
Why did Geu Rae do
something so foolish?
Even if he's not familiar…
Mr. Seok must be so nervous now.
It's like saying Mr. Choi is corrupt,
and Mr. Seok is in on it too.
Mr. Seok is not in the position to
take responsibility for his words,
so there's no telling what he'll do
if he gets negative vibes about this.
And there's no proof for
your distrust in Mr. Choi.
If the case gets out of hand,
and Mr. Choi is proven to
have no fault at all,
our team and you will have to
take responsibility since
you started it.
Geu Rae found out?
Mm-hmm.
You're trying to save me.
You're
trying to make me a full-timer.
He thinks he's affecting
Mr. Oh's judgment.
So I think he wanted to
confirm his suspicions.
He must've wanted to save the team.
Though it was immature.
I'm sure he couldn't take it
thinking it was his fault.
That fool.
He should've discussed it with me.
Uh, Mr. Oh.
I've put Mr. Seok at ease,
so things won't get out of hand.
In order to make sure of that,
we need to show him
we're working again.
You're right.
We have no choice but
to keep dashing now.
Check each company's contract,
make sure it's checked
thoroughly by others too.
Double check Poshin's contract,
and make sure the details
are favorable to us.
What about the agent?
I'll go talk to Mr. Choi.
Yeah, the agent was confirmed.
The details didn't exist
in the previous files.
Didn't I tell you the
circumstances have changed?
I mean the solar energy
power plant business.
I thought the connections
would take care of that.
No, that's the norm.
We need something additional.
Categories were just divided
with potential issues in mind.
Just think of it all as connections.
Then, our profit rate from the
solar panel business would be 0.5%.
That means it's nearly zero
considering the business'
characteristics.
Mr. Oh, it's despite that.
Mr. Choi.
I've worked here for 28 years.
I grew with this company.
I always showed them results,
I mean always.
When the economy was bad, and
other companies were in trouble,
you know how we were?
We found a market using
all my lines in China.
I saved the company each time.
I helped it grow,
and that's how it grew.
This was all possible because I had
made family-like business
partners there.
It's no different this time.
No matter how much
we pay for the connections,
it's for the company.
I respect whatever way you
had helped the company grow.
But please don't use that method
for this case.
We'll proceed with the original
contract we had sent.
Mr. Oh.
That's what the company approved
and that I can accept.
So please help this
business go smoothly.
Please delete the details
on the agent, sir.
Or we won't be able to
work on this business.
If that's deleted,
we'll definitely get
the second business too.
I'll make sure there's no problem
with you becoming vice president.
Mr. Oh.
Proceed as the original
without the agent.
Will that be ok?
Yeah.
Geu Rae, did you get replies for the
emails you sent to domestic companies?
Yes, they're on your desk.
Did you threaten Mr. Choi?
Will that be ok?
He'll accept it.
He has to become vice president.
Your team is good.
Securing that much supply within
a short period of time…
Do you work well with them?
Yes.
Why are you so nervous?
You still get nervous around me?
Oh, what do you think?
Do you think it'll be impressive enough
even without the agent details?
Enough for Poshin to want to
give us the next business?
I,
my opinion is
I don't know.
But
but Mr. Oh will make it succeed.
So please trust him.
He didn't tell you about Geu Rae?
Mr. Park, I asked Chungsol so many
times for the parts statement.
It was delayed, then replaced to
cheap items, not once but many times.
I said no.
You don't care?
Mr. Lee said it was ok…?
No, please call me after
you find a solution.
Yes.
How much will the frigging Mr. Sung get?
Chungsol has to replace parts again.
Yeah?
They must've done so since they
couldn't get the original ones.
They must've done so?
You know it's not that
simple, the quality will…
Will be fine, just be quiet.
They can't change it,
I'll have them come now.
Hey.
Have them come?
If you need them, you go.
Don't you know what
the times are like?
Hello?
Yes, sir, I heard about it.
No, just proceed with it,
I'll get permission for it.
Meeting the deadline is more important.
No, you don't need to come.
I'll call you back in a minute.
Jerk, you made the factory
come to a stall.
Till when should I clean
up after your mess?
No, sir.
Come on, think of our relationship.
Geez.
Yes.
I received it.
I know I've received a lot.
So, I'll pay you back,
I'll keep paying you back!
Geez!
Ok.
I'll pay back all of it.
See you tomorrow evening.
I'll talk to you in person, bye.
Dang.
What is this?
I was hoping my suspicions
weren't true.
Oh, my gosh.
He's really doing something fishy?
Geez.
Hi, have you seen Geu Rae?
We couldn't have lunch together.
He won't answer your calls either?
No, the office is vacant and
his team must be super busy.
Yeah.
Maybe it's because of that.
What?
There's a China-related business.
Mr. Ma and Resource Team 3
were on it originally,
but Mr. Choi seemed to have
given it over to Sales Team 3.
The scale is quite large.
About $0.5 billion?
$0.5 billion?
Yes.
If it's a success, the
team could expand.
I'm a bit disappointed in Mr. Oh.
I thought he was against
all of Mr. Choi's intention.
I felt the same way.
But work is work.
But I'm still disappointed.
Maybe he just grabbed
the rope given to him.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Geu Rae.
Don't say whatever you want when you
don't know what you're talking about!
Don't…!
Don't say whatever you want.
Geu Rae, we…
Geu Rae…
Right, it's a chance to save you.
So I'll do what I can, why you ask?
If I don't do it now,
even if the chance comes next time,
I don't know if I'll feel the same way.
I think Mr. Oh accepted
Mr. Choi's case
since he can make
Geu Rae a full-timer.
Make him a full-timer?
Since he can ask for more people
if he becomes head of the dept.
Then how can that succeed?
I mean, what can I do here?
What can we do?
Probably nothing.
No, I'm sure there's
something like Ms. Sun's…
No.
No, Suk Yool.
This is different from that time.
I asked you to come play
Go, why won't you come?
I'm sorry.
Ok, come when you have time.
See you.
Hello?
Sales Team 3, Oh Sang Sik speaking.
This is Mr. Choi's secretary speaking.
Yes.
He'd like to have dinner with you.
Come on in.
I invited him.
I thought I was being too careless
after giving responsibilities.
He's done a lot for the company,
and I felt I ought to treat him
since I had chosen him
as you said.
I don't know if he's
serious for his age,
or shy.
I asked him to come for a game
of Go, but he won't come.
Oh, you heard of this,
right, Geu Rae?
"A good move for me could be
good for the opponent too."
Let's eat, the bass looks good.
Geu Rae has a lot of work today, sir.
Is that so?
Yes.
I guess we have no choice.
Let's eat together next time.
Yes, sir.
Come to think of it,
isn't there a reason you
need this business too?
I had you come since you
seemed to have forgotten it.
Some people only think of winning
and having the opponent lose.
They're bound to lose in the long run.
I like to lose and
have the opponent win.
I don't like either winning or losing.
Let's have a win-win situation.
You win and I win.
Isn't there a reason you
need this business too?
Let's have a win-win situation.
You win and I win.
I'll do it.
However you'd like.
But I can't just trust you
like I did with Lee Eun Ji.
So?
I'll make this case work
no matter what.
So,
please give me a definite answer.
Promise me that you won't ask
our team to be responsible
for anything related to connections.
Promise?
Should I sign a contract?
It'll be an arbitrary decision.
I'll take responsibility
if there are any issues.
Is that definite enough
of an answer for you?
That's not enough?
I don't know what Mr. Choi's thinking.
I was sure he chose our team
as the bullets and the shield.
But he answers me so easily.
Circumstances always change.
You made progress up until the
point of signing the deal.
You've been a much bigger
success than Mr. Choi expected.
Your team is bullets for him now.
Effective and fast bullets at that.
Plus, he's purpose-driven.
You should just focus
on your purpose too.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
Yes.
I'll see you there at 6:30.
Don't give this month's accounts
over to General Affairs yet.
Why not?
Must I sacrifice myself when
I'm cleaning up for your mess?
Yes, sir.
What about headquarters' work
environment improvement survey?
Just check and submit it.
Since the spent expenses for the
final report should be perfect,
I revised this to this.
Ok, looks good.
Hello.
You should wrap up work in the office.
Don't give kids stress.
You should quit smoking yourself.
Hasn't Young Yi said
you smell gross?
No, she hasn't.
Headquarters will do environment
improvement survey, right?
Oh, yes.
It's such a hassle.
Nothing changes even if you tell them.
Sir, you said you needed
to go to Finance.
Hello.
We're from headquarters for a work
environment improvement survey.
I'm Kang Min Gyung and this is
our new employee Lee Yun Suh.
Hello.
You can give out the surveys now.
You can give it back to
me after you fill it out.
They must've fallen for her.
No way.
Yun Suh!
Don't put your pen in
your mouth, that's rude.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Give it to us, we'll do it.
Don't give the whole thing to him!
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
They say the enemy of
women are women.
She's being mean because
she's younger and prettier.
What's wrong with putting
the pen in her mouth?
Personal habits in public
settings aren't good.
She should've been told off.
She was just cute.
Hello.
Cute?
She lacked the basics.
Her boss lacked the basics.
She embarrassed her.
Embarrassed?
I'd like to ask Young Yi
how she's felt till now.
Mr. Kang.
I always thought your
taste in girls was unique.
What do you mean?
You like stick-skinny girls like her.
Stiff girls that are cold-blooded.
Watch what you say.
I like girls who are proper.
You like giggly pushovers,
don't you?
Come on, get your words straight.
I like warm girls who
can make others smile.
I think you like thin or curvy girls.
Anyway the new employee is my type.
She's cute.
Who do you like better, Baek Ki?
What?
I think Ms. Kang would be fussy.
See?
Your taste is weird.
Yeah.
You're loyal, man.
Uh, Mr. Kang.
I'm disappointed in your
taste in women.
What's going on?
You've been working here for over
a year, and you still don't get it?
The boss' taste is the Bible.
To corny jokes, you go…
Laugh hysterically.
To his taste in food…
"That's yummy."
When he wants to smoke,
"I'll go with you."
You need to adjust to his taste in
music, art, politics, and society.
But you know what's way
on top of all that?
Taste in girls.
You should always say his is the best.
Only if you like that boss.
Hello.
Mr. Kang still doesn't
acknowledge it, right?
What?
Oh, yeah.
His taste in girls is weird.
- It's ready.
- Thanks.
Young Yi, you saw them, who
was prettier among the two?
I thought the new employee
was much more charming.
Right?
See, girls have accurate judgment.
So I want to learn to act cute
since I lack that.
She's the best learner.
Clearly different from
book-smart Baek Ki.
Different in every way.
Oh, I better go.
"Learn to act cute…"
We should be able to say that
as company employees.
Where did Suk Yool go?
I'm glad I renewed my driver's license.
Meeting at the waterfront
of the Han River…
Someone's watched a lot of movies.
Nice.
Gosh, it's Mr. Lee, alright.
Mr. Sung is so nervous.
Now give him money, money,
money for bribery.
What's that?
Suk Yool.
What?
Hi, Geu Rae.
- Getting off work?
- Yes.
Ok.
Is something wrong?
No.
Ok, see you tomorrow.
Geu Rae.
Is work going smoothly?
What?
It should go smoothly, it has to.
See you tomorrow.
Right, life throws tough quizzes
at you to make you helpless.
But it leaves you hints
in funny places at times.
But of course, there's no guarantee
the answers you get are correct.
Hi.
Don't get up.
Mr. Choi.
Sit down.
You're working hard.
Let me know if you need anything.
Yeah, Mr. Kim will be
losing some weight.
Have a good day.
After that day between
Mr. Oh and Mr. Choi,
our team seemed like they wanted
to succeed no matter what.
We only focused on work,
we didn't think about anything else.
- Mr. Oh.
- Yes.
About this, what will you
do for after measures?
The sample test results…
Then one day…
Oh Sang Sik speaking.
Headquarters?
Mr. Oh Sang Sik?
Yes.
We're from headquarters.
We were checking on each affiliate's
belt-tightening policies
and got a tip-off.
Tip-off?
In the headquarters'
monthly earnings statement,
there was a document
regarding the issue
of Mr. Choi's business with China.
I heard your team has a recording.
Recording, what's that about?
The tip-off was from China.
It must've seemed smart to
stay out of the strange game.
Though Mr. Oh's consolation
came right after,
words were recorded and when a
contract employee
pricked his conscience,
Mr. Seok indirectly agreed
without overt denial.
He must've reported it
to his boss with anxiety.
After receiving his report, the
manager in China had a hot potato.
He got it over to
headquarters right away.
How many times are you asking me?
This is totally normal.
They're saying it's not right.
You've always worked like this, right?
I mean for a long time.
Mr. Choi explained how he had worked
for over many decades.
But the scale has gone overboard.
He thought he
could persuade them.
But the reality was…
We have all the data, sir.
Look here.
So didn't Mr. Choi proceed with this
business with strong conviction
without consideration of
the company's profits?
Did any of the executives
not have conviction?
Then I'll rephrase that.
You said connections are
a custom in that society.
Then do you think this
big scale is the norm?
It can be out of the norm
depending on your viewpoint.
Did you say "viewpoint?"
Are you saying it could
be viewed as the norm?
The trading business has many risks.
The connections, uncertainty,
and losses are all analyzed.
And for potential relations
as a business partner…
Partner management could
be the core to work.
They say it has changed,
but China is still all
about connections.
It works despite the
negative views on it.
Those you leave at some point
are no good.
Mr. Oh Sang Sik?
And for potential relations
as a business partner,
connections have been
made by investments.
I think the scale can be determined by
the potential profit we can acquire.
Then how come there
are no connections
to be found in your past work?
Didn't you judge connections
aren't justifiable?
And it seems the request to the China
resident employee for investigation
after Mr. Choi's order
was made, is similar.
The president is here, sir.
Sir.
What brings you here?
You should've called me.
I met with Auditing team
at headquarters.
Mr. Choi, it'll go with
the proper procedure.
Sir, this is normal.
What's the problem with custom?
You're well aware of that.
And you said you trust me…
I was aware of it, but I don't
know if headquarters was too.
Prepare for anything you need to.
He was your choice.
Oh, you guys…
Mr. Jung, good job.
You should get promoted.
Ok.
Go back and work.
Go now.
No, sir.
Let's go.
[Offshore plant EPC case]
[Approval request]
[Oh Sang Sik, Choi Young Hoo]
Mr. Choi!
- I did it!
- What?
I got the deal for the
offshore plant EPC case!
It's the first offshore
plant case in Korea!
We did it!
Yes!
This is great!
We did it!
Come here!
No, Sang Sik, you did it.
Mr. Choi was appointed to
unlisted affiliate, One Global.
By raising issues regarding connections
and effort to improve
the circumstances,
Mr. Oh and Sales Team 3
weren't punished.
Poshin stopped the solar
heat power plant business.
It was in protest to issues about
connections and
Mr. Choi's punishment.
Geu Rae.
Go shred this.
Things were unsettled in the office.
Rumors about connections spread in
Chinese firms we had relations with,
so some teams suffered direct losses.
The reason could be found in Mr. Oh's
inflexible work style and side effects.
As the days went by,
he was blamed for everything.
That strong Mr. Oh seemed to waver too.
And I knew.
That it all started with the careless
words of a certain contract employee.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I'm the one who got Mr. Seok
to find out all the details.
I'm the one who made the
whole company nervous
as well as you who knew nothing.
So I started it and ended it.
Geez, what's with you?
I told you not to be like this!
The one who should be responsible
and take responsibility is
the share and prerogative
of those in that position.
I hate when you do this,
not knowing your place!
I just can't believe it,
it's just "OMG, OMG" as kids say!
It'll be tough.
The scale is different
from Mr. Park's case.
You have one thing
you're good at!
Patience!
Let's hang in there!
We're the tough Sales Team 3!
Look up.
Stand tall.
The bituminous coal contract
went according to your request.
We reviewed other companies…
How can you ask to recheck the shipping
contract right before production?
Don’t you know verbal contracts
have legal validity too?
Isn't the contract regarding the
Chinese firm that even
visited us many times?
That's right, ABD Shipping.
Right, ABD Shipping among
all those companies.
They want to review the whole contract.
This is all because of Sales Team 3.
Mr. Oh asked about the agent regarding
connections through Poshin,
and rumors must've spread to
all the Chinese companies.
Why, that…
Mr. Choi leaving is making
me anxious as it is.
Let's look for another shipping company.
I'll look into it now.
Negotiations are hard when it's urgent,
we can only choose
from Japanese firms.
Their costs are so high.
Man, I'm going to write on the
noticeboard, "Leave, Mr. Oh!"
I'll select a good company.
Young Yi.
I know you're worried about Mr. Oh,
but we're not the only issue here.
All the teams related to
China will be influenced.
We could've continued business with
Poshin since our relations were good.
Don’t you know our team had no choice
with headquarters' auditing and all?
While we're on the subject,
did they have to find out that way?
It was wrapped up with righteous
results and Mr. Choi's punishment,
but was it worth it?
Poshin stopped it as the
issue got out of hand.
Exactly.
A trading man set up the whole
infrastructure and couldn't
persuade the buyer.
Think of the potential loss of $0.5 bil.
How can you influence all
businesses related to China?
Please check the noticeboard.
If you have a conscience,
you'll feel bad.
Are you telling me to
take responsibility?
That's not it.
I'm checking who's at fault
from the company's viewpoint.
I'm telling you its position
regarding customs.
Mr. Oh.
It's not your fault.
Time will solve everything,
stop drinking.
No, keep drinking today. Here.
Mr. Choi fell into his own trap.
No one's at fault.
Times have changed,
so how can he not?
Right?
He hasn't changed,
neither have I.
Shall I make you a boilermaker?
I'll make it for you.
When boilermakers and
Sales Team 3 get together,
that's it, a success.
Mr. Oh said it's a must for sales.
Here.
I'll feed you, Suk Yool.
Drink it, my arms hurt.
There you go.
It's ok.
Here.
Tissue, tissue.
It wasn't intentional, it's good.
It's ok.
Let go, I have to wipe this off.
You don't have to.
Oh, gosh.
I'm home.
Why are you so late?
You drank again?
You know about drinking?
I know better than you.
You need a snack?
You must need one after
drinking so much.
Yeah, ramen!
With some green onion, yeah!
Ramen at midnight?
That's all we have.
Get up and eat this.
Your dad used to cook his
own ramen after drinking.
I'm cooking it for you when
I never cooked it for my honey.
Bon appetit.
Mr. Choi.
Hi there.
It's really cold, isn't it?
Yes.
How are you?
Good.
How about you?
I'm doing better than expected.
I worked for that company for
28 years, and I was shocked when
they had an issue with my ways.
They say an executive is someone
who can see the stars on clouds
when everyone is
looking at the ground.
I thought it was ok to jump above
the ground to get on the clouds.
How many people
could possibly see the
stars with their feet on the ground?
But I learned my lesson.
Nevertheless,
the type of executive the company wants
is a giant who can see the stars
with their feet
on the ground.
When I first met you, Mr. Choi,
I was sure you'd be like that.
- Yeah?
- Yes,
I thought you were amazing.
I wanted to become like you.
Thanks for not bringing up other
issues during the auditing process.
I wanted to tell you that.
Are you talking about the
doubts regarding the rebate?
They weren't doubts.
They're your groundless suspicions.
Yes,
that's why I couldn't bring it up.
It wasn't for your sake.
I just didn't have hard evidence
though I had suspicions.
Just like with Lee Eun Ji.
I'm glad you're still working.
It's hard to see results in
the global service business,
but performance is key.
But things will be tougher for you.
Since you affected China that way,
it won't be easy for you to
work in One International.
Is that so?
I don’t understand.
That's right.
Mr. Choi was right.
We tried to work as usual,
but the company's atmosphere
was still disturbed.
Hi.
Where's Mr. Kim?
He's in a meeting.
Can I see the items' chart for Sudan?
Mr. Kim said he needs to give
approval for everything.
What?
He told us not to show our
data to anyone when he's away.
Give me the data.
Hey, buddy!
Our team worked on it too!
Why can't I see it?
I'm sorry, I'll take care
of it after I tell Mr. Kim.
Let me see the data.
Mr. Kim, it's so hard
to see a simple chart.
What?
You want me to go up there again?
Send it by messenger.
What are you trying to do now?
I get it.
Oh!
Is something wrong?
It's weird.
What's wrong?
About the import from Laos.
The finance manager
has approved it too,
but the chief of the
headquarters hasn't yet.
It was turned down.
This is too much.
Totally.
Dang.
Your team isn't even working
on any businesses now.
Sales Team 3, Oh Sang Sik speaking.
Apparently there has never been so
many complaints from China before.
The Business Team doesn't know
how to take care of it now.
I'm sorry to say this,
but all the businesses you
were involved with before,
and all those related to Sales Team 3
are being rejected.
The losses for other
teams are increasing.
Are you saying we should
take responsibility?
Not necessarily.
Still personal responsibility…
Anyway Chinese companies are saying
they can't work with One International
since connections can be an issue.
So each team had to persuade them
it wasn't the company's position,
but an arbitrary individual opinion.
But things aren't looking good.
So I think we need to make
a gesture that we fired you.
But we couldn’t fire an employee
that wasn’t even punished.
So the company is saying I have
to leave for China to calm down.
That's not true.
No,
you know how they're
treating our team.
I'll have to leave
for our team to survive.
The company will obviously
want the fastest, easiest way.
But that's not the best way.
We can find the right way.
So wait till…
Then what?
What if all dies while waiting?
Mr. Oh.
So you'll hand in your
resignation or something?
Resignation…
Yeah, resignation.
Mr. Oh.
It's ok.
It's not like they can't run without me.
All of us employees are
ready to submit it.
We always dream of
submitting it every night,
and go to work with it in our pockets.
I've been preparing myself mentally.
But…
I'm just worried about that kid.
Go to bed, it's late.
You won't get much sleep
before work tomorrow.
Can I
quit work?
No, you can't.
Right?
Are you quitting or getting fired?
I'm quitting
myself.
Ok.
But you remember
we have three kids, right?
What?
Receive your bonus before you quit.
Fridge.
TV.
Two computers.
What are you doing?
Things to buy before you quit.
You get an employees' discount.
I hate you.
Oh, hi Young Yi!
Mr. Oh.
You're early today.
Yeah, for a change.
You're looking good.
Your team must be treating you well.
Yes, there are no problems.
Yeah, the one who enjoys it wins!
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Good morning.
I was so focused on a bad boss that
I couldn't think about your team.
I'll serve you better, Mr. Oh!
- You…
- Yes.
You should grow out your hair.
- I want to see your bob.
- Yes.
- I miss it.
Baek Ki's hair has no solution.
Let's go.
[Resignation]
I'm not dying.
I'm just leaving the company.
Geu Rae with extra quality
and quantity of effort.
Yes.
Hang in there.
What about you?
I've hung in there enough.
I want to take a break now.
My legs are shaking.
Make sure you win.
Even if you think you won't
make it, fight to the end.
In life,
there are many things you start
even if you know the end.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
I couldn't take
responsibility for you till the end.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for everything.
Mr. Oh.
I thought it through.
I told you we're ready to
submit resignations every day.
Don't do this.
This too will pass.
Take care of Geu Rae.
I'm glad you're still working here.
Hurry up and get promoted.
That way, you can get Geu Rae
and Dong Sik promoted,
and help my team out.
Dang.
I'm just asking you
for a bunch of favors.
Make sure to
get promoted next year.
Take care.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Thank you.
Don't eat sandwiches alone.
You take these.
You know, Geu Rae?
When Mr. Chun first came, his
hair was more rustic than yours.
You know how his hair was?
It was the same.
Maybe it was shorter,
more like a mom.
But weren't I slimmer before?
"Slimmer" my foot.
I was slimmer.
Oh, Mr. Oh.
I heard Mr. Byun was laid off.
Really?
Just kidding.
You want to smell my new cologne?
No, no!
That's why you're still not married.
I wanted to quit after
seeing him get married.
It'll happen someday, I'll hurry up.
My biggest regret
working here
is having this kid on our team.
This kid?
Who?
Not me, right?
What about me?
Let's say it's me.
It's me!
Come here!
I'm going to pee.
- Mr. Chun.
- Yes.
You know how they're like?
I went to the hospital for IV therapy.
The company was in chaos.
It was a mess
for every single guy.
What are you doing?
I didn't have a light for a smoke.
You quit.
Don’t smoke.
It's hard to quit.
I'm not drunk.
I'm fine, so don't follow me!
Yes.
Go!
I said go.
Then I'll get going.
Ok.
Go.
Don't come visiting me just
because you know my address.
Answer.
Yes.
Geu Rae.
What did I say?
Hang in there.
What else?
Win.
Remember that.
Go now.
Geu Rae with extra quality
and quantity of effort.
I'm sorry.
In life,
there are many things you start
I'm sorry.
even if you know the end.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry.
Captivate me.
What?
Persuade me by captivating me.
What can you sell?
You could teach me
since I don't know.
You could give me an opportunity.
You need to be qualified
to get the opportunity.
Get out, jerk!
Our kid got in trouble because
yours dropped a file!
Mailbox or message box…
What's the definition?
Hello, I'm new employee,
Jang Geu Rae.
I'm here, Mr. Oh.
So
why you again?
I thought you had asked for me.
Contracts and approval requests,
it's for the Resource Team!
Don't make them contact us again!
Yes.
Geu Rae.
What are you doing here?
Hello, Mr. Oh.
First Merry Christmas.
- Who are you to say my judgment…!
- You're trying to save me.
You're
trying to make me a full-timer.
Isn't that why
you're working with people
who you normally never would?
Mr. Oh.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Sorry...
I'm so sorry.
[Misaeng]
Just because you can't see the road,
doesn't mean it's not a road.
Anything should be done.
I'm just asking you for a fair
evaluation, not special treatment.
But it's not a solution.
Let's do it.
Geu Rae.
Can I be ambitious again?