Not Yet Alive
Final Episode 20
After Mr. Oh left, our team
became stable as he had wished.
Hi.
You're early.
Hello.
What did Legal team say about
the Malaysia complaint?
They're reviewing it, and fortunately,
it'll be smooth since our fault isn't big.
There will be a meeting
at 3:00 tomorrow.
Ok, good job.
I wonder why Japan isn't replying yet.
- Mr. Hwang, here.
- What?
Do this today.
- Yes, sir.
- Ok.
The remaining people were
making efforts for me.
The more they did, the more
reasons there were for me to leave.
The reason I stay despite that?
Geu Rae.
What did I say?
Hang in there.
What else?
Make sure you
win.
Win.
Remember that.
That's why.
Even if you think you won't
make it, fight to the end.
In life,
there are many things
you start knowing the end.
That's
why.
The day which is the end
is approaching.
Would you all like some coffee?
Alright.
Sounds good.
Ok.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 20 (Final Episode)]
April is the cruelest month, breeding
lilacs out of the dead land, mixing
memory and desire, stirring
dull roots with spring rain.
You feel me, don't you, Geu Rae?
Don't you feel ticklish down
to your bones, Geu Rae?
If you're itchy, go to a sauna.
You're dirty.
Dirty love?
Which teams are going for
the transition meeting?
Wasn't it us, Sales Team 1,
Resource, Steel, and Fabric?
We can stay, right?
Yes.
Transition meetings give
me a sense of d??vu.
D??vu?
Oh, Mr. Ma and Mr. Oh's conflict?
I'll get going.
I need to finish organizing the receipts.
- Go ahead.
- Ok.
The contract due date is approaching
and there's no solution.
Mr. Kim and Mr. Chun are doing their
best, but they can only do so much.
And they can't do anything about it.
But Ms. Sun is doing her best.
I want to do anything I can to help.
Is the Myanmar case bidding complete?
No, sir.
Myanmar is special, so I went
with the original company.
You guys just proceed without approval?
Sir,
this is how we worked up till now.
This is how "we" worked?
And how is that?
You guys have your own way,
so just shut up and go with it?
No, sir, I mean?
Just go with what I say.
Must I explain and
convince you each time?
- Coffee, please.
- Yes.
I've been watching you guys,
so you want to argue
about everything?
Are you taking this seriously?
You know?
Don't explain things to me.
Tell me through the papers.
Make calls brief without explanations.
What's there to repeat over and over
again when files were already given?
- I'm sorry.
Aren't you tired of blabbering
at the end of a day?
Give me the coffee.
Yes, sir.
I'll do my best to find a
proper new employee next time.
I'll find one with good specifications,
so work hard until then.
Get to work.
I asked you for a lot of water.
I asked you for so much
water, it seems too watery.
I'm sorry, I'll get you another cup.
Forget it.
Hey.
What happened to the Chungsol payment?
The items came over ages ago!
You want to be sued?
Many documents are missing
including a quality guarantee.
They said they'd send it.
Then they will!
Even if I input payment in the ERP,
you think they'd take responsibility
for the missing files after that?
If an issue arises because of that,
I'd have to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
You love responsibility, don?t you?
How on earth were you raised at home?
You trust no one and
you're a selfish mess.
Why do you go crazy
over the Chungsol case?
Raised at home, go crazy?
Take care of the payment ASAP, ok?
ASAP!
I can't even look at this dirty one.
[Notice for cooperation with
intern selection]
They should take care
of those who are here.
Our Steel Team will start an additional
business with discarded fridges
and electronics related to
Resource's urban energy business.
I wish file transitions
would be finished soon.
Mr. Yoo and Ms. Ahn will
help as much as they can.
Fiber will take
care of the asbestos.
If Resource gives us
the files on asbestos,
we'll develop a Malaysia
export case through Samgang.
Geez, why does everyone
want Resource's business?
A TF or transition every
time things get exciting.
- Mr. Jung.
- Yes.
How are you doing work?
I'm sorry.
We were on the\M Ghana fast Internet line
installment case with Sales Team 1.
Since we're receiving the payment
through mineral resources,
I'd like Resource to take care of it.
So why receive the payment
through mineral resources?
Bartering is from the Stone Age.
Right, Mr. Jung?
Oh, right.
But apparently large inspection teams
have come for French consultative groups
regarding Ghana resource
development investments.
International projects to secure
Ghana energy develop? lop...
Develop what?
What are you trying to develop?
What?
I think it's a good opportunity
for related businesses, sir.
Yes.
We'll research about the
consumers and demands.
Why should your team do that?
We can do that, right, Mr. Jung?
What?
Then go ahead.
I wish you could do it by tomorrow.
Ms? Ms. Sun.
Alright.
I have another meeting to go
into, so let's end it here.
Wrap up individually too.
Yes, it's true that there's a
price drop in raw materials as
with the end of the super cycle.
But the market of Canadian chromium,
nickel, and platinum is still large.
You can read from the
data that there will be
a variety of synergy effects
among this consortium.
So the schedule will be?
I'm sorry, I'll send you the detailed
schedule by email as soon as possible.
Ok, thank you.
[2 years since starting work]
Why couldn't I even say "development?"
- Is it over?
- Yeah.
This is pitiful.
Ever since Mr. Jung attacked him,
Mr. Ma doesn't care about us.
What if we end up sitting
next to the restroom?
Be quiet, let's just hope we don't.
I hope our luck gets better.
When will that happen?
The day you retire?
Mr. Yoo, you still
haven't gone to London?
I wish dept. heads were
contract employees.
Young Yi.
Geu Rae is leaving soon, right?
Yes.
Mr. Kim will suffer the most
after he does.
Yeah, you have to train
interns and newbies.
That's if Geu Rae's successor comes.
Right, their team rarely had newbies.
But he really can't sign
another contract, right?
Why would the company sign
him on as a full-timer?
Ms. Sun and the team seemed
to be making efforts.
But it won't produce any results.
I'm sure they know too.
I thought I'd just have to do my
share despite who became my partner,
but I preferred someone
I could communicate with.
I just wanted to tell you.
I didn't have the ulterior
motives you're thinking of.
I'm sorry.
No, apologize after getting the job.
Young Yi.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's sad, isn't it?
The four of you started work together.
Is there really no solution?
That's all I think about these days.
There isn't.
Maybe you can start a movement.
Movement?
The more the better, you know.
The company can reconsider
it if many people think about.
Though it's not a solution.
Start a movement?
Mr. Ha meant we should try to make
the company understand Geu Rae.
That he's worth keeping
and he has to stay.
How?
Yeah, we can't have
a presentation for him,
or put up posters like in college.
We can't go to upper management
like in the dramas.
Why not?
We can go, talk, convince,
and cry out loud.
This is like the last resort.
They ruin someone's
life instantaneously.
Why's it so hard
to see the real of a person?
Where are you going?
I have to do something.
I'll try the method that
made me fool once.
I'll get going.
I think there's something I can do.
What?
Hi, Young Yi.
Ms. Sun,
I have a favor.
I'm Fabric Team 1, Han Suk Yool.
It's been nearly two years since
I've started working here.
I had contacted you before
because of an unpleasant issue.
I'd like to apologize first.
The reason I'm apologizing first
is so people won't close the window
just by the mention of my name.
I'd like to ask an
important favor today.
Two year contract employee Jang Geu Rae
has started work with me
and he's working in Sales Team 3.
I hope he can become a full-timer.
You can't ignore
Jang Geu Rae's performance.
Well, I know.
The interns were always
complaining he started through
connections and special treatment.
That's not necessarily true.
We'd like a fair evaluation,
not special treatment.
He passed the presentation
interview with me two years ago.
He joined Sales Team 3.
He was the first of us to be in a
presentation with upper management.
That radical presentation brought the
Jordan used car business to success.
We owe it to Jang Geu Rae.
Connections.
Yes, people called him the GED
Jang Geu Rae who used
his connections to get the job.
So when we all entered as a full-timer,
he joined as a two year
contract employee.
He had to suffer various
insults since his intern days.
But he worked harder
than anyone else
thinking of One International
as our company.
Is that for Geu Rae?
Yes.
I'm hoping it would help.
I'll make files proving his
performance for our team.
Yeah, such portfolios are necessary
for full-timer transition evaluations.
I'll take a look when you're done.
Yes, sir.
He'd come to work with us,
and leave after we do.
He worked so hard to make up
for his lacking experiences.
When the item he planned
he was excluded
because he was a contract employee,
he gave up on it without
a complaint.
Please change it.
I've
never been so embarrassed
of my specifications before.
I feel that way too.
How can specifications
make someone's
treatment so different from another?
Why should one's effort be
treated differently from others?
That must be reflected in regulations,
but transition to
a full-timer is impossible.
Yes, you're right.
But I'm just asking you that
he won't be evaluated unfairly
in a standard evaluation
due to Mr. Choi's incident.
Please, sir.
The basics are key to evaluate
one's adaptability to work life.
Though it was hard to prove
his basics at the starting point,
he has shown enough potential
during the last two years.
Jang Geu Rae must become a full-timer.
He said,
"I'll sell this fabric with you,
Suk Yool."
Please help me keep that promise.
I've had my shameful moments,
but I'd like to keep that promise.
Please.
Please check the payment regarding
the Malaysia contact lenses.
Yes, the proposal review is complete,
it's doubled because of the stock.
I'd appreciate a prompt reply.
Each team can send one employee for
college graduate intern selections.
Wow, new interns after two years.
Yeah.
It's like Geu Rae came yesterday.
Nice to have a successor, isn't it?
Show them as the senior.
Go.
Yes, I'll be back.
- I'll be back.
- Go.
Let's have a talk.
What kind of possibility?
Headquarters will send guidelines
to the company soon.
Competent contract employees will be
transitioned to full-time positions.
It's an opinion among
upper management,
so we will go by those
guidelines too.
Trends are changing.
Please help out, Mr. Chun and Mr. Kim.
I'll do my best too.
First of all, make a file of all
of Geu Rae's performance results.
Yes, sure.
Yes!
Hey, hey!
Let's do it, Geu Rae.
Can I
be ambitious again?
I'm back.
You're so late!
Sorry, sorry, ma'am.
You have a bunch of
deliveries waiting!
The door will have to be
fixed to shut tightly.
You drive me crazy.
Welcome.
I'll have a rice roll.
Sure.
We'll have two ramens
and one rice roll.
Sure.
Hey, how's your intern?
Geez, you know that
the college graduate
did not knowing
how to make copies?
He came to you?
Ha, he called his mom to ask her
in front of the copy machine.
Geez.
Gosh.
Unbelievable.
So I don't know how to do it.
You could teach me since I don't know.
You could give me an opportunity.
Thank you, I'm starving.
Thank you, so hungry.
[Kim Dong Sik]
Sorry, I missed your kid's
birthday because of a business trip.
[Sun Ji Young]
Hi, Ms. Sun.
Mr. Oh.
Long time no see, how are you?
Don't worry.
I feed myself.
I'll settle things here,
so come if you get fired.
Trust me.
I'll set a red carpet, so if
you can't deal with it anymore,
just tell Mr. Ma
you'll quit and come.
Why Mr. Ma when he's
not even our boss?
Yeah?
About Geu Rae.
He passed HR's evaluation today
and it was brought up in
the Admin. Team's meeting.
We just need the participants'
majority vote.
Looks like Geu Rae's
transition will be
smooth from the various
circumstances.
Ok.
That's great.
Thanks.
Keep working hard.
When will the results be in?
Tomorrow.
Ok.
Thanks.
Bye.
Not yet?
No.
I think it'll go smoothly since
Ms. Sun is in the meeting.
I overheard Mr. Ma and Mr. Jung talking.
It seemed positive since
it was an upper discussion.
Plus, Geu Rae's performance was
great with lots of referrals.
Hello.
What's keeping you so busy all day?
I have to submit some things by 5:00.
Let's have lunch together.
I won't be able to make it as I'll need
to have a quick lunch while I work.
Ok.
Geu Rae.
You're in charge of the Shenzhen
export case for China, right?
I heard there was a request
for additional supplies.
Yes.
Shouldn't our team work
on a Chinese item too?
Yeah.
We don't have to worry
about your team, do we?
You'll have to.
I don't want to.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
Have a good day.
Hello.
Geu Rae, I put the file about
recycling fridges on your desk.
It's about copper, aluminum,
and plastic excluding steel,
so it'll be easy to understand.
Thank you.
Oh, and can I see last quarter's TF
team business report this evening?
Yes, I gave it to Baek Ki
in the morning.
Thanks.
Geu Rae, let's have a drink someday.
Yes, thank you.
Where are the Malaysia files?
Ms. Sun is coming.
What is this?
I sent it since there's a new system.
I'm frigging sorry.
I work as a trading man
for this moment.
Congratulations.
Pay me some respect!
Speak for yourself!
Everyone's saying what they want,
why can't you say anything?
I'd like to get to know
you better, Geu Rae.
You're here,
so hang in there.
Surviving is winning here.
Surviving means going towards
a complete life somehow.
We all have incomplete lives yet.
Ok, the contract is here!
You know the chicken
place owner nagged
me for a month after
the helmet test?
When they're looking for a Korean
product that will beat Japanese ones,
you can't discuss Vietnamese
buyers without being stood up yourself.
They want the strongest,
lightest item with
the best ventilation system
and air resistance.
Oh, yes, you're the export king
and we got the deal thanks to you.
And the Vietnam helmet export
has the best profits.
Moon Choong Gi  is here.
What did you say?
Meccaphone!
Take a look.
I can't do it!
Hey.
Are you disregarding me since
I am a salary CEO?
You guys invited me as a professional
executive, so you should listen.
What?
You're acting all arrogant because
you invested half of the company?
My life was so easy getting off
at six sharp at One Aluminum.
Nice.
It's a good item.
So?
Nice, isn't it?
It's a good item.
It's good.
Let's work together.
Let's do it.
But let's have another CEO.
Neither me nor you.
What?
Let's bring Kim Boo Ryun over.
Kim Boo Ryun?
That cold guy?
He's such an aggressive perfectionist.
If you don't agree,
I won't do it.
Getting off on time is most
important for employees.
I know you worked late every day.
And come on, half?
I invested 51% and Kim 49%!
This company should be run 51-49!
So 51!
Do mecca phone when I ask nicely.
Gosh, that Moon Choong Gi!
Geez.
Mr. Kim, go in and talk with the CEO.
[Milk day]
The milk is almost ready.
Time to drink it.
I'll go to Youngjin.
See you later.
Hello?
My kiddo!
Dad, buy me fried chicken!
Spicy half, fried half!
Give it to me.
Clean up.
Your company changed, but why
do you get off at the same hour?
You said you'd reflect on your
life at your new company.
You said you'd talk
a lot with the kids.
You said we'd see the Jejudo beach,
and we never went there.
"Camping" my foot.
You said you'd fix the curtains,
but you've been busy for four days!
So?
What time will you come?
I'll be late after
visiting three clients.
Ok, I'll eat.
Ok.
Bye.
I heard the San Paolo items arrived.
Oh, I was wrong.
Go pick them up at the airport.
I was working near there.
It would've been perfect
to go after lunch.
But you said it already arrived.
I ran over skipping lunch.
You did?
I didn't know that.
You should've told me.
Still here?
Suk Yool.
You can't take a leave.
There will be a security
educating session.
Educating?
I checked.
It just came up.
Put off your leave.
Did you set it for
tomorrow on purpose?
I told you and got approval too,
it's my dad's birthday and fa?!
Family trip.
How can I put off my dad's birthday?
Why'd you take
a leave like that, fool?
Are you yelling at me now?
Put off your leave if I tell you to!
Should we put off Mr. Jung's
business trip again?
Hello?
Hi, how are you?
I'm free.
Let's have a drink.
Ok.
Bye.
Sung Joon Sik in Fabric Team 1 is
having an inappropriate relationship
with Chungsol's Mrs. Lee Gyung Sun,
bringing huge losses to our business,
so please look into this.
[Suggestions]
Dang.
Mom, sorry I can't go.
I was busy with work.
Of course, I earn all
the money in Seoul.
Mm-hmm.
I know dad is disappointed.
Let me talk to him for a minute.
What?
He won't take the phone?
Have a good time at
the warm country.
I'll make sure to go next year.
Yes.
Bye.
Man, oh, man.
You should've just received a bribe.
Then it'd be easy for
me to tell on you.
You call that a life?
Excuse me.
Is there Sung Joon Sik here?
Right there.
In white?
Thank you.
Are you Mr. Sung Joon Sik?
Yes.
Are you Mr. Sung?
Hey.
You're Sung Joon Sik?
Sung Joon Sik?
Who do you think you are?
You know Lee Gyung Sun, right?
From Chungsol?
Yeah, from Chungsol's Fabric Team.
She's our client, what about her?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Who do you think I am?
Who do you think?
Hey, what did you do with my wife?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I knew you'd deny it,
so I took all these shots.
Look.
Is this you kissing her or not?
You still don't know?
- I think it's me?
- Look!
"I think it's me?"
Hey, you jerk!
Sorry.
Come here, man!
- Suk Yool.
- You're running away?
Come here, man!
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry.
- Now you're sorry?
Now you're sorry?
Please calm down,
you can't do this here.
How far did you go?
What did you do and
how far did you go?
Don't tell me!
Come here, man!
Come here, jerk!
I'm sorry.
Hey, come here!
Come here.
I'm sorry.
What did she give to you?
Give it to me now!
This watch.
Shoes.
Wait, my socks.
Tie.
Not those!
Are you joking now?
Car keys.
Here, car keys.
But this is mine!
Hey, man!
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey!
Please, you can't do this here?
Ajusshi, has your wife
had an affair before?
[Ahjusshi: middle-aged man]
- Not yet.
- Right?
Then you don't know how I feel.
Come here.
Why do you live like this?
I told you to bring
a wet tissue, not this.
Baek Ki.
Yes.
You achieved 150% of the
expected quarter performance.
Yes.
You'll catch up to Mr. Kang soon.
No, sir.
You better be on your toes.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And I printed out
the email for Germany.
You hadn't revised
the word I checked.
Sir,
that "Z" should be capitalized.
Since honorifics are needed here.
Yeah?
Yes.
And Mr. Kang.
There's something I didn't
tell you last time.
When you pronounce the
"w" sound in German,
you told me to make it
sound like I'm gagging
after putting my toothbrush
too deep in.
Yes.
Actually,
it should sound like you're popping
out condensed air from your mouth,
not your nose like this?
That's how you say it.
So?
Is that so?
That's what my German
academy taught me.
Which academy did you go to?
Wa Germany Academy.
My classmate teaches there.
I can't make it to lunch. - Suk Yool.
You really can't eat it?
Uh?
You've seen enough scary movies,
let's bring it up a notch.
I'll eat it if you can't.
You said you wouldn't be
able to eat due to work.
I was so hungry, I grew
supernatural powers.
Is Mr. Sung ok?
His whole face is a mess
and he's so embarrassed.
I wonder if he can
continue coming to work.
It's ok, he's a psychopath.
But
when did you two watch a movie?
I love movies too.
You shouldn't discriminate people.
- You like scary movies too?
- Are you crazy?
Why watch those when you have
so many good flicks out there?
I miss Geu Rae.
Three out of four of us just
isn't symmetrical.
What is this?
If the subject is an item,
use the active voice.
If the subject is a person,
use the passive voice.
For example, this class is interesting.
This class is interesting.
Mr. Park opened a restaurant,
and he's looking for
a manager or whatever.
Are you interested?
No, tell him thanks, but no thanks.
You have other options?
I'll have to make my options,
study more too.
Has your Chinese improved?
Let me hear your Chinese.
Ni hao.
[Ni: derogatory term
for "you" in Korean]
How could you talk
like that to your mom?
Forget it.
I can't teach you anything
since you don't know.
Young Yi.
Hi.
It's been three weeks.
Yes.
It feels like three years since we
used to see each other every day.
You left just like that
without a farewell party.
You might've left like
that to start anew,
but we all felt a bit guilty.
Come on.
After you left, Suk Yool is
so disheartened,
he doesn't even come downstairs.
We have new interns now.
But no one makes
an impression like you.
What?
Oh, they're here.
Long time no see, Geu Rae.
Hi.
Geu Rae.
I wish the love were 9-to-6.
What the? wait.
What, what?
Here.
Thanks.
- What about me?
- Me?
I'm jobless.
Glad to be here.
I want to get off from the company
called your heart,
but I keep working late.
Then don't ever go home?
Stop it.
I'm sure Geu Rae
doesn't feel like that.
Will you stop it?
Tell me, Geu Rae.
What am I to you?
Am I of any importance to you?
- Stop it now.
- Stop it.
That wasn't funny?
Mr. Oh didn't ask you to come?
He could feel sorry about inviting
him to an unsettled company.
That's true.
He could be thinking an adventure
for himself is enough.
Why don't you give him a call?
What?
Yeah, just call to say hi.
Geu Rae.
You can't just join and leave
a company as you wish.
Like I can't control the
love I have for you.
Stop it!
Suk Yool, eat this.
Stop it.
Growing apart
When I thought youth
would stay forever
The seasons will return again
You can't help but
sing thinking of how
you can play while everyone works?
Mr. Oh.
What brings you here?
- Are you done getting settled?
- What?
It's been three weeks already.
The milk is ready.
The suit, dress shirt,
and tie are ready.
Suitcase too.
Shoes too.
You can come anytime.
Yes.
So the TS has to be complete for us too.
It's because of the complaint, so you
can't say it's been discarded already.
Who would believe that?
Exactly.
Sales Team 3 intern,
Kim Geun Young speaking.
Yes.
Hello?
Dong Sik, has the Philippines
payment been made yet?
Will you hurry with that?
They keep calling us.
- Geez.
- Yes, sir.
Sales Team 3, Kim Dong Sik speaking.
Sir.
A meeting tomorrow?
Please hold on.
Yes.
Yes, I made reservations
for 5:00 at Hwaryun.
Yes, sir.
Time goes by slow these days.
It used to fly.
It's no fun.
You still look for fun from work?
I know.
Drink it.
What?
Alright.
I wonder why
I feel lonely.
It's weird.
It was like this at
One International too.
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Hi.
Hello, sir.
It's ready on your desk.
Thanks.
Did you send the Uzbekistan invoice
packing list, bill and all?
I did a couple hours ago.
Mr. Oh.
Yeah?
I always had this question.
What?
I'm busy, hurry up.
Why do you always put your
family photo faced down?
What?
It's noisy, you haven't
heard my wife nag before.
Once in a while it's fine.
If it continues, it sounds
like a barking dog.
Do you even know what I mean?
What happened to the
experienced employee case?
The hits are increasing, but
I haven't gotten any replies.
Oh, yeah, what about
using the new material?
I heard the restrictions have been
lifted, and it can be sponsored.
Yeah?
- I'll look into it.
- Mm-hmm.
I wasn't going to fling the door open.
That's my seat.
The Trade Association
should be calling.
What should I do now?
Oh, Mr. Kim!
CEO Kim.
Hello.
Hi.
I looked around the whole building.
The rooftop needs work.
Geu Rae.
Take the recruitment ad down.
Work is no fun for me now.
Take it down.
What are you doing?
We have procedures too!
We recruit properly!
Procedures?
You told us to be radical.
He got in through connections too.
Come on.
You let Geu Rae be radical and I can't?
Really?
Do it!
- No.
- Do it... please!
No, where are you going?
Don?t go, come here!
Glad you're here!
Get back to work!
Suh Jin Sang?
He took cell phone case samples
from the China factory and ran off.
What are you talking about?
You mean the metal cases
we signed the contract for?
Yes.
- Where is he, can they find him?
- Can you find out where he is?
What this time?
We're searching now.
The China resident employee has
gone to the Immigration Office.
I don't think it'll be hard to find him.
Ok, let me know ASAP.
I'm dumbfounded.
I can't believe he did this!
- This can ruin the contract.
- What should we do?
How many contracts does
One International have?
Three, sir.
- What about us?
- Two, and one is under progress.
Yes.
With One International, it has to do
with the buyer's credit and manpower,
it's a life-or-death issue for us.
I'll kill Jin Sang.
- Yeah.
- He ran off to Jordan.
Jordan?
Ok, we'll take off right away too.
You can't delay the Vietnam
case, right?
If we can't go tomorrow, the
contract might be annulled.
Then Geu Rae will have to go.
- Get a visa and a plane ticket.
- Yes, sir.
Call Mr. Cho too.
Okay.
This is from Incheon to Abu Dabi.
This is from Abu Dabi to Amman.
Here's your passport and luggage ticket.
- Thank you.
- Have a good time.
Hello, sir.
I finished ticketing and will go in.
You know you need to
transfer planes, right?
- Make sure you do that.
- Yes, I know.
Mr. Cho will be at Amman.
You know his number, right?
Yes, I know.
Ok, don't just eat anything.
Sir.
What?
I'm not a kid.
Ok.
Bye, sir.
Geu Rae.
Hello, sir.
You must be tired now.
I'm fine.
Where is Jin Sang now?
We know he's in Amman.
He's not in any of the
hotels or guest houses.
I wonder where he is.
Any acquaintances?
He doesn't have any here.
Have you been to Jordan?
In the alleys,
there's a nice, cheap hotel.
It only costs $10 a day.
Have you checked hotels
in the old districts?
- Hotels in the old districts?
- Yes.
There can't be any hotels there.
There are two or three,
but I don't think so.
It's very old?
Yes.
- Old?
- And cheap.
Yes.
You can stay there for $10 a night.
I don?t think he would stay there.
No, please look into it.
Yes, sir.
But where's Mr. Oh?
Hi.
Where are you?
I'm looking at the land.
Land?
Come on.
You know why the Russian mafia
has tattoos on their knees?
What?
It means they'll never kneel down.
They never give up.
You should do whatever you can.
I see.
But that's too?
We always need a plan B.
This will determine our business'
success, so be alert.
I heard building one doesn't take long.
This call is costing a lot, bye.
Hello?
See you three hours later in Petra.
What?
Why Petra?
Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both
And be one traveler, long I stood
And looked down one as far as I could
To where it bent in the undergrowth;
Then took the other, as just as fair,
And having perhaps the better claim,
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;
Though as for that the passing there
Had worn them really about the same,
And both that morning equally
leaves no step had trodden black.
Oh, I kept the first for another day!
Yet knowing how way leads on to way,
I doubted if I should ever come back.
I shall be telling this with a sigh
Somewhere ages and ages hence:
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I?
I took the one less traveled by,
And that has made all the difference.
Alcatraz.
Pharaoh's treasure.
The gateway to Petra.
It's a path you have to pass by.
It was the central trade route
in the ancient times connecting
the Persian Bay to the
east, Red Sea to the south,
and Mediterranean to the west.
Incense road?
Come to think of it,
my dream as an 18-year-old
was to travel around the world.
As I watched Indiana Jones 3,
I became determined.
Indiana Jones 3?
Mm-hmm.
I had forgotten about it.
But Jordan reminded me
of my dream.
Dream?
As commerce decreased,
Petra was forgotten for
over 1,000 years.
I see.
So, I was thinking.
Just because you forgot your dream
doesn't make your dream vanish.
Just because you can't see the
road doesn't make the road vanish.
Lu Xun said this.
?Hope can't be said it exists,
nor can it be said it's not exist.
It is just like roads across the earth.
For actually the earth had
no roads to begin with,
but when many men pass one
way, a road is made.?
I see.
Uh, Mr. Oh.
Yeah?
Why did you want to meet here?
I just told you.
What?
When?
Just now.
What?
I just told you.
I should've brought Young Yi.
She would've gotten it right away.
Do you mean
you want me to catch Jin Sang?
Geu Rae.
Did you find him?
It's the Cairo Hotel.
I'll see you in front of there.
Geu Rae!
Hi.
Maybe he already checked out.
Hello?
Has the man who stayed in this
room already checked out?
His name is Mr. Suh.
Mr. Suh Jin Sang.
Mr. Suh Jin Sang!
Geu Rae!
I can't believe this.
My, my neck.
My ribs.
I think I'm dying.
Where are the items?
Wha, what are you talking about?
The samples you took
from the China factory.
What did I ta, take?
Mr. Suh.
If you just give back the items,
we'll end it by firing you.
- What?
- If you don't, we'll take legal actions.
I mean you'll end up in jail.
What do you me, mean?
Are you crazy?
Come on, must I go
to jail on this trip?
It's not in the room.
You jerk!
Let go, it hurts, I'll kill you guys.
I'll call the embassy
about this diplomatic issue.
You have proof?
We have no choice.
Where are we?
Wadi Rum.
What?
Wadi Rum?
Thank you.
It's cold out there.
Let me repeat myself.
If you just give back the items,
we'll end it by firing you.
I really don?t know.
Come on, and Geu Rae, who
are you to threaten me?
Do I work for your company?
Am I Korean?
Geez.
Mr. Oh.
We caught him, but he won't tell us.
We don't have a choice
either without evidence.
- Geu Rae.
- What?
Russia
mafia's knee tattoo?
Come on.
Ok.
I swear I didn?t take the samples.
They're looking for you
in Basilisk, Russia too.
Mr. Cho, what's the share of
the Russian mafia for Basilisk?
What?
Mr. Oh said it's about 70%.
Isn't that absurd?
Right, I heard they'd been
sponsoring for a few years.
Already 70%?
Then that's a mafia's company.
Mr. Suh.
Mr. Oh told me to tell you something.
What's that?
In Russia, the fist is more
influential than the law.
Why would he say that to me?
Let's wrap up.
The fist is more
influential than the law.
Just tell me where it is.
Then there won't be any problems.
Geu Rae, Amman Airport.
In a locker at Amman Airport.
No. 20, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry,
please let me go.
Geu Rae, you're a true
One International employee.
Who did you call a One
International employee?
Why is he a One International employee?
It's just an analogy.
He worked so hard so that One
International wouldn't suffer a loss.
You mean our company,
not One International!
That's the same thing.
One International's loss is
your loss, and your loss?
Be quiet!
Don't you know our motto?
You can steal our business,
but not our people.
I heard it's your bad luck.
Dong Sik?
You're bad.
I'm not bad.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Why didn't you say anything when he
called you a One International employee?
What?
You still miss it?
No.
Before, you said you only needed
some insurance and gosh?
Now that a year has gone by,
you want more pay and benefits, right?
I know, please increase my pay.
What?
You really miss One International?
I don?t know.
Why, you?
Captivate me, sir.
What?
Just captivate me.
What do you have that you can sell?
My effort.
I've never used my effort,
so it's like brand new.
Brand new?
I'll work hard.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Drive, man.
I had an accident, don't hit me.
A road opens
as you tread along it.
A road that doesn't
open isn't a road.
Roads are open to everyone.
But not everyone
can have the roads.
This isn't the army for
you to get proficiency pay.
You told me to catch me.
I risked my life and caught him.
This is wrong.
Another road has opened.
And I'm not alone.
[Misaeng]
[Kim Eun Ji]
[Thank you for watching "Misaeng"]