Not Yet Alive
It was always like that.
Even on the way to the
go-academy in the crack of dawn.
Even when I came home after
my late night part-time job.
There were people outside
no matter what time I start my day.
I thought people would
still be sleeping.
But as always…
…the world is faster than me.
The documents are ready, sir.
See you later, sir.
Hi, Geu Rae.
I'm going back to the site.
-Geu Rae…
-Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Be partners.
Why did you change your mind?
No, I haven't.
I just delayed my decision.
I'll ask you this time.
Why me?
I think your experience on
the field will help our presentation.
Geu Rae.
What do you think the life is?
You think it's a big question?
It's simple.
A collection of your
choices is your life.
The choices you make
in each moment…
…makes up the quality of your life.
Five minutes have passed since
we came up this rooftop.
Don't forget.
These five minutes…
…here on the rooftop….
…were the…
…best life-changing
five minutes for you.
That dog?
That obnoxious dog?
That arrogant dog?
The dog with the bob?
Yeah.
I understand that's his nickname.
But why is Suk Yool called that?
Yeah.
Because he is a dog.
He comes an hour earlier
to work to look at girls.
The two of bomb will
make nuclear bomb.
Let's see who explodes first.
I can't wait.
[Misaeng]
We'll have to choose an item first.
I'll leave it all to you.
Just share the progress through email.
You want me to decide
on the item by myself?
Of course we'll need
democratic consultation.
I'll do my share too.
Geu Rae.
I could tell right away.
You have discernment.
You can do whatever you
want with the presentation.
So can you stand out.
Let's do it.
I trust your discernment.
Did you decide on your partner?
It's due today.
Not yet.
Not yet?
[Geu R…]
There won't be many people left.
I heard Geu Rae will be
partners with Suk Yool.
Huh?
Young Yi!
Hi!
Let's submit it.
-But…
-Whatever, we're the only ones left.
Sang Hyun…
What did I say?
No one will do it with you.
Only I could handle you.
Submit it, ok?
By the way Young Yi.
Yes.
Keep your chin up.
Hello.
You came early.
-Dong Sik.
-Yes.
They said they'd send the
Vietnamese container data.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
You were so full of
energy yesterday.
"Do it for me, do it, let's do it!"
Anyways, what is this?
What's this?
I sent it since we have
a new system and all.
See you later.
Hello.
I'm Geu Rae.
I had the intestine for the first
time thanks to you, Mr. Oh.
I never eat mutton since
I don't like meat.
But as I ate mutton intestines
for the first time yesterday…
…I felt the beginning of camaraderie.
Our kid got in trouble…
I was also able to learn
Mr. Oh's true feelings.
What's he saying?
Mutton intestines?
I'll do you proud as a team…
[Delete]
What a crazy start of the day.
But he came too?
You don't remember?
I remember eating it
for the second round.
Why'd he go?
Well then...
...do you remember meeting Mr. Ko?
What?
I met Mr. Ko?
You don't remember
fighting about glue?
I'm no kid to be playing with glue.
Geez, you were sulky like a child...
...because he had great results.
Hey, cut the nonsense.
Follow me.
Let's go for a smoke.
It's a good morning.
Good morning.
[Korean fine fiber duster sales]
Didn't the executive
director reject this?
I'll change the conditions.
But he told you not to do it last time.
So I'll do it again
changing the conditions.
Mr. Oh…
He rejected it once.
Also, it costs a lot.
That's why I want to do it.
Would I do it if it didn't?
Yes.
You're sharp.
At the start of the day...
...why does he mess up my hair?
You could teach me.
Give me a chance.
You need to be
qualified for chances.
What do you mean?
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
-If you're done, call a dispatch rider.
-Sure.
Get out, punk!
You get it now?
Why you don't get a chance?
Why you're not qualified?
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
There are documents in
the cabinet from 3 years ago.
Find the complaints regarding
the Osung's fertilizer case.
Also find that year's...
...MOU and contracts too.
Osung…
Contract…
What are you doing?
What else?
Trying to interpret that.
Trade dictionary?
Even if I'm fast,
you should catch it.
I don't have high hopes.
So at least act like you're trying...
...to understand me while you're here.
You're driving me nuts.
Don't ask me again.
Call the guy now.
Osung…
Again, I'll leave it all to you.
You can do whatever you want.
Why?
I told you I already got in, haha.
Hello.
I heard you're partners with Suk Yool.
Yes.
Then I guess I was rejected.
Young Yi!
Let's not worry too
much about the item.
And just receive something
from my club seniors.
-Club seniors?
-Mm-hmm.
Let's go to the lounge.
Mr. Lee.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm just so close with
my female juniors.
Aren't you overreacting?
As if I sexually assaulted
you or something.
Mr. Lee.
I was told to be careful
of women when working.
You can become so scary.
Come to the lounge.
How to choose the resources?
Mm-hmm.
My senior works in Ulsan.
He got hired with this item.
They won't know it.
-We can tweak it a bit…
-Mr. Lee.
I have other seniors too.
So there are lots of material.
You don't have much to do at all.
No.
I like not having much to do.
But not old stuff.
It's no good.
Geez.
Why go through all the trouble?
You're so uptight.
Geez.
What's wrong?
Not feeling well?
No.
Sit down and relax.
You were busy running
about today.
I'm good.
Come on.
It's your boss's order, not mine.
I met him at the 1st floor café.
He wants to make up for working
you like a dog with a $4 coffee.
They'll tell us the 2nd presentation
assignment the day before.
It'll be tough if we have lots of work.
I wonder how Geu Rae's doing.
I get Suk Yool.
I don't understand
why Geu Rae chose him.
When he had so many choices.
So many choices?
Didn't you know?
They must've thought he'd
help them stand out.
They wanted to use Geu Rae.
I must've thought that too.
7.6%...
-The copies.
-Hand them out.
-Sure.
-The overseas market is 2.9%.
Geu Rae.
Work harder.
Let's do it.
Young Yi.
See you tomorrow.
What's a container crane?
Container handling gantry
crane or ship-to-shore…
Telegraphic transfer?
Exchange rate when electronic
means of transferring funds overseas.
We just need to make
the orders to Ulsan.
I'm surprised the manager approved it.
I wonder if the executive
director said anything.
Make sure not to make any mistakes.
So they can't pick on you.
There won't any problems
since we've been on this.
We're just tight on time.
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
Check the Vietnamese case info.
The loading, discharging
rates and DF…
That won't be in the dictionary.
-We use that term here.
-I know.
Aren't you talking about
dispatch fees?
The fee that ships pay for putting it there
when they can't load and unload.
Can I check after
I make these copies?
Huh?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Did you tell him?
No.
Maybe he's a genius.
He memorized
the dictionary in 3 days.
Look at him prepare the
presentation item too.
Oh, my gosh.
Although he might not
know what he's doing.
Yeah, that's important.
I wonder if he knows
what he's doing.
Mr. Oh.
Do you honestly want
him to make it or not?
Want my honest opinion?
Why get so serious?
I honestly want him to fail.
Huh?
Again…
What is it this time?
It's not sexy.
Do it again with something
else that's sexy.
Geez.
Hi, Geu Rae.
Why this time?
Didn't you get my text?
Are you kidding me?
You don’t get me.
Things have changed.
"Sexy" doesn't only
refer to sexual appeal.
Something…
…with an edge.
You probably don’t get that either.
Good partners would get
each other right away.
You're inflexible and conservative,
aren't you?
You must not be able to adjust
to fast changing trend quickly.
That's not the issue.
It's not?
Then what's the problem?
That?
Geu Rae.
That's no good for the item.
I've won many awards…
Didn't you say I could
do whatever I want?
I asked you to share it.
I said I'd do my share.
So I have to do
whatever you ask me?
Geu Rae.
I know what I'm doing.
Also, I'm what the company needs.
Who do you think
should listen to who?
I'm not saying I'm
better than you.
I'm giving you good advice.
Then…
…what kind of item should it be?
You find it.
Something you're good at.
And something sexy.
I'm in Seoul for work.
Shall I go in?
No, it's ok.
Ok, call me when you're ready.
Unsexy = Tooooo plain.
Why, that…
That bomb exploded first.
Hello.
Hi.
How are things going?
Not so smooth.
Yes, right.
Sorry I'm late.
Hi.
Our material overlaps.
Let's talk outside.
Come on.
Hello.
You're really quitting?
You've worked so hard.
Try one more time.
You always make it happen.
Yeah, man.
Even we made it too.
You were better than us.
You sure you won't regret it?
What's all that mess for?
He didn't even sleep
over the weekend.
That's the only place
for veggie wraps.
It's gross.
They're good for you though.
He's sleeping.
-Should I wake him up?
-Nope.
He has tons of presentation
items on his desk.
He's preparing alone?
Who's his partner?
The guy in Ulsan, Suk Yool.
The slacker?
You know how he is.
Looks like Geu Rae is
doing all of the work.
So the slacker and
clueless guy met.
True.
My experiences…
Lee Se Dol.
Lee Chang Ho.
Yu Chang Hyuk.
Cho Hoon Hyun.
Cho Chi Hoon.
Kim In.
Cho Nam Chul.
Segoe Kensaku.
All my heroes are vanishing.
Don't go.
I'll do well.
It ended ages ago.
Yet, I still have the same dream.
I'm a fool.
[Unread]
Geez.
Hi, Geu Rae.
Didn't you get my
text about the item?
I did, but I was too
busy to read it.
Check it even if you're busy.
We need to hurry
and decide on the item.
Ok, ok.
Nagging me nonstop…
I'm sorry!
Sorry.
Call from the headquarters.
Never mind.
Just enjoy the party!
Don't go.
[Sang Hyun]
Hi, Sang Hyun.
Young Yi.
I have to go meet my club senior.
Let's postpone our evening
meeting to tomorrow.
-Uh…
-I'll bring a lot of materials.
Uh…
Sang Hyun.
Do whatever you want.
Geu Rae.
[Vietnamese fiber…]
They're not cutting us any
slack for the presentation.
They want us to pull it all off.
Same with your team?
Yes.
My partner is giving me trouble too.
Huh?
You saw how stubborn
he was last time.
I thought I'd just have
to do my part…
…whoever became my partner.
I preferred someone
I could communicate with.
I just wanted to let you know.
I didn't have ulterior
motives in mind that you think.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
No need to apologize.
You can do that after you pass.
Anything fun to share?
-Yes.
-Yes?
You shouldn't be
sitting here now.
Your team seems to
have an issue.
Huh?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
That was just a verbal contract…
But…
Yes.
Yes, sir.
I'll try to find a solution.
Yes.
Bye.
-Mr. Oh.
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm sorry.
-I told you to check it a million times!
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
I approved it, so it's
my responsibility.
No, I…
Follow me.
You never make mistakes.
I know you had a lot
on your plate. But...
…I told you many times.
You and I are on this project,
so we need to do well.
Actually, I should've
checked the FTA conditions.
-Seok Ho.
-Yes.
Do you know what's
going on in my team?
It is a big mess.
Mr. Kim's fine fiber
duster export case.
The buyer asked them to meet
the FTA conditions now.
They just mentioned it during the...
...verbal contract and
Mr. Kim missed it.
He didn't think too much about it
as it was before FTA took effect.
As far as I know, the
ship leaves tomorrow.
Exactly.
But they won't budge.
They'll annul the contract if it's not...
...fulfilled within the appointed date.
If we make cancellations and rebook,
can we make the contract date?
Rebook?
Then the ship…
We have ships with
quick arrival times.
After all procedures and if we're
lucky to get a quick ship…
Get a ship first.
Or even air transport.
Then the cost will…
Hey!
That's not the issue here.
Yes.
Come in.
I'll get it fixed within 3 days.
With the air fee, storage and
booking cancellation charge…
What will you do about the cost?
Preventing the contract annulment
is the priority here.
For trust in the future.
You're aware of that and
you created this mess?
Thank you.
Get your stuff.
-Let's go down right away.
-Ok.
Get the documents on the way.
I got the containers put in storage.
If we go now, which one can we catch?
-That…
I made reservations since the
earliest is an hour later.
Let's go.
Ok.
Mr. Oh, I'll…
Just do whatever you were doing.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
I wish I can do whatever
I was doing.
Thanks to this jerk.
To our youth!
With all our energy!
[One International Ulsan]
Geez.
There's not enough material.
Some are from China,
Indonesia, and Taiwan.
We need to make all the documents.
It'll be more complicated
than we think.
Are the Chinese documents ready?
They must be there somewhere.
We'll have to search.
I think I'll have to check the storage
and look at the documents myself.
-I'll send a fax.
-Ok.
-What about the rest?
-Mr. Hwang will call me.
Leave the importer request.
I left it on your desk.
Dang.
I'll ask Geu Rae to…
No, we have tons to do here,
so tell him to bring it down.
Yes, sir.
Why, that…
Please leave a message after…
Hey, Suk Yool!
I sent the item, so check it!
[Kim Dong Sik]
Suk Yool works here too, huh?
Hello.
Mr. Oh.
Give it to me.
Ok.
Go to the storage…
We got a ship?
Yes, there's one.
We just need the certificate
of origin in time.
Got it.
-Go to the storage and find some data.
-Ok.
Find anything about fabric
from the last 3 years.
Ok.
This way.
[Unread]
What's he doing?
-Uh…
-Huh?
Oh, my!
You pervert.
Wait.
I touched it already.
So I'll touch it once more.
Is he psycho?
Geu Rae!
The site you were talking about…
...is where you
act like a pervert?
My skin is tender like a baby.
Why won't you check the item?
I was on my way to check it.
What brings you here?
I sent three.
Hurry up and check them.
Three?
Look, Geu Rae.
I wrote 20 pages for a single item
at the company I interned at.
Yet, you found three in a week?
It's not that easy.
Just check it.
Come on.
Look, Geu Rae.
I'll do it again if I have to.
If you're dumb, you have
to put in more legwork.
Succeed with quantity?
No way.
Forty pages?
Forty-two pages?
Unbelievable.
He thinks this is a love letter?
Fifty-three pages?
Gosh.
You should be on your toes.
You ought to concentrate.
-Geez.
-Huh?
Want a massage?
Stop it!
You're so weird.
How's the presentation
coming along?
Huh?
Why?
You never asked me before.
-Our presentation preparations…
-Alright.
Fax.
Yeah.
It came.
We just need to send it to the
company with the number now.
Then I'll go to Seoul
and prepare the rest.
See you in Seoul.
Did it go well?
-Geu Rae.
-Yes?
[Geu Rae: "Yes" in Korean]
What's wrong with you?
Let's talk.
I have a question.
Have you been
conned before?
What?
They're not helpful at all.
Saps morale…
Are you talking about yourself?
About Suk Yool…
His motives are strong.
If you're incompetent,
he'll look good.
Even if you're competent,
he'll use that…
…to look good.
I see.
His motives are like a tornado.
He gives others damage
or trouble.
The center is calm though.
Aim for the center.
Did you see them?
I heard you're here with Mr. Oh
because of a team mistake.
How are the items?
This is all I did.
There's so much to do.
What did you think?
Well…
Again?
Let's go with the second item.
Are you sure?
Yes, but…
Then that's it.
Huh?
We decided on the item together.
You're experienced and
you shouldn't...
...suffer any loses because of me.
You agreed on the
item, so we're set.
Huh?
I'll create the presentation details.
So it's beneficial for me.
I'll share the data, but
I won't accept support.
As promised.
Huh?
The world of go is always a war.
And…
…sometimes you retreat
when approached…
…or try to survive together.
But the winner
and loser are clear.
How old are you?
Huh?
I lived in that world
for over a decade.
Over the years…
…my focus on winning
has grown even I'm a loser now.
I'm a pro at it.
[Certificate of origin]
We took care of
the team's mistake.
The certificate of origin was sent
in time and the forwarding agent…
A forwarding agent is a company that
organizes shipments for others.
According to the trade term dictionary.
It was sent to the forwarding agent.
And a ship was successfully
sent off in Ulsan.
And a few days later…
…he came.
[Resume: Born in 1987]
[Resume: Born in 1986]
Disciplinary committee?
I know.
Just because there were
some extra fees?
What's going on?
I know.
It doesn't usually happen.
If it happens, he'll
probably get demoted.
Must you do this to the young kid?
So why redo the item the
executive director rejected?
So it was the executive
director's idea?
He had his reasons
for rejecting it.
You were playing smart about it.
When you redid it, you were telling
him you were risking your everything.
-Sir!
-You should've done well in the first place!
Why screw up?
The committee is reviewing
it, so just wait.
Mr. Oh…
-I'll look into it too.
-Do your work.
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
If you learned about trading
contracts, work on that.
Yes.
Mr. Oh…
Do your work.
I'll take the discipline.
What else can you do?
Please leave a message after…
I heard the disciplinary
committee is on Mr. Kim…
He knows everything.
I know everything, huh?
You need to be quick
with acquiring info.
He's great at guessing too.
I didn't guess.
I'm good at reading minds.
I'm an expert…
…especially with girls' minds.
He's crazy.
Culture and trade.
Nice.
Change the title.
People need different things
depending on the culture.
-Culture…
-Wait.
What does "mentality
trapped in culture" mean?
I just happened to write that…
Geu Rae.
You don't think of our presentation
as a primary school essay, do you?
These incomprehensible sentences
will just do us harm.
If you had to interpret it…
For example…
"Would chicks in hot
countries like cosmetics?"
"Of course not, and they
don’t sell well."
That's what you meant by
"mentality trapped in culture"?
Then think about this.
There's BP fiber.
It has low durability and
thermal resistance...
...so it's bad for regular clothing.
So should we throw it out?
Think!
Have you done some thinking?
Yes.
This fiber has low
thermal conductivity.
-What's that?
-It's…
That's it!
It doesn’t absorb moisture.
What's that?
Fast dry! Will you concentrate?
We can sell it in cold countries,
but what about other issues…
This is why you need me.
The power of experience.
I'd sell long johns in cold countries.
To people trapped in the
culture of the cold climate.
I caught that, but you wrote
it without any thought.
That's being "trapped in culture."
What do you think?
You can just trust me, ok?
I'd sell long johns in
cold countries.
To people trapped in the
culture of the cold climate.
I didn't think that far.
This is why you need me.
The power of experience.
Is there no other way?
Mr. Kim is competent.
You know that, sir.
I'm responsible for
what happened.
It was just a mistake…
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Please do what you can, sir.
Thank you.
Bye.
What happened?
Mr. Kwon is eloquent,
but he's in Russia.
Mr. Oh.
Just go talk…
…to the executive director.
What?
What do you mean, what?
Why don't you take
the shortcut?
You know all he has to do...
...is put in a word.
-Mr. Ko!
-The executive director…
Yeah, I know things aren't
cool between you two.
You need to swallow
your pride this time.
The executive director?
Ok, forget it, don't go.
Dong Sik will just get a pay cut…
…and sent to the factory.
He'll just have to
sacrifice a promotion.
Yeah, your pride is more important
than your subordinate.
I'll be the only one who knows
you didn't do your best.
Why should I care
about your team?
What a pain in the neck.
You know all he has to
do is put in a word.
Yeah, I know things aren't
cool between you two.
You need to swallow
your pride this time.
Geu Rae.
Did Mr. Oh come back?
He said he'd return soon.
Yeah?
Then I'll go to KOTRA.
Ok.
See you.
-Bye.
Geu Rae.
Let's go submit the presentation files.
We can go now.
Hello.
Jang Geu Rae and
Han Suk Yool.
It's tomorrow finally.
Thank you.
I thought about it.
Let's wrap it up in a sexier way.
Let's end it with a question.
Huh?
What?
You don't understand?
I said "sexy" means "uncommon."
Not something
everyone else does.
We should end it with
a meaningful question.
An interview should convey…
That's what I'm saying.
You can infer his opinion
through the question.
So frustrating.
Let's think about the question.
Refer to some books.
Sure.
Ask me questions if any.
If you still need…
Geu Rae.
Mr. Oh.
Hello.
I didn't get the meeting briefing.
Huh?
I'll submit it soon.
Soon?
How many times did
I tell you not to...
...let the presentation
disturb your work?
I'm sorry.
You getting disregarded
looks natural.
Why just say "sure,
sure" like that?
Are you dumb or do
you lack will power?
You told me to get into
the center of the tornado.
Because the center is calm.
I could suffer damage
next to him.
Didn't you mean I should get
inside if I can't move far away?
Although he makes me mad...
...I realized I need him.
I have to acknowledge him.
It's something I can't
overlook with pride.
I'm sure of that.
I'm ashamed...
...but I have to survive for now.
[Executive director Choi]
Mr. Oh.
He's not here.
He went to the headquarters just now.
-Hello, sir.
-Hi.
See you, sir.
Oh, are you ok?
You should watch
where you're going.
Your lower body is weak, huh?
Lower body…
That's important for men.
Work out your lower body.
Run on the stairs from now on!
Geu Rae.
Yes?
You dropped one.
I'm sorry.
Did you practice reading it?
Huh?
Practice it like you're
making an announcement.
It's different from just
reading it to yourself.
When you're nervous,
your breathing shakes.
If you speak louder for others…
…you'll be out of breath.
Don't just rely on the mic.
That's tougher.
Listen to your tense
breath on the speakers.
That'll make you even
more nervous.
If you time yourself,
it would be good too.
Listen to your tense
breath on the speakers.
That'll make you even more nervous.
If you time yourself,
it would be good too.
It will be nice and comfortable.
See you on the rooftop.
What's with him?
Mr. Choi's office.
This is Mr. Oh.
Is he in now?
Yes, but he just left for the day.
Did you tell him
I wanted to see him?
Yes, I did.
Did he say anything?
No, he didn't.
Geu Rae.
What is it?
How about practicing
it out loud?
We can record it and
time ourselves.
Huh?
Why?
It's Mr. Oh's advice.
It'll be helpful.
It's ok.
Geez.
I'm in charge of the details.
This is one of the details.
Did you forget I'll do the talking?
Let's do it.
Let's check the length
since it'll be strict.
So?
Will you shorten it
if it's too long?
We can't do that.
I already memorized it.
We can't change…
That will mess everything up.
-We already submitted the slides.
-Hey!
Don't say whatever you want!
Watch what you say.
Isn't it good to find
issues beforehand?
-Mr. Oh…
The guy who's putting his
responsibility on subordinates?
What?
Why should he get in
trouble for that?
What happened to your team…
…is all Mr. Oh's fault.
We all know that.
Are you done?
He comes and messes up all
the files at our factory.
How could a pro do that?
I can't treat him like a boss.
Blood…
I told you to watch
what you say.
What do you know
about my boss?
We're both interns, man!
What do you mean, boss?
You work here, jerk?
Don’t talk to me like that, idiot!
You don’t talk to me like that!
Come here.
It didn't hurt at all.
Wait.
text!
Text.
[Presentation task: What item would
you sell to your partner and why?]
Sell it to the last person…
…I want to sell it to?
[Misaeng]
I wouldn't ever buy that.
What will I do with him?
It will be a fun day.
Let's do it.
I mean, please do well.
We'll talk for 10 minutes
and have Q&A for 5.
We should have used a good idea.
Community college…
Our company is good…
They're really good.
Geu Rae and Suk Yool.
Suk Yool.
I forgot.
Next.
I'll do it.
Why, that…
I'll forget why I chose him.