Not Yet Alive
Hey!
You call this work?
You should've made this
understandable!
What is this?
Contracts, bills, complaints!
The report order is all random!
I'll redo it, sir.
It's regarding the Resources team,...
...at least you don't make them
call us again to double check!
Yes, sir.
Thankfully, only I hadn't changed.
[Fabric Team 1, Han Suk Yool]
Suk Yool.
It has been a week.
Suk Yool couldn't get adjusted
to the office environment.
We got a refusal as a reply.
Hold on, please.
Baek Ki was not being treated well.
Young Yi...
...became a pro
at delivering things.
I don’t have chopsticks.
Young Yi.
Chopsticks.
Kimchi's missing.
Young Yi.
Call the restaurant to get it.
She was so confident as
an intern two months ago.
Now she was putting up with
the seniors' cold treatment.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 5]
Hello, sir.
Young Yi!
I feel like I'll have a
great day thanks to you.
Good morning.
Hi.
You're running late today.
Am I?
No, you're usually 30 minutes
earlier than us.
I had to take my kid to daycare.
My husband is working now.
-Hello, Geu Rae and Young Yi.
-Hello.
You know Ms. Sun from Sales Team 1?
She's a true pro.
Until Young Yi came.
She's the most popular employee
whom guys want to drink with.
By the way, I'm the least popular.
You're the #1 employee
they want to work with.
By the way, I'm the least popular again.
We entered the company together...
...but she's climbing the
ladder faster than me.
You're doing job training today?
Yes.
She's the toughest working...
...woman here and she's respected.
Teach them a good lesson.
When's loading?
Next month around the 15th.
What's the penalty fee
if that's changed?
Penalty…
Taking memos is good..
...but you should thoroughly
understand current contracts.
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna check your
note in front the buyer too?
No, sir.
From now on…
…for each contract you
give to Dong Sik and me…
…give me a summary of where
you're sending what and when.
Yes, sir.
Oh, yeah.
Did you finish the Resources transfer?
I sent it yesterday.
I get more suspicious
when he's so chirpy.
Where are the approval conditions?
DA 91, sir.
What about Joshua's mistake?
Myanmar case?
Ok.
The last one is Turkmenistan?
Yes.
Let's see.
How come there's only a B/L draft?
[B/L draft: A draft created before
the bill is issued to the shipper…
...as a contract of carriage of goods]
Huh?
You didn't get the official B/L
from sales team 3?
[B/L: Receipt for cargo
accepted for transportation]
Well...
I knew it.
Oh Sang Sik.
-You're in trouble.
-Huh?
Where's the original B/L?
Well…
He didn't write the company
name, seller, and buyer info…
...and got profits in his pocket
without the original.
Call him now.
Huh?
Now!
Yes.
Uh, Mr. Oh.
About the one on Turkmenistan.
How come there's only a B/L draft?
What?
Where's the original B/L?
Huh?
Sorry won't cut it.
Mr. Jung.
What?
A newbie did it?
Hey!
Train them well.
Don’t let it happen again.
What did he say?
He said he's sorry.
Hello?
Shall I go there or
you want to come here?
Shall I go?
You're with Mr. Ma, aren't you?
Hello.
Hi.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Why'd you put in the B/L draft?
I gave you the B/L two months ago!
No, you didn't.
We never got it.
I know you and Mr. Ma.
Aren't you even embarrassed?
What?
Even if you're scared of Mr. Ma,
you should take responsibility!
How'd you get to that position?
What's wrong with you?
You're the one who didn't
take responsibility!
What?
It just ends with my being embarrassed.
There was no death like someone.
Mr. Jung.
Oh…
What did you just say?
Let him go.
What?
Let go.
Let him go.
What, you want to hit me?
Go ahead.
-Come on.
-Here.
Oh, gosh...
Come on, let's have another funeral.
Mr. Jung!
Mr. Oh!
What are you doing?
Why'd you hit him?
If they said the B/L is missing, you
should check and solve the issue!
Are you a kid?
How can you hit him first...
Sang Sik.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
Nothing for you to apologize about.
The Turkmenistan one is
from two months ago.
I'm sure I gave Mr. Oh the bill
before I went on my business trip.
The meticulous man couldn't
have forgotten to give it over.
Why did Mr. Jung have
to bring up the past?
[Resignation]
Who died?
Yun Jae, he died.
What happened?
Was it a suicide?
Any will?
Were there any rumors that
could give us trouble?
Was there anything about me?
That jerk.
He acts all noble and
hides when he's cornered?
He's not in the place to hit people.
He only put in the B/L draft.
Where's the original B/L?
He said he gave it to us.
That jerk needs to be
embarrassed to wake up.
What's going on with the B/L?
I don't know.
I don't care anymore now.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
So, Mr. Oh really
could've given it over.
Why'd you have to bring all this
chaos when you're not sure?
That's not the issue here.
We weren't going to make
the B/L a big issue.
He just went to ask and he hit him.
He threw him in front of everyone.
That shows how Mr. Oh
disregards our team.
That's why I'm saying sorry.
Why should you be sorry?
The guy who hit him should be.
He should give an official
apology to the one he hit.
Ok.
Alright.
And…
…tell him to upload an apology
on the Company Intranet.
No way, Mr. Ma!
Are you trying to embarrass Mr. Oh?
He needs to be embarrassed.
Last year, because of him, I…
Anyway, if he doesn't do it,
I'll make this a bigger issue.
What will you do?
Tell them it's bullshit.
Mr. Oh!
Hey!
Is Mr. Jung ok?
Yes.
He's not hurt.
Mr. Oh said he's sure he sent it.
I can't look for it.
I know.
What are you two
so serious about?
You don’t want the training?
Geu Rae. I heard there was
some fun on your floor.
Oh, I heard news about Mr. Oh
just the other day.
I'm sorry about what
I said about him on the rooftop.
By the way, my friend...
...I could see why he got upset.
He has a story.
I was told that in the past Mr. Oh…
Nice to meet you.
Sit down.
I'm Sun Ji Young from Sales Team 1...
...and I'll be in charge of training.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sure you've seen
the emails I sent out.
What I sent…
[Husband]
What I sent is feedback...
...from our business partners…
I have a funeral to attend.
Pick up So Mi from
the daycare, honey.
It shows how Sales Team 1 and
One International work hard…
…on client care and
contract management.
Let's see how important document...
...communication is
through your emails.
-It's all a strategy, you know.
-Huh?
They don’t give you work, right?
They want to show who's
boss in the beginning.
That's what Mr. Song said.
It's all because you're talented.
So keep your chin up.
Young Yi's luckier since
you have work at least.
It's tough to get adjusted
to Resources.
They don't know how
to become friends with women...
...but I'm loved by bosses.
Hello, sir.
Is training over, Young Yi?
Run here now.
I'll be right over.
I'll get going.
My boss always needs me.
Oh, dear.
Hello, sir.
Sir.
You think you're above meetings?
Gosh, the meeting with
me was nothing to you?
You didn't say it was urgent...
...so I was going to go
after finishing the proposal.
Accounting said they need it
by today for setting budgets.
Then you should've
pulled an all-nighter.
What will you do about the
meeting on company selection?
This is why I can't work
with women.
No sense of sacrifice.
What can I expect?
Why are you so stiff?
Aren't you going to
say you're sorry?
I'm sorry.
Go.
Get out of my face.
You can take her there
before you leave.
Leave it to your mother
or whatever.
It's what we promised.
Are you the only one who works?
It's the meeting I postponed
a week because of you.
I can't postpone it again.
Never mind, I have to
go out for work now.
I'm sorry about that.
It's ok.
Is something wrong?
Your eyes are red.
It's ok.
Oh, my.
Thanks.
So Mi's mother.
So Mi forgot to take this yesterday.
Yes.
Thanks.
See you…
Your child must have drawn it...
...but there's no face.
She didn't finish it, I guess.
[Columbia…]
[Condo export (x)]
[Condom export (o)]
Why do you keep looking at me?
Huh?
I asked, why do you
keep looking at me?
Sorry.
Are you at your seat?
Can I go see you now?
You know…
…I didn't finish what I was saying.
Actually, you won't
feel good about this.
Sit down.
Someone died because of Mr. Oh.
Stop looking over.
-Take care of this.
-Sure.
That's nonsense!
Sit, sit.
It was when he was
an assistant manager.
Something his subordinate
did went wrong.
Mr. Oh must've been at fault too.
Mr. Oh ignored him...
...when he resigned.
The subordinate opened
a small shop with his mother.
But…
…he died in an accident
making a delivery.
So they're saying it wouldn't
have happened...
...if Mr. Oh had taken
responsibility.
Go.
I'm going.
-Ok.
-Go.
Mr. Oh is something else.
This is so wrong of him.
Mr. Oh wouldn't avoid
responsibility.
You never know about people.
Who wants to get fired?
Sir.
Chemicals is really being stubborn.
You asked for Mr. Oh's help before.
Now you want us out?
So, don't you know
what we went through...
...for the Japan and China
cases and meet with them?
Hey!
Give it!
-Give it over!
-No, that won't solve it.
This is too much…
Hey, take it!
How can you just give it over?
This has to do with our performance.
We did all the work and you
want to give them the benefits?
How could you let that happen?
Mr. Oh!
Please!
Uh…
They're thinking whatever they want.
Why won't you say something?
What are they thinking wrong?
The executive director signed
a contract with a bad company.
You know it was an absurd contract.
You know everyone knew
it was a bad company.
I heard he
even got a commission...
...while Eun Jae took all the blame!
His death has nothing to do with
you, so just tell them the truth!
Nothing will change whether
it was my fault or his.
That time…
…I didn't take the responsibility.
How I didn't say I would
take responsibility…
…won't change.
Mr. Oh.
How many people could take
responsibility in that situation?
Everyone would've done the same.
Let's go.
We need to prepare
for the training meeting.
Why Eun Jae?
If not him, will you
take responsibility?
Will you do that?
Daycare centers only
open until 6 P.M.
We can't ask them to
understand again.
Soo Jin.
Oh, my!
Are you ok?
Soo Jin.
Get up, Soo Jin.
Come on, let's move her
to the nursing room.
Hey, help her.
-Are you ok?
-Soo Jin.
She's pregnant and she
must have overworked herself.
What?
Pregnant?
Yes, she needs rest.
Hey.
Did you know that?
No.
Geez, how many kids
is she having?
Didn't you say she has two kids?
Yes.
Why'd she get pregnant again?
She's so selfish.
Move!
She got pregnant again?
Another leave?
We covered so much for her after
the first and second kids.
When will we train the
employees and all?
I busted my behind after
she had her second kid.
Gosh, we'll have to borrow
other team members.
Geez.
Women are always the problem.
After all that studying, they get
married, have pregnant, a husband…
They have so many excuses.
Or they try to get a
quick fix by crying.
That's because they're unloyal.
Do your work.
Ms. Sun.
Thank you.
Soo Jin's been working
overtime for the whole week.
I wonder why she didn’t tell us.
She couldn't have.
Third kid is tough.
Times have changed,
but working...
...and taking care of kids is hard.
Working moms are
always at fault.
To the company, to in-laws…
…and of course the kid.
It's impossible
without the husband's help.
If you want to continue
working, don’t get married.
It will save you trouble.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yeah.
Time for the meeting.
Ok.
-I wish he wouldn't come.
-Huh?
Oh, nothing.
Mr. Oh.
Regarding the Resources
takeover case…
How about not joining that one?
Why not?
I'm aware of everything,
so I won't make any mistakes.
Each team will hand in the reports.
Our team will give you a report...
...regarding the Indonesia
case when we're ready.
You're aware it will take 2-3
days to receive a reply, right?
I hope Resources can
give us some more time.
We'll take it you'll give
us 2-3 days and wrap it up.
Fine.
The other teams can just
do your data organization.
Sometimes they keep calling us.
Take care of that, Mr. Ha.
Sure.
Sir.
I think we can wrap it up.
How can we wrap it up?
There's no B/L.
Sir, you can talk about that later…
You really won't give it over?
I told you it's been given over.
What company is in on this too?
How much did you pocket?
Sir.
You know Mr. Oh wouldn't do that.
You, be quiet.
Women should know their place.
Sir.
Then you should've talked
to me in private.
What?
Why aren't you apologizing?
Why won't you upload it?
Since there's nothing
to apologize about.
Why not?
After hitting a man?
Gosh.
You've aged, but you're
still irresponsible.
Still.
Excuse me?
Irresponsible…
What do kids say this days?
Ir…
-Irresman.
-Yeah.
The irresman is evolving by the day.
This isn't about what
happened last year, is it?
What?
What are you talking about?
The complaint regarding your
sexual harassment issue.
What?
When I stood witness.
Hey Oh Sang Sik!
Why bring that up here?
And, sexual harassment?
Why's that sexual harassment?
She shouldn't have worn
that low-cut shirt.
Did I touch or look inside?
"If you're going to hide yourself
each time you bend over, why'd you wear that?
Just let it all hang out."
Is that sexual harassment?
That's sexual harassment?
That was sarcasm.
I meant don't wear such stuff.
"There's nothing worth seeing."
You added that.
So…
…is that sexual harassment?
Asking them for
a cup of coffee is too.
Worrying they can't
get married is too.
I hate all these tough women!
Young Yi.
You tell me.
Is that sexual harassment?
Is it?
Why can't you answer me?
I think it is…
…if the person who heard it…
…was sexually offended.
What?
Hey!
What did you just say?
Where are you going?
You told me to write an apology!
I'm going to do that!
You should wrap
things up in there.
Yes.
I'm going nuts.
An apology?
You read each word carefully.
I'm sure he'll say something wrong.
Yes.
Let's go.
There's a meeting with a client.
Gosh.
That jerk.
Geez.
Mr. Ma got in trouble
for sexual harassment?
He got a pay cut
for 3 months for it.
Mr. Oh stood witness for it?
Mr. Oh is hard to understand too.
He stands for justice
in times like that.
He's so different in his
situations, it's hard to understand.
Geez.
He's good at work though.
Wrap it up.
Mr. Kang.
Wait up.
I wonder where the B/L went.
Mr. Oh is amazing.
He's just insisting he gave it when
they say they didn’t receive it.
He's saying he gave it since he did.
So where is it?
You mean Resources is lying?
We were interns two months ago.
Baek Ki.
You were an intern there, right?
Yes.
You didn't see it?
No.
Baek Ki.
What is it?
The B/L.
You really didn't see it then?
I said I never saw it.
Why?
You were working there, so
I was wondering if you did.
What are you trying to say?
I worked there, so I should know?
Do you know all about your team?
Why don't you go dig
through the files?
No need to drag me into this.
Baek Ki.
There's a B/L from the
Sales Team 3 on the desk.
Bring that over.
You really never saw it?
Why do you keep asking?
You never saw it?
It'll be better if you didn't
know if I did or not.
What are you saying?
If I say I did, will
you tell Sales Team 3?
Think about your position.
If that's revealed, how do you
think Resources will treat you?
It's like pouring gas over fire.
Why do that?
Mr. Oh won't take your side just
because you help Sale Team 3.
-Baek Ki.
-This isn't your business.
You're in Resources.
That's reality.
Mr. Oh is a true man.
[Frigging sorry.]
Oh, my!
Geu Rae.
Read it.
Come on.
Sorry.
All of it.
Frigging sorry.
Why, that psycho...
Mr. Oh.
Why did you do that?
What?
Why?
He wanted an apology,
so I gave one.
I wanted to give
a nice Granny Red...
...but they're out now.
Sir!
Oh Sang Sik!
I'm going nuts.
Sang Sik!
You want to see this to the end?
Come on.
I wrote the apology.
Hey, you!
Do you need a lesson
to come back to your senses?
I said I'd wrap
it up with an apology!
That's what I did.
I said I'm really sorry.
-What?
-Ok?
I'm sorry.
Frigging sorry.
-Why…
-Why, you!
How dare you?
Sir!
-Let go!
-Sir!
Sir!
Let go!
Now!
Mr. Kim!
Are you ok?
There was a big thug
when he got hit.
You want a piece of me?
How dare you?
Who do you think you are?
Let go!
Are you ok?
Hey.
Are your bones okay,
nothing broken?
I'll go to the hospital.
Go ahead.
Get CAT scans, MRI,
the whole works.
Get a blood test too.
Hey! If your brain gets
damaged, it's bad!
Why, that…
I'll be ok.
Really?
Don't worry, I'll be ok.
Sir, let's go.
Call me if there are
any problems.
Geez.
It's ok.
Mr. Kim!
Sit down.
I'll go to Accounting.
Ok.
Geu Rae.
Get me some water.
Ok.
Oh, those jerks…
Sir, sir?
Those jerks.
They're trying to threaten
us by hurting themselves now?
They're like gangsters.
Don’t ever work with
Sales Team 3 again.
Sir, let's wrap it up.
Mr. Oh must've learned
his lesson.
Give me my glasses.
Uh…
Geez.
Young Yi.
Bring me some coffee.
Sure.
What will we do?
The issue is getting bigger.
Why didn't you just say it
when he signed it?
You should have
honestly said it was left out.
Hey, our boss wasn't being told off
for once and I couldn't say that.
Also, Mr. Oh is all worked up.
I couldn't do that.
What will we do?
Shall we shred it?
If Dong Sik asks for me,
tell him I went for a smoke.
Sure.
Mr. Oh wouldn't miss a B/L.
Who cares if he's good?
You can't do anything
about newbies.
You're right.
He won't know what
B/Ls and drafts are.
Sales Team 3 is in
the Mr. Choi's...
...bad book and they're
treated poorly.
They have the worst
seats and few employees.
That's why they have
such a newbie.
Mr. Oh.
Why aren't you working?
I have a question.
You have a light?
No, sir.
Men should know how to smoke.
I used to smoke 3 packs
a day when I was your age.
And you don't know the basic.
You should have a
lighter to serve others.
I'm sorry.
What's your question?
Uh…
The B/L.
Is there any possibility you
gave it and I missed it?
Huh?
So…
…are you covering for me…
No, right.
Go do your work!
Geu Rae.
Hi.
-Make two copies and file them.
-Yes.
Mr. Kim.
What?
How long do you keep
received B/Ls?
Why?
You want to look for it?
Shall I?
No way.
You want to go search
another team's stuff?
That's nonsense.
If it was possible,
I would've done it already.
-Hurry up with that.
-Yes.
What was he talking about?
About B/L…
I hope he doesn't
search Resources.
He can't be that stupid.
Look.
Yes.
Bring this for the buyer meeting.
Again?
We postponed it last week.
I know.
Delay it for just 3 hours.
I'm sorry.
Ok.
Sign this.
Sure.
You're picking up your kid?
Your parents can't?
Right.
I have to leave her
with my in-laws.
I'm a guy too,
but guys think...
...girls should give in all the time.
They don't know how hard girls...
...have to work to climb
up the ladder.
That too.
I know.
That's why my wife stopped
working too.
You have three kids.
If not, I would've quit.
What's he doing?
Good job.
About keeping silent.
Geu Rae.
Why are you lurking
around Resources?
Were you looking for the B/L?
No, sir.
Then why'd you go there?
Did you go to see Young Yi?
Come here.
Did you ask Young Yi?
No, I…
Why didn't you ask her?
Should I ask her?
No way!
Who told you to lurk
around there?
Don't you have work to do?
I'm sorry.
-Geu Rae.
-Huh?
[Geu Rae: "Yes" in Korean]
Not you.
Go on a business trip
if you're so idle.
Huh?
Ms. Sun.
This isn't right.
It's ok.
No.
It could become a problem if a
subordinate gets involved in personal issues.
Hold on.
Mr. Oh, Geu Rae…
It's ok.
I don't want him to
cause accidents here.
I can't be any more embarrassed.
Mr. Oh is really doing
things his way today.
Thanks.
No problem.
Meeting a client?
Yes.
I'm going for Ms. Sun's child.
Huh?
That's good.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Geu Rae.
Is Mr. Oh ok?
Huh?
Mr. Oh shouldn't have brought...
...up what happened before.
He should respect people have...
...things they don’t want
brought up again.
I understand why Mr. Oh
got that mad.
He's not mad now.
He's blaming himself.
Most bad choices become
regrets and get forgotten...
...but not always.
Some things haunt you forever.
They don’t get forgotten...
...and you can't take them back.
He's blaming himself.
He looks lonely to me.
I came to get So Mi.
Yes.
I got a call from So Mi's mother.
Let's go home, So Mi.
Ok.
Alright.
They're in the all-day class.
Their mothers will come soon.
Where's my mom?
She'll come soon.
Let's go wait inside.
Let's go.
Can they play with me
in the playground?
We have to be with
them as guardians.
The teacher will go home
soon and I have to work.
I'll stay with them.
I'll just go home late.
The flower has bloomed.
Come on.
1, 2, 3.
Nice.
You're fast.
Hello.
Let's go home.
Bye.
Up you go.
Some things haunt you forever.
They don’t get forgotten...
...and you can't take them back.
We'll take care of that, oh!
I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Is everyone gone?
They went to the buyers' meeting.
I'll carry some.
Thanks.
Resources is tough, isn't it?
It's always been tough for women.
They always discriminate
between the genders...
...but only elites go there.
You're hanging in there very well.
It's not that easy.
Right?
Uh, Ms. Sun…
I have a question.
Sure.
There's something I should
do and I know it's right.
I'm hesitant about it though.
Why?
It might complicate things.
Does it have to do
with Resources?
Does ignoring something
that's right...
...make things more simple?
At least, you can avoid criticism.
It's because I'm a girl…
I don't know what it is.
What does gender have
to do with what's right?
It has to do with…
…your conscience.
Regarding conscience…
Everyone knows.
There are people who don't
do it when they know…
…those who do because they know.
Geu Rae.
Sorry.
For telling you now.
It would've been better
if I'd brought the B/L...
...but I couldn't possibly do that.
Anyway, I'm in Resources.
Yes.
It's in the bottom file box.
This is the cabinet number.
I'll take care of So Mi.
Thank you.
Who are you?
I'm So Mi's teacher.
I work for One International.
I'm taking care of
So Mi for Geu Rae.
I guess he had to go.
Yes.
He had to go for work.
By the way, are you two dating?
Huh?
No.
Then please give me
his cell number.
Huh?
She said it was here.
Who's that?
Why, you…
What are you doing?
How dare you go through
our cabinet?
Come here.
You…
You came for the B/L, huh?
Did Mr. Oh ask you?
No.
Come, you're dead.
I know what he's like.
Is this what you
learned from him?
I know the B/L is here.
What are you saying?
Where is Sang Sik?
He went home after asking
his subordinate to steal?
I'll make sure he can't
work here again.
Where is he?
Tell him to come now.
Tell him to come now, jerk!
Ha!
The guy with no connection
brings in this guy...
... through nepotism and
makes him steal?
Hey.
The guy with no connections is here.
What are you doing?
I've been respecting you.
You want to be embarrassed
in front of a newbie?
Or you want to go to the rooftop?
How do we know
if it's from you or us?
We don't...
...but you and I know.
What no… nonsense is that?
Someone knows it's
from Resources.
Who?
Who knows?
I won't let you go…
…if you bring up Yun Jae again.
Ok?
Yes.
Also…
…if you screw Sales
Team 3 again…
…I'll kill you.
Ok.
Tell Mr. Ma you found it.
Mr. Oh…
Upload an apology.
Please…
Or I'll kill you.
I'm sorry.
Shall we have a drink?
Mr. Oh…
Can I ask you a question?
No.
How did you know the
Resources cabinet number?
Someone told me.
Who?
None of your business.
How come she didn't
draw my face?
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry.
-Where's So Mi?
-Sleeping.
-She drew this?
-Yeah.
She didn't draw my face.
I look like a ghost.
I have nothing to say either.
I guess I'm always sleeping.
You have golf tomorrow, right?
Your clothes are ready.
Things will be smooth.
I'll take care of So Mi tomorrow.
I'll come straight home.
There's no solution.
We're working hard for ourselves...
...but we're suffering because of it.
It'll be better when So Mi grows a bit.
Yes.
Right.
I'll take it there before 10.
It's ready…
Hello.
So Mi, you came.
Yes.
That's no problem.
We're making the orders.
I'll call you back.
So Mi, say bye.
1, 2, 3.
Bye.
You were always looking
at me like that.
The back of my head.
See you later.
I won't push you away again.
So Mi.
Will you draw me today?
Ok, I'll draw you.
Honey!
Where are my socks?
Socks.
Why'd you drink so much?
Bye, dad.
Ok.
Study hard.
Work hard!
-Ok.
-Bye!
What?
It won't open.
Why is he here?
What is it?
Oh…
He brought you
here last night...
...but I guess he was
too drunk to go.
What?
Hey!
Geu Rae.
What are you doing?
Oh…
Hello.
[Misaeng]
Hurray!
This is what life is!
Here you go.
I heard it was you who
told about the B/L.
This must be what adultery feels like.
Come on.
You don't like this?
Oh, it's nice.
What will happen to Dong Sik?
-He has a GED.
-I heard there's a lot to learn from you.
I said one thing.
Do it the right way.
-I'm stupid.
-Fool.
Gather all the teams now.
I'll be waiting…
[Resignation]