Not Yet Alive
If you want to accomplish something,
health should be your priority.
The reason you lag towards the end,
the reason you recover
slowly from damage,
and the reason a mistake
affects you for so long,
are all because you're
health is not at the best.
When you're unfit, you want to be
comfortable and you lose patience.
Then you become so tired,
you don't care about victories.
If you want to win, your body
should be able to withstand
your challenges.
Will power is nothing without
your body health.
What do you do on the weekends?
I watch movies
read books
and sometimes exercise.
I like exercising too, I do yoga.
I heard you moved out of home.
Yes.
I agree parents have done their deed
by raising their kids up to age 20.
Right.
We can't rely on our dads anymore.
We need an oppa by that age.
[Oppa: Older male or older brother]
How's working for a big company?
You must have enough money for a house.
Even large ones.
An Na wants to get married soon.
An Na hates working.
It cramps your style and
makes you look poor.
Healing.
Healing is necessary.
Welcome.
I'll have the earliest show of My Way.
What brings you here?
I live nearby.
You too?
No.
I was in the area.
That's a blind date outfit right there.
Huh?
No.
Friend's wedding.
You must not have enjoyed it.
Right.
The bride wasn't nice.
She was interested in the
groom's company's loan system.
-The wedding was a horror movie.
-Horror?
Are you here alone?
Yes.
Thank you.
One, two.
Give it to me.
Why didn't you tell me
you didn't like horror?
You saw two in a row today.
There's a nice blood stew
place nearby, shall we go?
See you tomorrow.
Baek Ki.
Shall I tell you another scary story?
Huh?
Tomorrow's Monday.
Look, I made dad's company.
Hey, dad!
Get up!
Stop!
You should play with them on Sundays!
Let me get some rest on Sundays.
I want to rest too!
Honey.
I feel so weird today.
Under the weather.
You're still drunk!
Here.
Have some onion juice.
I'll make the kids
ginseng and yours too.
I don't need that.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 8]
Hello.
- Hi.
- -Da In.
You look tired.
-You too.
-No way.
-I'm just busy.
-Ask for more people.
-Don't say that if you won't come.
-Invite me.
Congratulations.
Hello.
I'm sorry about the rare
earth resource item.
There's nothing for
you to be sorry about.
Mr. Oh is disappointed, isn't he?
Yes.
Mr. Kim is going to
support him this time.
He'll give him a big one.
[Middle East Mecca Phone export]
The Arab Mecca Phone item?
It's worth $3 mil.
The IT Sales team was on it,
so it's nearly prepared.
Will Mr. Mun be on it again?
Then who else?
I can't do it.
What?
You know what he's like.
Give me a job I can do.
Hey, you earn a salary,
so how can you say that?
You should be able to do anything
you're told to do!
Anyway, I don?t want to be
embarrassed in front of my kids.
You're ridiculous.
You want to idle around at home?
Yes, I'll do that.
I'll submit my resignation.
Resignation?
Dong Sik's issue affected
our dept.'s performance.
Ok, if you sign the deal,
I'll get you more people.
Really?
So did you say you'd do it?
Did you say you wouldn't do it?
Anyway, he said we'd get more people.
Can't you just do it?
He has to do it.
What is he worried about then?
I can't commit a crime as a dad.
This is just like embezzlement.
I think it's different.
It's worse, man!
Ok, if you say so, but my question is,
did you say you'd do it or not?
You want to be stubborn
with that absurd reason?
Alright.
From now on, I'll give your team
all the sales headquarters' work.
-Repair those damages from now on!
-Huh?
That's just... absurd!
It's the Mecca Phone data from IT Sales.
But?
The agency list is here too.
So we have to do it.
Call them to check the progress,
-models and make applications.
-Yes.
We could be doomed.
Huh?
What will you do?
We have to do it.
We need to find a solution.
A way to make him give up.
Dong Sik.
Project budget.
We don't have much left, do we?
What?
You're short on the project budget?
Yes.
I really want to do it, but I can't.
Yeah?
Use mine.
If that's not enough, get a receipt.
I'll take care of it all.
Here.
It was weird.
Mr. Oh took on any job.
I wonder why not this one.
He has a unique character.
Character.
Huh?
Mr. Mun?
He has a big distribution
company in the Middle East.
It's a big client.
They're a key partner.
Then why is Mr. Oh?
Mr. Mun is quirky,
so everyone avoids him.
So it's of little interest
from our point of view.
Look.
Why do you think IT Sales told us to
have it forsaking their performance?
Is he fussy?
You just? have to
make things happen, you know.
Mr. Oh's character?
This goes against his principles.
Principles?
What principles?
Oh!
Ok.
Let's get sick.
I bought expired milk
as you asked me to.
Good.
I also put it under the sun for
three hours as you asked me to.
Good.
What will you do with this?
Drink it.
Huh?
If we get food poisoning,
he can't make us do it.
Mr. Oh!
Drink it.
How can we drink this?
You have to.
Ok.
You still have some.
Man.
Is it coming out?
No, it was dirty.
I'm not getting any signals.
Me neither.
Are you sure it was expired?
Yes, I'm sure, sir.
Is your stomach fine too, Mr. Oh?
Dang lactic acid bacteria!
He said "principle."
Principle.
Work is everything for us,
so I wonder what principle
could possibly go against it.
Is there such a thing?
Yes, Sales Team 3, Oh Sang Sik.
Hello.
This is Madam Cha at Jangwon.
We had our grand opening in Shinsa-dong.
I called to say hi.
Why are you calling this office?
Jangwon?
Oh Sang Sik speaking.
- Hello, Mr. Oh Sang Sik.
- Kim Dong Sik speaking.
We've renovated our
place in Bangbae-dong.
Not interested.
I'll tell him.
-Geez.
-I'll call you back.
Yes, sir.
It's Mr. Lee from a luxury
lounge in Seocho-dong.
-He said he'd give you a 20% discount.
-Hey!
Rumors must've spread, last
time with the IT Sales team...
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Oh Sang Sik?
Yes, I am.
I'm Michelle Jang of
Partners Cooperation.
I want to be your business partner.
But what is?
Ms. Bae.
You'll be doing business with CEO
Mr. Mun in the Arab, correct?
We sealed the contract last year
entertaining him with Sales Team 1.
You can ignore all
the calls you've received.
Partners Cooperation will
be your best partner.
From limousine pickup service,
to any service the VIP wants.
We'll satisfy all your needs.
Of course,
round 2 also, satisfaction guaranteed.
Just overlook it
this time, buddy. Ok?
Don't you feel sorry for Dong Sik?
His face looks like a sick chicken now.
What?
Mr. Kim promised to get
you more people, right?
Geez.
Mun Chung Gi making a dirty
mess at the bar is one thing.
There's a reason Mr. Oh
hates entertaining him.
He's always wants round 2.
Round 2?
It's illegal, of course.
Some buyers want that even these days.
Mr. Oh won't do it because of his
principles, not just the laws.
Principles.
So what do you mean?
Well, he told me a few times.
So, it has to do
with human rights.
Human dignity something?
So I can't explain it.
Mr. Oh's principle is he won't
ever entertain them with round 2.
So he puts people above work?
Right.
It's so frustrating.
Honestly, this is a team effort, and
there's no such thing as principles.
You do what you have to.
If we just pull this off,
this quarter's performance will be good.
Eat it.
I'm good.
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Hey.
What are you worried about?
-Just finish with round 1.
-What?
Get him drunk and sign
the deal, it's simple.
He'll be down with round 1.
The Mecca Phone item
is a headache, right?
I know everything.
I want to help you since
I'm smart regarding that area.
Unfortunately, I'm so busy myself.
Baek Ki!
Hey!
I want to help him too.
There's no solution.
I hope he doesn't get different ideas.
[Task: Mark order, organize
order, mark "-"?]
[Order]
[Mark "-"]
You can leave now if you want
to work at a different company.
I'm Lee Ji Hyun at headhunting
firm, Search & Brains.
I'd like to recommend good companies
if you're thinking of changing jobs.
Great timing.
Hey, about the carbon emission item.
[Carbon emission allowance: Right to emit
a certain amount of six greenhouse gases]
Finance gave approval.
The day has finally come.
Whose business shall we make it?
Let's make it yours.
It was originally your plan.
Young Yi just added Russian photos.
She made the crucial hit.
So, do it together.
Huh?
-No, she can do it herself.
-Why, you!
That's absurd.
She's smart, but still a newbie.
She can't do it alone.
I can't work with her!
Hey!
You think I want to give her work?
This could be a big success.
Think of the team!
Finance gave approval?
Yeah.
Good job.
Thanks.
Mr. Ha's in charge, so support him well.
Ok, I'll do my best.
-Sir.
-Let's talk.
Tell him you can't do it.
Huh?
Don't feign ignorance.
You thought I'd want to work with you?
I'll support you well.
Hey, don't you get it?
"I'll support you well"?
You want to act cool to the end?
-Sir?
-Tell him you can't do it.
If you're a part of our team,
don't cause any more trouble!
Don't you feel sorry for Dong Sik?
His face looks like a sick chicken now.
One International,
Kim Dong Sik speaking.
Yes, hello.
Yes.
I'm not sure about that matter.
I'll check and call you back.
Yes.
Bye.
Mr. Kim.
Yes.
Mr. Kim promised to get
you more people, right?
Dong Sik!
Yes?
Let's do it!
Yes.
Huh?
Let's do it.
Do it!
Let's do it!
I'll seal the deal by round 1.
Geu Rae.
Tell Suk Yool to come.
I'll start now.
This is the entertainment strategy
for Mecca Phone CEO Mun Chung Gi.
His trade insurance
corporation grade is A.
-His occupation?
-I know,
that's not important.
This is the list of people who
failed to sign the contract with him.
They have one thing in common.
They all couldn't or wouldn't
entertain him with round 2.
When they did have round 2,
they all signed the deal,
or had a positive response.
-None of them signed after round 1?
-No.
Ok, what's the possibility he'll
sign it when he's drunk after round 1?
The answer is, we don't know.
He's never been dead drunk.
Let's say he happened to get hammered.
He's laid-back,
liberal, and a big bluff.
[Can you withstand Mun's
alcohol tolerance?]
He might feel good,
so it could be possible.
-That's the alternative we have for now.
-Ok.
Like I said before, the problem is
he's never been hammered.
How's his tolerance?
For a 40% degrees whiskey?
He has to have three
bottles of 40% degrees
whiskeys within 1.5 hours to get drunk.
So it's a bottle per
hour, just make it simple.
I'm sorry.
We must get him to sign by round 1.
We can't get drunk first.
Sorry I'm late.
Things ran late.
[Operation plan: Victory!]
The seating is key.
Mr. Oh will sit here and Mr. Kim
on the opposite side.
Geu Rae will sit next to Mr. Kim.
Mr. Mun will sit
in the seat of honor?
Young Yi.
Sorry.
Glad you're here, Young Yi.
- Later.
- Mr. Oh.
Mr. Oh.
Sit down.
This is Mr. Mun.
She can't be him.
Aren't you busy?
I am, excuse me.
Sit down.
Mr. Oh will pour Mr. Mun a drink.
Next you will, Mr. Kim.
While he's drinking,
Mr. Oh? excuse me.
You'll act like you're taking
a phone call and leave.
-In this chaotic moment? Geu Rae.
-Huh?
Then you go.
So, he's drinking three
shots while we drink one?
-Yes.
-Good idea.
But,
this can't last forever.
Prepare two bottles of
whiskey from the get-go.
One is real and one is black tea.
After Mr. Mun pours all of you a drink,
Geu Rae pours him one.
Mr. Kim will then change it
with a shot of black tea.
Wet towels and trashcans to throw
out the alcohol are essential here.
You act like you're drinking
it, then you spit it out.
The wet towel can't absorb too much,
so if you spit it out before
absorption, it will get messy.
The key to the trick
is the absorption.
So keep many dry towels
similar to the wet one.
You need to put empty
glasses in your pocket.
To change them with full shots.
You need to act drunk
and remember to call each other
every 30 minutes to rotate seats.
Boilermakers are seven times
as strong as normal alcohol.
Learn how to make them,
it'll make things exciting.
See, now you get it?
Why I kept saying we needed her?
I've tasted 40 types of alcohol
including loyal alchohol,
rainbow alcohol, gold liquor,
and cappuccino liquor.
Ok, Geu Rae.
Learn how to make boilermakers from him.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Learn it.
Who are you, Young Yi?
Principle?
Why are you laughing?
I feel like looking at an old
watch in an antique store.
Huh?
The word "principle."
Nowadays, college professors
who mention
"social justice" get the same response.
Mr. Oh still has it.
Or he's struggling to
keep his soul alive.
Mr. Oh?
You really won't prepare round 2?
-Mr. Oh, what if?
-No!
Get all the info you can
about Mun including receipts.
Why you, I'll do whatever it takes
to make you sign it by round 1.
Give me the revised agency list.
Stand there and
I'll tell you what to fix.
Good job, it looks fine.
Do this too.
They're contract documents.
Check for typos, any mistakes,
and make sure I can mail it
by noon tomorrow.
You heard it.
Please do it by tomorrow noon.
Huh?
Baek Ki.
What are you doing?
I came to create business.
I didn't come here to make charts,
check typos, and balance accounts.
I've done enough of those
tedious tasks as an intern.
I don't think they're
for me to do anymore.
Can't you see how other
team newbies are working?
Their names are already on the
next sales proposal, even Geu?
Sir.
How come you don't like me?
Haven't you learned anything so far?
All I've learned is patience.
I think it's time
to apply what I've learned.
Put that back on his desk.
Baek Ki.
Don't need to console me.
Why's he so angry?
Mr. Oh.
-Are you off for the day?
-Yes.
We'll have grade A
premium beef, join us.
I have Mr. Kim's credit card here.
Where's Geu Rae?
You're off for the day?
Yes.
See?
He's shocked we
might go without him.
Geez.
Their beef is so juicy?
Young Yi.
Young Yi!
Come on!
Please excuse me.
Young Yi!
Young Yi.
Geu Rae.
You didn't go for dinner?
Mr. Oh said, let's do it next time.
Sorry if it was?
He said it's not because of you.
His wife called.
Sorry, I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
It's ok.
I'll get off at the next station.
Drop it!
-You're a hypocrite, sir.
-Young Yi.
You thought I'd be grateful,
and think of you as a savior?
Please.
That's enough, Dad.
Sorry, when did you get off?
I didn't even say bye.
Bye, see you tomorrow.
Their names are already on the
next sales proposal, even Geu?
Haven't you learned anything so far?
[I'm Lee Ji Hyun at headhunting
firm, Search & Brains.
I'd like to recommend good companies
if you're thinking of changing jobs.]
Mr. Oh isn't in yet?
No.
Where is he when it's almost time?
I can't use this, I'll give it to him.
There he is.
We're all ready.
-Bring the medication.
-Yes.
[Hangover relief medication]
Let's go.
Yes.
Shall I bring some more of these?
Yeah, we'll need it when we drink.
-Bring them all.
-Ok.
Welcome.
We sent a limousine for Mr. Mun.
He'll arrive soon.
We've all been on
stand-by for two hours.
My men are? ready too.
Yes, let's do it.
He's here.
He has finally come.
Principles are laughed
at in this day and age.
How was your flight?
Good.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Mun.
I'm Oh Sang Sik of One
International Sales Team 3.
He's the guy who made Mr. Oh
bring up that old word.
I'm Kim Dong Sik.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
This way, please.
Ok.
Will Mr. Oh be able to keep
his principle as intended?
Wow.
The match was over
sooner than we thought.
Sir, I'll pour you a drink.
We had a different operation
location to work with.
We panicked even before
we could load our guns.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hold on.
Hold on?
Hello?
Mr. Oh.
The most meticulous plan in the history
of alcohol entertainment with clients,
was ruined before it even started
in front of the heaviest
drinker on earth.
Here.
Ok.
The boilermaker recipe I learned
-at the last minute was useless.
-This is a water fountain.
Wow.
Round 2!
We will party till the
break of dawn, here you go.
Ok.
Mr. Kim couldn't tell which was
whiskey and which was black tea.
Mr. Oh was still struggling to get
the contract signed by round 1.
Here's me.
We realized when the clock
hit 4:00 in the morning.
We had totally failed.
Mr. Oh's heart will
cry a river of tears all night.
Hey.
41 59//Our youngest one, right?
Geu Rae.
You can go now.
You're quick, Mr. Oh.
Ok, go home.
Wait!
What's with it?
I don't have time for this.
Please, sir!
Don't worry!
You too, don't worry.
Good job.
Where's Dong Sik?
Dong Sik.
Dong Sik!
-Dude!
-Get up...
Send Dong Sik home.
You go home too.
Get a couple of hours of sleep.
What? about you?
Dang.
Wait.
Mr. Oh failed,
but Sales Team 3 survived.
"Survived" my foot,
we were in trouble.
Big trouble!
Huh?
We're in big trouble.
How could that happen?
You're awake.
You're surprised?
How? did you?
I sent her there.
Mr. Oh.
That quenches my thirst so well.
Man.
You thought I'd do
whatever he wants?
You sent his wife?
It's all in the data.
Data research is always crucial.
The key is in the data.
In some of the economy
news on Mun Chung Gi,
they said he'd be
arriving with his wife.
I happened to see his anniversary.
[Romantist of the distribution
field, Mun Chung Gi]
It happened to be the same
day we were entertaining him.
[Wedding anniversary]
That made my blood boil for a minute.
Huh?
He was going to screw
around on his anniversary.
Ideas boiled in my
head at the same time.
Regarding the round 2
readiness you mentioned.
I'm sure I said preparations,
not readiness.
I wanted to give his poor wife
an unforgettable anniversary gift.
I met her on the morning of that day
and told her about our gift for her.
You mean "your" gift.
Then everything happened
perfectly after that.
We failed perfectly, you mean.
How could this happen?
Gosh!
What guy would want to be
entertained by his wife?
So you chose your principle
instead of the contract.
What will you tell Mr. Kim?
Dang, you're crazy!
Are you insane?
Sang Sik, you might as
well jump off a bridge!
As long as I'm in headquarters,
you will never get more people!
I told you before.
Repair the damages made
by all the sales headquarters!
All of it!
Everything!
Gosh.
Hello?
Dad!
My baby, future tradingman!
Dad, are you coming home early tonight?
Yeah.
Then buy some spicy chicken on the way.
Just spicy chicken?
What about fried chicken?
Then make it fried.
Only fried chicken?
What about spicy?
Then buy half and half.
Then shall I buy two half-half chickens?
Then you can just buy
one spicy and one fried.
Right.
You're dumb, Dad!
Hey, don't call your dad dumb.
I love you, Dad.
Bye!
I love you.
Oh, gosh.
I feel so down.
Blood, dang?
Dad,
Buy one half-half and one spicy.
From your No. 1 son.
You were here?
You weren't picking up your phone.
You had a nosebleed?
Yeah.
Are you ok?
I dozed off for a few minutes.
Now I'm bleeding.
You dozed off?
I don?t know if
I dozed off or fainted.
Maybe my blood pressure
rose because of fatigue.
I'm ok.
Don't tell Dong Sik anything.
I don't want to hear him nag.
Young Yi.
Yes.
Why are you looking
at the EU-ETS data?
[EU-ETS: European Union
Emission Trading Scheme]
What are you trying to do?
What do you take me for?
I told you to butt out.
You're trying to get on my nerves?
You're saying it's yours
and you have the right?
That's not it, sir.
If you can't drop it?
Fine, take it.
I don't have to do it.
Put your frigging name in
the center and succeed!
Young Yi.
Suk Yool.
Keep your chin up.
Everyone knows losers act like that.
Guys can be the biggest losers.
More so around talented women.
Be strong since you're not at fault.
When you pulled off the
2-year-old item as an intern,
rumors of your legendary
talent spread everywhere.
Go back to that Young Yi.
Keep your chin up and be proud.
Be strong.
That's more like you.
What?
I'll do as you said.
As you said, I'll keep out of it.
I'll run your errands
while you're on that item.
What?
Send us your resume by midnight.
Baek Ki.
Is the document I asked for ready?
I'll wrap it up so you
can have it by tomorrow.
Baek Ki.
I won't stop you if you want to quit.
Steel is a conservative business.
A single item changes gradually,
adjusting to the business market
over a long term.
So for our team members,
rather than someone who is eloquent
and focused on instant results,
we need someone with basic skills
who can look far into the horizon.
So,
are you telling me you've
taught me basic skills so far?
Then I've certainly been mistreated.
I've learned the basics in school,
as an intern, and work training.
Teaching me the basics
is just an excuse.
I think you just don?t like me.
See you tomorrow.
I want to hear it this time.
How come you don't like me?
Baek Ki.
It's not a matter of
liking someone or not.
I don't even know you that well.
Then what is it?
Don't you remember
the first thing you did
after you were assigned to the team?
Sir.
I developed a profitable
idea for the Steel team.
Are you talking about the
business item report?
I think training includes the time
to check what one has learned.
There's a big pile of files
for a newbie to learn, but you
gave me a business report
as soon as you came.
Before you even read
the Steel item files.
If you try to stand out from the crowd,
you become hasty.
If the basic skills are so important,
why didn't you tell me from the start?
I gave you many chances
to see your own
mistakes.
I don't know about others,
but that's my style.
Chances?
You call making graphs and
checking typos "chances?"
Can't I learn more by working
together with the team?
You have a long way to go.
[Send]
[Your email has been sent]
You're off for the day?
Yes.
Bye.
I decided to take your advice.
Huh?
I decided to give in as you said.
I realized what beats a strong spear
is not a stronger spear or a shield.
You found your solution
and I found mine.
Shouldn't you drink ginseng
instead of onion juice?
She'll buy it for me next month
after kids.
Give it to me.
Why are you sweating so much?
It's weird.
Shouldn't you go see a doctor?
I'm just hot.
I'll get some rest.
Sure.
This won't do.
I'll go get some air, Dong Sik.
-Yes.
-Answer any calls for me.
Yes, sir.
What's wrong with me?
Where on earth is Mr. Oh?
He went out for some air
because he was dizzy.
He's not picking up his phone.
Dizzy?
He must've overworked himself.
Any other symptoms
besides dizziness?
Other symptoms?
Like what?
Your forties are risky.
One of my friends worked like a dog
similar to him and had a stroke.
Come on, a stroke in your forties?
One actually collapsed due
to high blood pressure.
And died.
Come on.
He fainted yesterday.
He had a nosebleed too.
What?
Why are you saying that now?
He still won't pick up?
No, although it's ringing.
I hope he didn't collapse somewhere.
I'm sorry.
Call him!
Keep calling him!
I'm ok, hurry up!
Please leave a message?
Where on earth are you, Mr. Oh?
Where is everyone?
Looking for Mr. Oh.
He went for a break
and hasn?t returned.
He should've told us where he went.
He must be feeling under the
weather and stressed out.
Under the weather?
Is it serious?
I heard he fainted and had
a nosebleed yesterday.
I hope he didn't collapse somewhere.
Then why are you standing here?
-Get your team to look for him too!
-Yes.
Mr. Hwang, Mr. Jang?
What time is it?
Missed some calls?
Oh, Mr. Kim too.
Hi.
Mr. Oh!
Mr. Kim.
What's with you?
Why won't you get
another health checkup?
Uh?
You know it's reflected
in the performance.
Don't you know I have no choice
if your form isn't filled in?
I'm sorry.
How old is your eldest?
He's in 6th grade now.
I've been to your kids' first birthdays.
With work here, I can't tell you
to spend time with your family.
But a dad should
take care of his health!
You need to include yourself
in that, you know!
Get another checkup and find
a big Middle East item next.
I'll support you this time.
Thank you, sir.
Wait.
Take this.
I bought dried eels for buyers.
Take it.
It's ok.
Come on.
Take it.
Take it!
It's heavy.
Thank you, sir.
Hello.
Yes.
Huh?
Mr. Oh!
It's ok, I'm sorry.
You were so dark.
Did Mr. Kim give you that?
It's dried eel.
You want some?
It?s ok, you have all of it.
Eat it for your health.
Don't let the stamina
give you another kid.
Hey, Mr. Oh!
What on earth did you do?
Yes, Mr. Oh!
You said you didn't want to do it.
You sold your soul, didn't you?
How come he wants
a double contract?
Card?
-Card?
-You haven't returned it, right?
Go treat yourselves with beef.
Ok?
Wow.
-Yes, Mr. Oh!
-What's going on?
So the wife entertainment worked?
Mr. Mun is that romantic?
I guess he is.
Let's call it a day.
What about beef?
No, I need to eat eel.
Geu Rae.
Clear the documents about
Mr. Mun on my desk.
What about beef?
No.
Give us the card at least!
[Kang Mi Ra, Mun's Wife:
Crucial person in charge!]
Come on.
[For the wife, wedding anniversary]
So Mun's wife is the person
in charge of the company.
So you chose your principle
instead of the contract.
So you actually?
hit two birds with one stone.
It's a liberal foreign company.
There's not a lot of overtime work.
You can control the amount of your work.
They like your various experiences,
so just tell them.
Can I choose the dept. I want?
Probably.
Oh, he's too hasty.
When will we get more people?
I heard Mr. Kim would get
us a pro on the Middle East.
He will, soon.
Who's coming?
I don't know.
You need experience to be quick.
-Who do you wish would come?
-Young Yi.
She should've come to begin with.
-I'll?
-Go!
Go!
Mr. Oh.
Hello.
We're on the same team.
[Misaeng]
Target the crises in front of you.
Yes!
-What?
-Is the interview date set?
He's the legend of the
Jordan export contract.
Shouldn't be so arrogant?
He's a part of Sales Team 3 now.
We didn't learn how to express
our feelings in school.
They're not dating, are they?
What do you think?
-I don't know.
-Oh!
You're the pretty face of our place.
What did you do to spread
those dirty rumors?
I'm going to quit.