Not Yet Alive
You only think about
what you think is right.
Everything else doesn't
go however you want it to.
This is a surprise.
You didn't like that nice suit
since it becomes wrinkly easily.
Yeah, just go classy today since
you need all the luck you can have.
Order good food and take a taxi there.
See you later.
Yeah?
Good thinking.
Hi.
Is Mr. Choi in?
Come in.
[Misaeng]
Welcome.
Sit down.
[Episode 18]
Your concerns are leading to results.
It's a good thing it didn't
lead to disappointment.
Poshin joined the national
solar energy business recently.
So the variable isn't reflected
in the solar panel business.
So reflect that
and have your team
show what you've got.
Yes, sir.
It's been a long time since
we've worked together.
It feels great.
It reminds me of the old days,
and I feel passionate about it.
Mr. Choi.
Mm-hmm.
I have a question.
Why me?
Why Sales Team 3?
Why, you ask?
I'm asking you because
you're Oh Sang Sik.
Oh Sang Sik.
Would there be any other reason?
Let's have lunch later.
Sure.
You decided to do it?
Will it be ok?
You did good.
We can hopefully move
away from the restroom.
Go over this, Geu Rae.
- Two items?
- Yeah.
This solar energy development
is a $500 mil. business
What?
$500 mil.?
How do connections work?
Connections?
Decrease our margin by
controlling the original costs
and increase Poshin's profits.
Mr. Oh.
I'd do anything you want to do.
But the fact that they might not get
the power plant business is what
you're concerned about too.
Yeah, as of now.
As of now?
There's a way to eliminate
the risk factors.
The Chinese government wants quality
solar panels and facilities.
They want a company that does much
business and can handle
a big development.
From Poshin's position,
the more solar panels they have,
the higher their chances
to get the business.
The more solar panels they have?
Hold on.
But why did the company before
have such a small scale?
Since it wasn't linked to
the power plant business.
Things changed recently.
So it depends on how we do?
So we actually have the upper
hand regarding connections.
Yeah.
Stop the nonsense.
Ask what Poshin thinks
about our plan, Dong Sik.
Find out if any quality solar panel
exporters are connected to us.
Yes.
There are some in the US and
Europe as well as here in Korea.
Ok.
Read that carefully and
support your bosses, Geu Rae.
Yes.
Don't act like the
captain like last time.
If you act like a slacking
philosopher again, I'll fire you.
Ok, go out and work.
- Yes.
But what do you mean
by "connections?"
It's better if you don't know it.
Come on, it's part of
the business manual.
Geu Rae isn't like a
pure, organic being.
They say in China, connections
come first in business.
For the Chinese, personal relationships
are more important than the law.
Especially in business.
So give me an example?
Don?t simply think of it as bribery.
Emotional bonding is the priority.
But it's definitely not Mr. Oh's style.
Then why'd he accept this business?
And Mr. Choi?
According to Mr. Chun, it's to get
away from the restroom, of course.
I hate the smell, don't you?
It's time we move away.
[Sal de Vida, Lithium
Project of Argentina]
Here.
Your dead project came back alive.
The headquarters said they want yours.
Sir.
Then what about Mr. Ma's Team 3?
Geez.
Congratulations.
Congratulations?
We're really dead now.
What will we do?
Be quiet.
We could be sent to
Sales Team 3's spot.
It stinks there.
Thank you.
It's thanks to all of you.
I'll get you all a cup of coffee.
Yeah?
It's been a long time.
What?
That, you didn't seem to
wear it for a long time.
Oh, this?
What?
What's been a long time?
Baek Ki.
What, what?
There's no water.
Change the water, Young Yi.
Making the guy always do it
is reverse discrimination.
That?s what Mr. Ha would say, right?
My legs, my legs?
Alright.
Wow.
Thank you, Baek Ki.
Your dress shirt
looks really nice.
Wait, wait.
This is
Pima cotton and this type of fabric
is made with high standards.
It's a quality shirt,
easy to dye with a smooth finish.
Psyche.
It's not that great.
Still, you must've
spent a small fortune.
But I don?t think
it's Baek Ki's style?
Geez.
Why don't you use the 16th floor
pantry instead of the 15th?
They don't have this.
You're not there, nor Young Yi.
Young Yi.
Young Yi?
Uh?
This was that expensive?
No, I bought it on sale,
so don't worry.
But you hadn't worn it,
so I thought you didn't like it.
No,
it's just a bit tight.
I worked out and lost
weight to wear it.
I'll get going.
Your coffee?
Is it high quality?
[Approval request]
Sir.
I see Chungsol is set as the supplier.
Have you reviewed it again?
Yeah, why?
Is there a problem?
The company with lots of delays?
I know.
Mr. Sung contemplated on that.
So we decided to penalize them in case
of another delay by the contract.
What?
I told you an oral contract is enough.
But he added it in the contract.
Gosh, you're so meticulous.
Is that true?
Are you my superior or something?
Am I obligated to report
such things to you?
Go check the contract.
What?
You can't believe it, right?
It upsets you to see me acknowledge
the delays and do that?
I have much more experience
than you, dude.
No matter how hard you try,
you can't beat me, you know.
What a joke.
I've seen you drink
during lunch before.
Now you don't?
I don't think it'll be
helpful for work later.
Just drink a little.
Yes, sir.
Partner management could
be the core to work.
They say it has changed, but China
is still all about connections.
It works despite the views on it.
I lived in China for five years.
All my Chinese partners
are on their own now.
They're all doing well.
I think businesses should
be based at facilities.
The fulfillment?
Those you leave at some point
after making profit
are no good anymore.
It should go for a lifetime.
You should make
a lifelong friend too.
Sang Sik.
Let's
make this happen.
Yes, sir.
And?
I knew you wouldn't
have saved my number.
Gosh.
No. eight, your number.
The number eight is
a lucky number in China.
Let's talk on the phone
like we used to.
Yeah.
Sales Team 3, Jang Geu Rae speaking.
Mr. Chun?
He's on the phone right now.
Yes.
Your number is?
I will contact you once
we find the right one.
- I'll tell him to call you.
- Thanks.
Bye.
The products of Solar Team Korea
meet Poshin's requirements,
so I got their number.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Sales Team 3, Kim Dong Sik speaking.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry, I didn't know it
was the CEO's phone number.
Oh, yes,
we'll try our best with the supply too.
Thank you.
China is proactive
just like Mr. Oh said.
Yeah, since it's a breakthrough
for Poshin too.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Find the person in charge
at the Trade Association
- and get detailed data on Poshin.
- Yes.
Have a good day, Geu Rae.
I see she keeps contacting you.
She tells me how she's doing at times.
I think she's interested in you.
No.
Be nice to her.
Maintain her pride for her.
Just reply to the text.
It's hard for me.
Ha? hard?
Wow.
It's just a nice simple reply,
don't over think it.
You know,
the day we drank together
after your blind date?
Let's go for round two!
Where shall we go?
Round two.
Geu Rae!
Where shall we go?
Let's go next time.
Ok.
Bye.
- Oh.
- See you next time.
See you
- if we see each other again.
- Yes.
But why are you following him?
I go in the same direction as him.
Bye!
Come on, you should go.
Where do you live?
Right over there.
Go now.
I'm almost home.
Ok, go home then,
I'm on my way home too.
Where do you live?
You live here?
Yes, don?t send me
any more useless texts.
Ok.
I'll send you useful texts from now on.
Bye-bye!
How'd you know my number?
I asked So Mi's mom.
It's pressuring.
Oh, it's pressuring for Captain Jang?
You don't know how lucky you are.
Mr. Kim.
Treat her well, she seemed nice.
It's not easy for
a girl to be that aggressive.
[Jang Geu Rae: Contract employee]
It's not the time for
me to be dating now.
What?
It is, of course.
If you wait around, you'll become
a crappy old bachelor like me.
Right, Mr. Chun?
Of course, there's
a time for everything.
Then is it time for me to become crap?
[Jang Geu Rae: Contract employee]
Tell me no.
What did Poshin say?
They like it as expected.
They want as much supply as possible.
I'm looking into solar panel companies.
It'll take time to go over
the US, Germany, and Korea.
Right.
But Mr. Oh?
What?
Poshin doesn?t have a middle manager.
What do you mean?
I called the number on the file,
and their CEO answered the phone.
Their CEO?
Yes.
Isn't it good if the CEO
is on the same line?
He's taking care of it himself
since it's important.
Just like Mr. Choi does it himself here.
Because it's our business.
If there are no middle
managers like us,
who will take responsibility
if there's an issue later?
What issue?
Mr. Oh.
What's wrong with you?
As soon as the solar panels are
ready, approve and submit it.
I told you it's all set.
The approval is just a formality.
No olives, but onion?
A lot.
Ok.
I will be back.
- Where are you going?
- Out to buy sandwiches for snacks.
Are you ok?
Yeah.
Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Let's be prudent with work.
Excuse me?
Yes, sir.
Hello.
I'll take your order.
I'll have four sandwiches.
One without olives, lots of onion,
and heat them all, please.
Yes.
Your team team the same taste as us.
Baek Ki.
New employees will have to come
for us to leave these errands.
Your team seemed busy today.
We have urgent work to do.
- Mr. Choi?
- Yes.
Though it's weird why
Mr. Oh accepted it.
Right, he doesn't like him.
But I think that decision was
possible since it'll help the team.
I was angry and I resented him,
but I realized I needed Suk Yool and
had to acknowledge him.
Since there's a difference
you can't overcome
with just pride and stubbornness.
The leader has to think
of the team members.
For Mr. Chun, Mr. Kim, and?
Did Mr. Oh say anything else?
No.
I see.
Let's go.
- Baek Ki.
- Yes.
The schedule has changed, so
you won't have to work late.
Is that right?
Mr. Kang.
I have a question.
What is it?
What changes when a team grows?
What?
So
when the team's position
changes or size grows?
You'll need that much more manpower.
The dept. head can ask for more people.
Then
can you switch temps to full-timers?
That should be possible.
Why?
Nothing.
See you tomorrow.
Going home?
Yes, Mr. Oh.
I heard your team is working late.
Yeah, Geu Rae was complaining again?
No.
Mr. Oh.
Uh?
I heard you started a new business.
Yeah.
Uh?
I'm sure it won't happen,
but if, I mean if you need my help,
let me know.
Ok.
Hi, Dong Sik.
Yeah, it's on the desk.
It started coming off
a few days ago.
Maybe it really costs a fortune.
But it's definitely not Mr. Oh's style.
Mr. Choi?
Yes.
Though it's weird why
Mr. Oh accepted it.
But I think that decision was
possible since it'll help the team.
However, I still have this doubt
in my heart I can't get rid of.
Why?
Mr. Oh was insisting on
it like never before.
Mr. Oh?
It seemed like he decided not
to make trouble about
Poshin not having
a middle manager.
Yes.
Yes, the model?
We focused on securing
solar panels instead.
Procuring the companies went smoothly
regarding the supply,
costs, and quality too.
Poshin agreed that
the conditions were great.
Is this right, Mr. Oh?
Mr. Oh sent a contract to Poshin.
Now, only approval is left.
Everything seemed to be going smoothly.
Then something unexpected happened.
Why, these?!
What's wrong?
Connect me to Poshin's CEO.
Why me?
Why Sales Team 3?
I'm asking you because
you're Oh Sang Sik.
Oh Sang Sik.
Would there be any other reason?
Was this why?
Mr. Choi?
We need to go through an agent?
And the commission is 2.5%?
The contract we sent
didn?t say that, did it?
The CEO is saying it was
agreed upon verbally.
What?
Verbally with whom?
Mr. Choi?
Uh?
So they'll take 2.5% out of
our 3% margin?
Then our profit would
decrease to 0.5%.
We decreased the 5% margin to
3% considering the connections.
But commission and
an unnecessary agent?
The 3% was set reflecting the
connections in the original cost.
But the sudden agent and commission
from our margin could be a problem.
I have a different opinion.
It's not like the margin is zero,
and many of our businesses
have 0.5% margin.
If we were to consider the potential
growth of solar energy power plants,
I think this could be
considered connections too.
I don't think there would be a problem.
Well,
I have to say something at least.
I don't know what's going on for sure,
but I could feel disharmony.
Just like trying to squeeze
into unfitting clothes.
It felt unnatural.
I had so many questions.
What's going on?
Did you know about
the tough conditions?
The adjusted costs were already
reflected in the contract.
Now it says our margin is lower and
there will be an agent
designated by Poshin.
This is just too much.
Mr. Oh.
Just approve and drop it.
Then
you knew all about it?
The profit may be small, but the
figures are fine within the company.
Alright.
Let's say we use an agent,
but don?t you think the
2.5% commission is too much?
There's no problem!
Sir.
I don?t feel good about this business.
With the middle manager, this and all?
If something happens,
our team will die.
Come on, who's going to die?
You don't need to worry so much,
please have some faith.
You shouldn?t be on this case now.
Wrap it up and focus on the solar
energy power plant business!
That's why you're doing this anyway!
Hold the China item for now.
Will that be ok?
Record all the calls
related to China for now.
What?
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
You had contacted the resident
employee in China before, right?
Yes, Mr. Suk.
Have you talked with
him ever since then?
I thanked him before.
And what did he say?
Is he trustworthy?
I didn't think he was flaky.
Call him.
Ask him to find out what the agent
Poshin designated is like.
And whether there were other cases
where an agent was suddenly introduced
among Poshin's items.
Tell him to call me directly.
Yes, sir.
It should be taken care of quietly,
ok?
Yes, sir.
We need to go through an agent?
And the commission is 2.5%?
The CEO is saying it was
agreed upon verbally.
What?
Verbally with whom?
We decreased the 5% margin to
3% considering the connections.
But commission and
an unnecessary agent?
The 3% was set reflecting the
connections in the original cost.
But the sudden agent and commission
from our margin could be a problem.
Hold the China item for now.
Record all the calls
related to China for now.
Something's weird.
But it's definitely not Mr. Oh's style.
Then why'd he accept this business?
And it's Mr. Choi?
Mr. Choi?
Yes.
Yes, sir, thank you.
- Sir.
- Yes.
About Chungsol?
Do you know they were
sued for order delays?
Yeah, Mr. Sung gave me
the report yesterday.
You knew about it?
But you still approved?
I told you a penalty condition
for delays was added.
But a lawsuit is still not good,
so why should we work with them?
That's true.
But Mr. Sung guarantees it,
so I'm just trusting him.
What?
If a meticulous guy
has such conviction,
there must be a reason for it.
Sir, I'm back.
Hi.
Sir.
I want to buy a car.
Pick one for me.
A car?
What, you're going to buy
something this expensive?
I'll sign a contract with my bonus.
I haven't spent it yet.
You'll pay the rest in installments?
Did you have lunch?
Oh?
Hi.
See you at the garden.
Baek Ki.
What is it?
What's going on?
So, uh?
I thought the shirt was so expensive.
What?
I already found out, so
I had to do something.
It cost $50,000.
And I really bought it at an outlet,
so no worries at all.
Thank you.
Sure.
See if it's your size.
Shall I?
It fits perfectly.
Take care of the heels.
I normally don't wear heels.
What, you bought it for her?
Uh?
Good job?
I was going to buy you a pair.
Every time handsome Young Yi
wears heels, I feel uneasy.
Your right heel is shaky, right?
Why'd you observe my shoes?
I didn't observe them, your
shoes caught my attention.
Your shoes did it, not me,
your shaky shoes.
Ok, ok.
I'm glad you're here.
Let me hear your opinion.
Ok, let's say there's a company.
We buy it and sell it,
so we have the upper hand.
But we have to
serve them, we have to.
We should be on the receiving end.
And they'd been sued for
not meeting deadlines.
I'm talking about that company.
But they still go ahead
with the contract
by adding articles to it.
What is this?
You don?t know?
I don?t know.
Bribery is going on.
Bribery.
I'm sure of it.
Bribery?
Mr. Seok has called, sir.
Hi, Mr. Seok.
This is Sang Sik.
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Work is tough, isn't it?
No, sir.
The agent you asked
about is a corporation,
but there's not much
info since they're new.
I looked into Poshin,
but they never used an agent before.
If necessary, they had
one to begin with.
And the 2.5% commission is absurd.
You mean it's a lot?
Yes, it's usually 1%.
And our margin was 3%, right?
Right.
According to those in charge,
considering the quality
solar panel conditions,
and the situation where
we had helped them,
we could have highered our margin.
And it's an urgent item for Poshin too.
It's strange, right?
Ah, no.
They must have their reasons.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
New?
Our margin could've been higher than 5%
which is before reflecting connections?
So what do you think, Mr. Oh?
By any chance?
Sir, do you?
Do you think Mr. Choi
is receiving a rebate?
Mr. Oh, you should drop this case.
I understand why you want to do it, but
the team could end up being eliminated.
Mr. Oh.
Why are you hesitating?
You have another plan?
Geu Rae is on the line.
What?
Yeah.
How are things going?
What?
The new business?
What are you so worried about?
Oh, nothing.
Geu Rae.
I don't know what's on your mind,
but just do it.
Don't look back,
don?t ask any questions and?
Trust Mr. Oh
and do it.
Why should I?
You said so.
That this business is meant for
Mr. Oh to build up the team.
If that happens and he becomes
dept. head, you could
have the chance to
become a full-timer.
Geu Rae.
I don't know what you're
concerned about,
but I wish
you'd do it.
Switch to a full-timer?
Yes, this is a good opportunity.
That's why.
If I insist, the team
could get in trouble,
but if I quit,
Geu Rae could be losing
his last chance.
Mr. Oh.
There's no proof Mr. Choi
is receiving a rebate.
Please give it some more thought.
Yes, Mr. Oh.
If Geu Rae's on the line,
I want to do the best I can too.
If that happens and he becomes
dept. head, you could
have the chance to become a full-timer.
Hi.
Where are you now?
I'm on the way back.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
I'll get some air, I need
to think things through too.
Yes, sir.
Do you think Mr. Choi
is receiving a rebate?
Geu Rae is on the line.
If I insist, the team
could get in trouble,
but if I quit,
Geu Rae could be
losing his last chance.
What is it, why?
Is it because of me?
What?
All the strange circumstances
with this case?
Things you wouldn't have
ignored normally?
This time you're overlooking them.
Is it because of me?
You're so arrogant!
Please stop if it's for me.
I don?t understand what you mean!
And what do you mean,
strange circumstances?
Stop the nonsense and go work.
I couldn't understand why an agent
appeared out of nowhere on the contract,
and a commission was requested too.
I call the shots.
I'm saying this out of concern that
I might've affected your judgment.
Arrogant kid.
- Who are you to say my judgment?
- You're trying to save me.
You're
trying to make me a full-timer.
Isn't that why
you're working with people
who you normally never would?
I don't want to put the team in danger.
Please.
Don't do it.
I don't know what you're thinking!
But if you want to criticize
Mr. Choi, save your breath.
Yes, we don't get along.
But we can keep our
personal lives and work separate!
He and I both!
You think work is a joke?
I think Mr. Choi has ulterior motives.
I think he's using us.
Don't be absurd!
He's produced much greater
results than you!
Also, his contribution to this
company is a lot greater than me!
He's worked for the company
much longer than you or me!
He might hate me, but he wouldn't
hurt his team or company!
Don't worry, I'll make this work.
No one will have trouble.
I'll find a solution to
get the best results.
Mr. Oh.
Right, it's a chance to save you.
So I'll do what I can, why you ask?
If I don't do it now,
even if the chance comes next time,
I don't know if I'll feel the same way.
I told him he won't make it.
It's tougher than Eun Ji's times.
What's the use of high hopes
and irresponsible consolation?
Many people are desperate for
those words or consolation.
Still, he won't make it.
Go down.
Your job is to work.
Don?t do anything besides that.
Don't have suspicions about anything.
I can tell that you love your shoes.
Don't be so overt.
You're embarrassing me.
Well, whenever I get new shoes,
I become more careful
to walk ladylike.
Any problems with R&D?
You can ask Sang Hyun
for help if necessary.
What?
He said he has a close
friend who could help.
Young Yi.
Who is this?
I'm Young Yi's dad.
Oh, yes.
Hello.
I'm Jang Baek Ki and we
started work together.
Go ahead.
See you tomorrow.
Ok.
I called Mr. Shin.
Let's go for some rice and soup.
I want to eat rice for a change.
Don't be like that.
You're choking me.
Your mom has a cold.
Her bones hurt too with
arthritis or something.
You should see her.
You can hate me,
but don?t hate your mom.
How'd you know where I worked?
I called Mr. Shin.
I visited him recently.
Why'd you visit him?
Just to say hi, ok?
He said he met you there
and you're doing well?
He was complimenting you.
I went to thank him.
I was late, but I owed him that.
I kept myself from going because
you were dead against it.
Think about my position.
He lent me so much money, so I'd be
a guy with no manners or conscience.
So,
what brings you here?
I heard you got a new bank account.
You paid it all off?
I was going to help somehow,
but I'm sorry I couldn?t.
Don?t waste your money,
and save as much as you can.
That way, you can use
it in an emergency.
Oh, yeah.
Uh?
Wire me $500 if you can.
What should I do?
What should I do to
escape from you, Dad?
Wire it.
Shall we have a drink?
This is my dad.
Dot dot dot.
He really makes me speechless.
My dad was a soldier.
He was upset that I wasn?t born a boy.
He always said, "You
should've been born a boy."
He always told my mom, "Don't put
too much effort into the girl."
They never helped with tuition.
So here, it's "They went to school?"
I started working part-time
from high school.
Here's your pizza.
My dad quit and started
this and that business.
He got swindled and went bankrupt.
Then he took my paycheck too.
I went to college on a full scholarship.
I worked part-time and
gave him money again.
But I couldn?t get free.
I got a job before I graduated.
Yes.
At Samjung.
You know Shin Woo Hyun?
Yes.
He was my boss.
But why?
How much is your yearly pay?
How are the benefits?
Since it's a big company, you
can get a big loan, right?
I'm going to open a store.
I loaned money from
the bank to help him out.
But it didn't stop.
There was no way.
Then my dad
went to Mr. Shin
without telling me.
Mr. Shin
taught me how to live
as Ahn Young Yi.
Not a girl who's sorry
for not being a boy.
Good job.
China or Arabian buyers don?t think
the person in charge would be female.
Whenever you're in a meeting with
guys, always sit in the middle.
Yes.
The fulfillment of labor and
myself,
my future?
I started to value them.
Until I learned my dad had
borrowed money from him.
Why'd you do that?
Why didn't you ask me?
You thought I'd appreciate it?
You thought I'd thank you forever?
I didn't want such
circumstances to shake you.
Shake me?
Who?
That's what he said?
That I'd have trouble
without the money?
- Young Yi.
- Drop it!
You're a hypocrite.
You did it knowing how pitiful I'd feel.
I know you're enjoying this situation.
Young Yi!
I just yelled at him like I was crazy.
And
it was over.
After quitting Samjung,
I stayed home for about six months.
Like I was dead.
I wanted to die.
Then one day,
when I was watching
a documentary on TV,
I realized I shouldn't die like that.
What documentary was it?
I don?t know.
It was about company workers
arguing over who'd pay for lunch.
They looked pathetic.
I thought I should be among them.
I wanted to
live my life.
Did you like
Mr. Shin?
Young Yi.
Yes.
Shall we go see
a late-night horror movie?
What?
You can't watch horror.
Uh?
I suddenly felt
I could watch one.
Then let's have some red
blood soup afterwards.
That's too much for me as of yet.
Let's go.
Sure.
Don't worry, I'll make this work.
No one will have trouble.
I'll find a solution to
get the best results.
Right, it's a chance to save you.
So I'll do what I can, why you ask?
If I don't do it now,
even if the chance comes next time,
I don't know if I'll feel
the same way.
Please update the subsidiary
material shipment status.
Yes.
Last time, the factory manager
complained due to the delay.
The fabric is on time
and under process,
so don?t worry.
Yes, as long as the materials are
on time and the sooner, the better.
Thank you.
Bye.
Bribery.
I'm sure that's involved.
I'm sure of it.
Gosh, what is he thinking about now?
Did he get yelled at gain?
I don?t think it's right time for him.
Hi.
What's going on with Geu Rae?
I don't know.
Is something wrong?
How come you don't care?
Is he an outcast?
- Is something wrong?
- Baek Ki.
Something must've happened to Geu Rae,
but you don?t know, right?
What?
I don't.
What could he be so worried about?
Ok, us newbies should get
together for lunch later.
Did you hear anything about him?
No.
I think Mr. Choi has ulterior motives.
I think he's using us.
Don't be absurd!
He's produced much greater
results than you!
And his contribution to this
company is a lot greater than me!
He's worked for the company
much longer than you or me!
He might hate me, but he wouldn't
hurt his team or company!
Geu Rae.
Yes.
What are you thinking about now?
Nothing.
Yeah right.
I told you not to be a philosopher.
- Mr. Oh?
- We finished our talk last night.
Mr. Oh.
Do your work.
If you or the company has
any trouble because of me,
it's all useless.
Your intentions
to save me are more than enough, sir.
Hi, Mom.
You must be busy, I'll make it quick.
Ok.
Which dry cleaners is your tie at?
I need to get it for you.
Kim's or Lee's?
Lee's closed down.
Oh, right.
Ok, bye.
Mom.
Yeah.
I'm busy, hurry up.
Mom.
Do you want to do public services?
What?
When I took my intern test,
you complained that you
couldn't go if I passed.
Of course, I want to!
Bye.
Come home early.
Ok.
Hello?
Geu Rae.
Mr. Seok.
Hello.
Hi, where's Mr. Oh?
He's away at the moment.
You can tell me if it's urgent.
I'll give him this recording.
I contacted Poshin, and rumor has it,
if this solar panel order works out,
the power plant business
will practically take off.
Then there's no reason
for One International
to take these conditions, right?
Don't we have a supporting role so
that Poshin can obtain the business,
by securing supplies?
Right.
So I told Mr. Oh there won't be
any problem with a much bigger margin.
But Poshin is requesting the margin
we deserve as the agent's commission?
Under the name of connections.
Right.
Mr. Seok.
I have a question.
Then aren't the roles
reversed right now?
I don't know how Mr. Choi
made that judgment,
but our company actually
has the upper hand, right?
Mr. Seok.
Geu Rae!
[Misaeng]
See it to the end even if
you don't think it'll work.
We have no choice but to run now.
Did he just grab it?
I'm disappointed in Mr. Oh.
Don't say that when
you don't even know!
We're from the headquarters.
We heard your team has a recording.
What is this?
In life, there are many things
you start knowing how it'll end.