Not Yet Alive
Episode 12
Let's go for it.
There's a good market with potential.
Few people will be convinced.
To be honest, they'll think we're just
being greedy for
performance results.
Don't worry about that.
Just focus on the work.
Mr. Ma is on a business trip,
so just make a report ready for him.
He won't allow it.
Just focus on the matter.
I'll persuade him.
Why are you silent?
The company employees
will think it's bad.
Honestly, half of the men
under Mr. Choi are gone.
If you do this, they'll think
you're screwing him over.
Aside from the politics,
just look at the work.
Is it a reasonable business or not?
It's reasonable.
Since when were we scared to do
things because of politics here?
[Misaeng]
[Episode 12]
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
This is not right.
I see.
I understand why you thought of it,
but it's realistically difficult.
It could ruin the career
we built so far.
I'm sorry.
I won't say anything else
since Mr. Oh wants to do it.
Let's work hard.
Yes.
If you think of something
like this again,
I want you to discuss
it with me in advance.
I think I'm close enough
with you for that.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Let's work hard.
Yes.
Dong Sik.
We should find Korean companies
and Jordan local buyers first.
Yes.
The Korean ones need to be able
to secure used cars consistently.
I'll focus on big used car dealers
in Incheon, Gunsan and Busan.
Ok.
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
Classify the Korean companies by size?
No, no.
Do that with Mr. Chun.
You don't understand
financial statements yet.
You shouldn't have him
classify things yet.
Let's go over the companies
that failed the bid last time.
Yes.
Where's Mr. Chun?
Aside from the politics,
just look at the work.
Is it a reasonable business or not?
Since when were we scared to do
things because the politics here?
Why are you sending
me to Sales Team 3?
To work.
Go help them well and
help them succeed.
You know gum disease?
Excuse me?
Do you think extracting it
is better or leaving it?
What a frigging situation.
[Balance bankbook]
Please insert your bankbook.
[Balancing bankbook]
Please take your bankbook.
It's over now.
Young Yi.
Payday makes you that happy?
What?
You keep smiling.
I'm a bit disappointed.
I didn't know you loved money.
What's wrong?
I love money too.
I'll become rich.
-I'm glad to hear that.
-What?
Now you seem more human.
-Are you ok?
-Yes.
It's been loose for a few days.
It's alright.
You're a real human.
What?
Why do you keep saying that?
Let's go.
Hello.
Hi.
Do women have to wear heels?
What?
Nothing.
Baek Ki, get consortium files ready
for the headquarters meeting.
Get Samjung consortium files
ready for a meeting too.
Yes, sir.
Steel Team, Kang Hae Joon speaking.
I can't believe the psychopath
is calling me a sociopath.
I heard you can't choose your
seniors, but what is this?
It's almost half
a year since we worked.
All I did was find out
he's a psychopath.
How could my life? be like this?
You have luck with your seniors.
Should I go back to the site?
Hello, Mr. Chun.
I'm Han Suk Yool in Fabric.
I admire you, Mr. Chun.
You started with experience as a
deputy manager of the Sales Team.
You showed great teamwork and
were sent to Life Supplies
in a single year.
Promoted to manager?
Suk Yool.
Can you give us a room?
What?
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
I like the vigor of newbies,
but look around.
Listen to what others call our team.
He's not that nice either.
What's going on with Geu Rae?
Never mind?
Geez.
You know what you got ourselves into?
It's a common mistake made by newbies.
You don't see the whole picture.
You just keep going forward ignoring
the politics and emotions.
Companies, I mean organizations
are not that simple.
I'm sorry.
Make suggestions that you can take on.
Be objective.
Are you capable of
supporting this project?
It could seem like you just
want to be a follower.
I'll work harder.
Harder?
You think working hard
by yourself will do it?
If it's that simple, who
wouldn?t work hard, my friend?
A biggie.
I admire Mr. Oh.
He accepted a newbie's
idea just like that.
Sales Team 3 takes on anything
that will bring in money.
Anyway they'll see the
business to the end.
Geu Rae always does that.
You always compliment him, you know.
-Do you like him?
-What?
I'm disappointed.
You never compliment
us, right, Baek Ki?
When did I do that?
You were against Baek Ki with
Mr. Park's incident in IT.
You complimented
Geu Rae for staying
and Baek Ki for leaving, right?
That time?
Right.
With Ms. Kim in Finance, you
eventually listened to Geu Rae.
Baek Ki told you so
many times not to go,
but you just went.
Right, Baek Ki?
Mr. Ha.
I told you to just attack him.
They didn't even ask you,
with Geu Rae as an example?
The truck?
You got me in the truck
and drove like a turtle.
You always listen to Geu Rae.
Right?
Don?t you feel bad, Baek Ki?
Geu Rae?
Why do you keep talking about him?
There's much to say about him.
Who else would think of redoing
Mr. Park's Jordan business?
Could you, Baek Ki?
Hey.
What are you talking about?
Sales Team 3 is doing what?
Mr. Kim.
Dong Sik!
What's going on with you guys?
What?
Mr. Park's Jordan used car business!
So Sales Team 3 is redoing it?
We'll try it.
What?
"We'll try it"?
Hey.
How could you do it like thieves
when even we're leaving it alone?
Thieves?
Then your team can go ahead and do it.
Hey!
I'm not saying we want to do it!
We know it's a good business.
Who doesn't know that here?
That's not why we're not doing it!
We set it up and we're not doing it.
Don't you know ethics
or have a conscience?
What does ethics or a conscience
have to do with work?
Mr. Kim, you shouldn't
be like this too!
What can you expect?
He was trained under a guy
without business ethics.
Who's the one without
business ethics here?
Tell me.
You hid the B/L and
blamed it on our team.
You're mentioning business ethics?
Are you crazy, you jerk?
Dong Sik.
You think this is right?
Mr. Oh will judge that.
Just ask yourselves if you can say
that when you set aside corruption.
What, you jerk?
I can't believe this jerk!
Let go.
Let go, man!
Hey!
You think Mr. Ma will give permission?
You really think so?
What will you do if he does?
You jerk?
What are you doing?
Geu Rae.
Lift your head up.
You didn't do anything wrong.
We're trying to work here.
There are no companies to work with
among the ones that failed before.
They all lack in size
and other aspects.
Ok.
What are your thoughts, Mr. Chun?
I can't tell just by the files.
I'll have to visit them.
Ok.
How long will it take?
Five days.
Finish it within three days.
You go with him, Dong Sik.
Get rough drafts ready ASAP.
Yes.
Will it be better to divide
the districts with Mr. Chun?
One person has to drive
to work on the road.
Yes, you should work together.
-Geu Rae.
-Yes.
Apply for a vehicle.
Yes.
Make suggestions that you can take on.
Are you capable of
supporting this project?
Is Mr. Choi in?
Yes, please wait a minute.
Welcome.
You're looking good.
So, it's nice working with
Sales Team 3 again, right?
The team is redoing
Mr. Park's Jordan business.
So?
I don't know what to do.
What are you saying?
How can you say that
when the team
has decided on a good business?
Why are you asking me, buddy?
You should work as a team member.
I remember that's why I sent you.
Gosh.
Life is tough.
So tough.
Mr. Chun, I'm heading off.
I'll pick you up at your
place by 7AM tomorrow.
What are you doing?
You'll hurt your neck.
Uh,
I think I made a mistake.
I'm so embarrassed for
making such a suggestion
without being able to
take responsibility.
You're ridiculous.
You want to know what's
really embarrassing?
Suggestion?
Responsibility?
Hey!
You said, let's do this!
Did I say, let's do it?
I think I was too easy on you.
I'm sorry.
Geu Rae!
You different-quantity-and
-quality-effort guy.
From now on, you'll read this
until you know it inside and out.
Just do whatever I ask of you.
That's what a newbie should do.
You don't think you could do 100%?
Then just do 80%.
A newbie trying to do 120%
is the worst for the team.
Geez.
Where are you going?
To... get water.
Oh, Captain Jang, to get water?
Please give me
a cup too, Captain Jang.
Run, man!
What?
Why make me repeat myself?
Our team will be involved in
the Mexico coal consortium
between Samjung and
the Steel Team.
Your team, Steel and we
will have a meeting soon.
Oh, there will be competition
with Samjung for export rights.
So be ready.
Mr. Shin is in charge there, right?
I heard he's meticulous.
Yes, he's excellent.
He was chosen as the Trading Man
of the Year twice at that age.
Yes, he's amazing.
He joined Samjung as
the youngest employee.
It was shocking when he was promoted
as the youngest team leader.
He has won contracts over $0.15
bil. for 5 consecutive years.
He's the youngest head of an overseas
corporate, the best in the industry.
I heard he has a fan club.
I'm a member too.
You?
Aren't I better-looking?
She's speechless.
A consortium with the competing team
must be stressful for a newbie.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
I'm here for the upcoming case.
Long time no see, Baek Ki.
Hi.
Young Yi.
You shouldn't leave like this.
Bye.
Captain Jang.
What time is it in Jordan now?
Call Mr. Cho.
Mr. Oh.
Call him.
[Amman, Jordan]
Hello, Mr. Oh.
I heard you got promoted.
Congratulations.
Yes.
The rumors have spread here.
Just hanging in there now?
I need to find out the current status.
Can you send some data
on related companies?
Yes, sir.
But Mr. Oh?
This is surely a good business
you don't want to waste.
I'm glad you thought of doing it again.
But the issue is that rumors of
the scandal can spread widely.
I know.
I'll have headquarters work
on the Jordan government.
I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Did Mr. Kim's files come?
Yes, they'll come right
after the company visit.
Get it updated right away so we
can have a meeting when they come.
Yes.
Where did they go today?
They'll be in Gunsan.
Good-bye.
Bye.
Thank you.
It's not easy.
There's no supply complex, so
there are many small companies.
When we need a bigger size.
A big company won't want to
work with a conglomerate.
Not necessarily.
It's actually easier to procure parts,
so it's easier to package.
Let's go categorize companies
with smuggling violations.
Yeah.
There were many.
Let's do that.
Where are we going next?
-It's ok.
-I'll drive.
Just do a rough draft
and hand it over.
Geu Rae will finish it.
You think he'll do it properly?
We have to trust him.
Aren't you tired?
Shall I drive?
No, I'm ok for now.
We have enough companies now, sir.
-Yes.
-How's Jordan?
Yes, send it to my email.
You have my card?
That's great.
The costs and companies
are accurate, right?
It will be a lot of work.
Yes.
Please send the files within this week,
We need to decide within a few days.
- No time really?
- I'll call you in Seoul.
Bye.
I'll have to do it as soon as I return.
Yes.
Bye.
We have two hours before checkout.
Shall we get some sleep?
Let's do that.
Mr. Chun.
Yeah?
You don?t like this business, do you?
You don't either.
But I don't think it will fail.
I know how you feel.
You want to support Mr. Oh
so he can do what he wants.
This company is the best in Jordan.
The financial statements look good.
Good performance.
Their resale performance is good too.
Solid market too.
- You know what it means?
- I can get a rough idea.
Except for the financial statements.
How can you exclude that when
it's everything, Captain Jang?
Scan it for now.
Also, review it again from the start.
If the numbers pop,
check by category.
Yes.
The numbers have to pop.
The amount, unit, dollar
conversion have to be quick.
Geez.
You can use all the help you can get.
How can you be teaching
him like that now?
I know.
Young Yi should've come.
Geez, I wonder if Seok Ho is doing well.
Mr. Ma is coming the day
after tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
Will it work?
We'll just do our best.
Ha!
You're an ambitious boss.
Yeah, you won't die for not
passing a business item.
The problem is something else.
With the concrete-like
teamwork of your team,
you could get cracks.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'm a daredevil who only
looks for risky business.
Come like the wind?
What's with that bark?
Time for my medication.
See you.
[Audit report]
[Financial statement]
The numbers have to pop.
The amount, unit,
dollar conversion have to be quick.
It should visually pop first.
Next are the numbers.
Get yourself familiar with the form.
And continue researching the
faults and flaws of that form.
Just like the game of Go,
I'll build a structure that
is easy to read visually.
But?
did I succeed in Go?
I don't know if I can bring the rules
of a failed game to
succeed in this game.
Can I do that?
- Hello.
- Hi
Where's Mr. Oh?
He'll come back soon.
Oh, how was it?
Good.
Good job.
I'm sure you want to go home,
but I'll need a report first.
Sure.
There are many companies
that are ambitious.
Let's go.
Bring it.
Took your medication?
Yeah, hi.
Geez, they'll stay up for three nights.
Gosh, I hope they're
not wasting their time.
Geez.
Another meeting.
We're reviewing
Mr. Chun and Mr. Kim's list first.
Whether the companies are
capable of provision,
whether they have a
good financial status.
Coffee's here.
Mr. Chun.
Whether their vision matches
ours and if it's realistic.
We're reviewing it thoroughly.
I'll go ahead with it.
Captain Jang.
Is there anything else besides coffee?
Mr. Jang.
So I didn't introduce him.
He's the team leader, Captain Jang.
A short break.
Everyone's laughing, but they
have different thoughts.
The uncomfortable truth in the
uncomfortable atmosphere
is being revealed
in the awkward laughter.
Hey, Sang Sik.
Are you crazy?
Are you insane?
This?
Yeah, about that?
It's like someone choked on
a piece of steak and died,
and you were standing right
there and you gobble it up.
Must you gobble it up?
It has to be revived
even if it's not us.
Who are you to judge that?
You ruined others by digging
into internal corruption
and made teams suspect each other.
Now you want to
gobble up this business?
That?s why I hate
you, you selfish jerk.
Forget it!
Please go through our files first.
Hey.
Do you think Mr. Choi will allow this?
Why stop him?
Excuse me?
It's a good profitable
business, so why stop him?
You?re the head of a leading team,
you should have better judgment.
Mr. Choi.
Let's do it well.
You're lucky, Sang Sik.
You're under the company's
spotlight as you wished.
What?
The company will be
briefing for your proposal.
Sir?
Mr. Choi and all the executives
will be at the presentation.
It's a good chance to
be evaluated fairly.
It's not a presentation, but
simply a business item?
Simply a business item?
You really think this is simple?
What?
Now that you started it and
things are set, you're scared?
No way.
That's not you.
What?
You said you were so confident.
Get a detailed presentation
ready by this week.
This is stressful for Mr. Choi too.
If he says no, you'll
say he's being personal.
But he can't say yes
when it's not possible.
So it should be a fair evaluation.
Mr. Oh.
It's on a bigger scale, so we
should expand our size too.
Let's get our presentation
Powerpoint files ready.
- Mr. Oh?
-Mr. Oh...
I know what you want to say.
There's no time, it's too much.
Above all? I know what
Mr. Choi is thinking.
But?
So what?
You want to quit now?
No.
We can't do that.
We've come so far.
We should try at least.
Mr. Chun.
Let's do it.
Captain Jang.
We don?t need your opinion.
You need to summarize
everything we've reviewed.
The info source should be accurate.
You need to estimate the rough
prices from the companies.
Most importantly,
we need a strategy
to persuade all those people.
It'll take a month.
- You take care of the Powerpoint.
- Sure
You'll do the first draft
and presentation, right?
Right.
Mr. Chun.
Get ready and call Jordan.
Mr. Kim in charge of the Middle East
will be in a video meeting
from Jordan.
Let's start.
Our team was experiencing
a new sense of tension.
A new set-up, work has begun.
What?
The flight was delayed?
Geez, how much longer will it take?
Isn't the Samjung consortium
meeting at 5:00?
Yes.
This is just crazy.
Ok, we'll take care of the meeting,
so come straight over after work.
Bye.
- Young Yi.
- Yes.
Mr. Ha can't make it to the meeting.
He already prepared files on Samjung
export rights, so you can go in, right?
I'm not?
We have no choice.
Think of this as a tee shot
and relax, just do your best.
-I'm Shin Woo Hyun.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Jung Hee Suk of Resource Team 2.
You know Kang Hae Joon
and Jang Baek Ki, right?
Hello.
Please sit down.
This is our new employee, Ahn Young Yi.
Mr. Ha couldn?t make
it due to circumstances.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Ok, let's start the meeting.
This consortium is key in expanding
the business to resources.
Support will be given in various ways.
We got added to be involved
and from our team's point of view,
I think some contract conditions
need to be revised.
I'd like to discuss that
before we start the meeting.
It will be? very
sensitive in many ways.
I'd like to resolve things smoothly.
Young Yi.
Yes.
It's about export rights.
The share status changed after
our team became involved.
I hope you can
reconsider how we only have
the rights for the previous shares.
Samjung has an exclusive contract.
We performed explorations
and geological surveys.
Yes, Samjung performed explorations
and geological surveys,
but our Plant and Steel teams were
involved from early on
and took the planning.
I don?t think
our role was small.
The export rights were agreed upon
during the original contract.
The agreement regarding export
rights you're referring to
was before our
Resource Team came in.
Please consider that our company
is participating in the consortium
because of Samjung's
lack of technology.
We would like to secure the
Southeast Asia and
domestic markets.
Fine.
I'll consider that.
I'll tell you our Steel Team's opinion.
We'll approach this
business in two ways.
One is procuring necessary steel parts
when establishing coal mining plants.
Next is after development?
Thank you.
The next meeting will be at Samjung.
I'll see you next time.
Yes.
Good job.
-Good job.
- Good job.
Let's talk.
Shin Woo Hyun.
Mr. Shin.
Sit down.
It won't take long, I have to
go to a buyers' meeting soon.
I wouldn't have been so flustered
if you'd told me in advance.
When I saw you in the One International
lobby, I thought you might work there.
But I didn't know you'd be in Resource.
I'm sorry.
How's work?
Things going ok?
Yes.
Is it fun?
Ok, good.
It will be like today from now on also.
It's strictly business.
I don?t know.
I don?t feel comfortable
around you yet.
Young Yi.
You did a good job today.
I don?t know who trained you
but he did a good job.
Good job.
Chinese or Arabian buyers
don't expect a female buyer.
In any meeting with men,
always sit in the middle.
Yes.
Mr. Shin.
Thank you.
Young Yi.
You're still working?
Yes.
Are you taking off?
I'll get going.
Sure.
Baek Ki.
You want to go for a drink?
Why do you come home
so late these days?
There's so much work.
I cleaned up your room.
I didn't throw out everything,
so you'll be able to find things.
I said I'd do it.
She put it upside-down.
It's Oppa.
[Oppa: Older male or older brother]
You want to go for a movie?
A close friend works for the movie.
No?
Ok, let's drink next time.
It's Oppa, hi.
I have tickets for a movie premiere.
7:00.
No?
9:00?
Hold on.
Hi, sir.
I called yesterday.
I won the event tickets.
Can I get 9:00 tickets instead?
No?
Why not?
I've started working in
PR at a conglomerate.
You shouldn't do PR like that.
Yes.
Both of them, please.
A754? 8531.
7548531, thank you.
Bye.
Don't you have another one?
7548531?
Hey!
Now I know what's worst
about company life.
Having to see someone
you hate every day.
There are too many faults and lies.
He makes me so frigging mad!
But the fact that bosses
like those guys better.
And the fact that he takes
credit for everything I do.
You want to fight?
How can a newbie fight?
Shouldn?t you wait for now?
What?
You should start with
waiting for fights.
If the opponent is strong.
"Strong" my foot.
How strong could
a deputy manager be?
You don?t know how to fight.
You have to hit them first.
You went for me first too.
You just have to be ready to quit.
This is just wrong!
Are you feeling ok?
What?
Yes.
You can really drink.
It seems your team keeps
working all night.
Yes, we barely finished
our Powerpoint work.
I guess only the draft
and rehearsals are left.
Now it's going to get tough.
Yes.
Yes, now it's going to get tough.
How about giving some motion?
No, the conservative
executives won't like it.
Sales Team 3, here we go.
Mr. Oh starts his rehearsal on the
Jordan business's outline
and direction.
I will start our
business report presentation.
Your voice.
A tone higher.
Ok.
We targeted?
The presentation pages Mr. Kim
prepared for the rehearsal were
revised, deleted, and put into order.
We checked expressions and
inappropriate breathing
watching the screen.
We made a strategy to
persuade everyone.
Wait, wait.
Surrounding Middle East countries
including Saudi Arabia, Iraq?
But I can't help feeling uneasy.
?to the big market.
What could be the problem?
Let's continue after eating.
The value, Middle East countries
including Iraq, domestic market?
Why's it so hard?
What?
You said you were so confident.
Am I really confident?
See?
I knew it.
Why aren't you eating, man?
Why are you here, Mr. Oh?
You said you had lunch plans.
You have something on your mind?
You didn't look happy.
I don't think we can
persuade them with this.
You think it'll work?
You're not happy either?
No.
I'm not really happy either,
but I think we'll be alright.
We've prepared thoroughly.
You must think it's not convincing
enough in other aspects.
Like stress or pressure.
Other psychological aspects.
I wonder if that's really it.
What's he doing?
He must be really stressed out.
I'm sorry.
This is the 15th floor
of One International.
911?
We need an ambulance?
Come on.
What are you doing?
Is the season getting to you?
I'm getting coffee.
I have a new cologne,
want to smell it?
What are you doing?
Get a grip.
Yes.
Mr. Kim.
Yeah.
Last time, we were talking about work?
Yeah, you have something to tell me?
About the presentation?
What about it?
I feel uneasy about it
for some reason.
Uneasy?
Who wouldn't feel
so in this situation?
Yes, but I'm talking about
the content as well.
What about it?
Well?
I think it shows how it could
be bad for our business.
What do you mean?
Nothing, sir.
Go on.
He was just thinking out loud.
Go on!
Why do you think it shows
how it could be bad?
That's?
?because our presentation is even
more like a manual than a manual.
It's perfect and that's a problem?
Yes.
You know?
A presentation starts with
the business outline.
Since we're following that, we can't
help but sound like
we're giving excuses.
So?
So instead of following
the normal rules,
we should be radical?
Geu Rae.
That's not right.
Be radical?
Yes, so?
When you look at a map
I would say thinking
north goes up is a habit.
Wouldn't earth actually not
have an upside or down?
So?
Australia is down here.
If you go like this?
it can be in the middle.
You can see Australia well.
If you put it back to normal
you can't see it well.
Geu Rae.
That's?
Starting with the
outline is a precedent.
If we focus too much
on precedents,
what's important might
not shine through.
Yes.
That might be it.
I kept feeling uneasy too.
Mr. Oh.
I don't know what he
means by being radical,
but if you're thinking
of changing the content,
I'm against it.
You know, we really
don't have time to revise it.
Mr. Oh, I agree with Mr. Kim.
I think we should choose and focus,
not be radical now.
I understand what Mr. Oh
and Geu Rae are saying.
I do.
But I don't think it's problematic
to bring in a totally new alternative.
Geu Rae.
Go organize old reports.
Yes.
You agree you must be convinced
to convince others, right?
I'm not convinced to begin with,
so it sounds like
excuses as he said!
The audience will catch on.
Do you remember the folder
structure made by Geu Rae?
We were trying to think
within the structure,
but he didn't even think about it.
He just focused on the goal.
Instead of the team's existence,
cracks or saving face,
just focus on the goal
of making this happen.
Whether we can take this road
or not.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
Geu Rae.
Come in.
Make the situation in your
head into a Powerpoint file.
I'll give the presentation.
Show your picture.
Give it over by tomorrow morning.
We need time to revise it.
Mr. Kim, I?
Write out parts you think
will take time by computer.
This is absurd.
Sir.
What happened to Mr. Oh?
It's not the Mr. Oh Sang Sik I knew.
He didn't lack judgment like that.
He hasn't changed.
What about you, Dong Sik?
You have to leave this
team to succeed.
- Sir.
- You know?
What are you talking about so seriously?
Your team must be so busy.
Is the presentation two days later?
Yes, sir.
I came to get some air
and it's quiet out here.
When you're sitting at
your desk all day,
you don't know when seasons change.
When you grow older, you feel
sad about losing the seasons.
See you later.
[Mail has been sent.]
Yes.
[Jang Geu Rae]
Geu Rae.
Hello.
- I finished this?
- I saw it.
You should go to a sauna.
I'll tell Mr. Oh when he comes.
Yes.
Mr. Kim.
I'm sorry.
I'm not so sure.
You're not wrong and
Mr. Oh had his concern too.
I understand the situation too.
If this doesn?t work out,
I think I'll be really
mad at you, Geu Rae.
For a long time.
I'm sorry.
See you later.
Mr. Chun.
Mr. Oh.
Good morning.
Yes.
-Good morning.
-Hello.
Hi, are you revising it?
Yes.
Mr. Kim revised the presentation
file I worked on all night.
And rehearsals began.
[Amman, Jordan]
Check the satellite connection.
Mr. Cho, can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
Shall we start the screen test?
Yes, please sit in the vice
president's seat for the test.
You're working so hard.
Vice president?
Hello, sir, how are you doing?
I'm good.
Since I drink less than in Korea.
That's nice.
What color clothes will
you wear today?
I'll wear a light gray suit.
Will that be a problem?
That sounds good.
The company logo's location
doesn?t look good.
Can you move a bit?
Is that ok?
It's good.
Mr. Oh.
It's a great business.
Thanks for not abandoning it.
Sure, we'll start the rehearsal.
We revised the presentation a bit.
Revise?
Yes, please look at the new file.
If you look at the second
page, Indonesia?
Give me some water, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
After listening to Mr. Oh's
final rehearsal, I kept quiet.
I've never seen rules I learned
in training shake in reality.
After seeing the radical change,
I realized I was a part
of the change too.
And I became suspicious.
I returned to my trivial self.
-And?
-Mr. Oh.
Will that be ok?
Sir.
I've never seen this
kind of presentation.
Am I wrong, Mr. Oh?
Didn't you want to make
this business happen?
What have I done?
What are you doing, Geu Rae?
Praying?
No, sir.
Go in.
Yes.
[Misaeng]
I don't think our team's
business will work out.
Why not?
I think Mr. Oh is overdoing it.
Gosh.
That's too sad.