Not Yet Alive
I told him he can't make it.
Empty hope,
and irresponsible
consolation are useless.
There are so many who are
desperate for that
empty hope at least.
Still? he can't make it.
A road with a dead end.
It's not that.
I just want to continue working.
With everyone I've worked with.
Us,
together,
always.
There's still a whole year left
that we can walk together.
[Misaeng]
[Episode 15]
Hello!
You scared me.
What's with you?
I'll start working!
You look so energized
these days, Geu Rae.
Brew some coffee from the 15th floor.
Or you could get them from a café.
Suk Yool.
Keep your chin up.
I told you to wait.
That's all we can do.
I've been there.
- Sang Hyun.
- If we just wait?
Baek Ki.
How are you?
Good, long time no see.
Let's have a drink if
you're not busy today.
I'll be nearby.
- Uh, call me later.
- Bye.
- If we just wait?
- Give me the files.
I'll take a look before I go.
Oh, here.
Baek Ki.
"Shall" would be better
than "must" here.
It adds a polite nuance to
the sense of obligation.
But I thought we needed
a stronger "must."
Alright then.
[must (x), shall (o)]
You have a hard life too.
- If we just wait?
- There's trouble, sir.
There's a hole in the ship.
What?
I don't think it's that bad.
Yes.
We'll find out and call you back.
Bye.
What happened?
- Let's have a meeting in 20 minutes.
- Yes.
- Come with me.
- Yes, sir.
I don't know the details of the
urgent call, but it won't sink.
- Where did it happen?
- Near Vietnam.
Call the company and you ask
for updates in real time.
- Check my meeting schedule.
- Yes.
And Baek Ki, call the buyers.
- Never mind, I'll do it, just book a meeting room.
- Yes, sir.
This is Jang Baek Ki at
One International.
There's a problem with our ship.
Yes.
Yes, can you check
for any similar cases?
Thank you.
Bye.
Right around here.
These are the list of companies
- we could contact for worst case scenarios.
- Ok.
We can't send another ship there?
It's impossible due
to the product's cost.
What about using a crane?
Vietnam's sea makes conditions tough,
so let's not think about that.
What about a tugboat?
You think tugboats just
fall from the sky?
Everything will sink by
the time we send them!
What's going on?
Steel is in trouble.
There's a hole in the
ship they sent to Aquaba.
What's going on?
- Hello.
- Hi.
There's a hole in the ship?
Yes.
Mr. Kim.
There was ship trouble last year with
Sales, how was it taken care of it?
They didn't depart long ago, so the
products were loaded on a different ship.
Yeah?
Gosh, this is bad.
Let's go.
Can't you fill in the hole?
Geu Rae.
- Are you kidding?
- Yes.
You can fill it in.
Why take him so seriously?
No, I think it's good advice.
Yeah?
Let's go, come on.
You could be blamed.
Sir.
Ok.
What about filling in the hole?
What?
Is that possible?
If it's just a small
crack, it'll be possible.
Well?
Let's send divers and
check if it's a crack.
We can have welders stand
by at nearby ports.
- Ok, let's do it.
- Yes.
Call a nearby branch and
ask them to get welders.
Yes.
Kang Hae Joon, speaking.
Sir, this is Jang Baek
Ki at One International.
We'll need welders and divers for?
Geu Rae.
Yes.
- Did you finish the weekly report?
- Yes.
Yes.
Did you check the Mongolia contract?
The Japan rice wine B/L draft?
The rice wine B/L draft.
Why are you working so hard
when you finished everything?
You told us to get the
next business item ready.
I'm working on one too.
- You'll do it alone?
- Yes.
You've never done an item alone.
Then maybe I shouldn't?
No, go ahead.
Yes.
Thank you.
Mr. Yoo.
I've uploaded the Norway mineral
case in the shared folder.
Ok.
Print out a copy for me too.
Yes, sir.
[Mom]
I'll call you back soon.
What?
What can we do?
I couldn't dissuade your dad again.
Young Yi.
What do you mean what we should do?
I'm sorry.
What does dad's business and taking the
early rent deposit have to do with me?
Mom.
I'm barely sane now.
You know how I've lived for the past
half-year after he borrowed money.
You told me to live my life.
The landlord said we can pay monthly.
I just ask you for
the security deposit.
- I can?
- Mom!
We don't have anywhere to go now.
I don't have money.
I barely paid off the debt.
I can barely breathe now!
It's barely over now!
I can't do it.
Mr. Oh.
Did you want something from me?
Nope.
Oh, OK.
Steel team.
Hello.
I heard there was
trouble, are things ok?
Yes, thanks to Geu Rae.
What did he do?
Fortunately it's a small crack
and we can fill it in as he said.
So we're resolving the issue now.
That's not thanks to Geu
Rae, but all the workers.
He just happened to think of an idea.
So that means he's really competent.
Some people know how to
resolve issues like him.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
- See you later.
- See you later, sir.
One International, Jang Baek?
Yes, sir.
I'm glad to hear that.
We will receive a call as
soon as the ship is repaired.
- That's the status and additional costs.
- Thank you.
Mr. Han said the first
filling is complete.
And the divers are on
stand by as you asked for.
I think if there's another crack, we
can repeat welding with it anchored.
I'll secure an area just in case.
Ok.
That was so stressful.
What would we have
done without Geu Rae?
Geez.
Hello.
Hi, Geu Rae.
- Mr. Song asked me to give this to you.
- Thanks.
- Thanks for before.
- What?
Welding.
I crossed my line.
I'm sorry.
Keep up the good work.
Pardon?
Some people know how to
resolve issues like him.
Keep up the good work.
Is this yours?
If you
have time to worry about others,
you should work on your own flaws.
You shouldn't butt in
others' business too much.
Okay.
Thank you for the advice.
If you
have time to worry about others,
you should work on your own flaws.
Please, Baek Ki.
Alright.
I'll ask Auditing for you.
Thank you.
I don't deserve that.
Look!
Gone insane now?
Oh, new item, you're
clearly something else?
Gosh.
You shouldn't look at
others' stuff like that.
I should go to the field.
What?
Why?
Here,
I mean at this company,
there's nothing I can change.
Changing your boss's irrationality
isn't accepted either.
You need to wait to fight
with a stronger opponent?
Until when?
I'm most scared
about waiting until
I become a jerk like him.
I'm sure he wasn?t like
that in the beginning.
If you're not insane, why are
you smiling by yourself?
There's a distance you can't do
anything about no matter what you do.
Baek Ki?
If you get a step closer, you're
two steps further the next day.
He's always like that.
Right.
[Oh Bong Ja Salon]
What?
That Geu Rae?
He was a disaster.
Life is so unfair.
He got in, passed tests,
and fired people
he didn?t like all through
connections.
He got an item through connections too?
That's not really true, Sang Hyun.
My gosh?
Slow down.
People like me is disadvantaged
because of ditchers like him!
Why do you think I failed?
Ok, let's say it might
not have been me.
Still,
one of us were sacrificed for his spot.
He did a good job with the presentation.
Yeah, right.
Stammering and selling those
absurd dirty slippers?
Gosh, he made it with that.
It all proves how
strong his connections are.
I can say Suk Yool is competent,
but not that jerk.
You should be honest too.
You think Geu Rae is one of us?
I hope you don't.
He's not in our league.
"Fair opportunity" my foot.
How can we share fair
opportunities with him?
My mom spent so much on
tutors and cram schools!
She worked so hard!
This is reverse discrimination.
I should've enjoyed my life too.
I never slept before midnight
all throughout school.
Elementary school?
I went to so many cram
schools and in college?!
I studied abroad too.
But
what's this?
Huh?
How's your company?
It's just temporary.
I'll go to a conglomerate.
Baek Ki.
You know what?
In order to keep our position,
we need to work for a conglomerate.
So how's Geu Rae doing now?
This proposal has to be as
professional as possible.
I created a proposal according
to the company's manual
with professional terms suiting
the business direction and
the reasonable vision.
Well, I don't know.
I'm not sure, but it feels
different this time.
Mr. Oh said only my conviction
is important in persuading others.
I have conviction this time.
Geu Rae.
You must be confident.
No, sir.
You worked hard past office hours.
I'm sure you did well.
Well,
I just did my best.
Your best only works in school.
At work, only the results count.
Geu Rae has distinct ideas.
He sure does.
Once in a while.
What's up with him again?
Stop putting him up on a pedestal.
I'll see you later.
- I'll see you later, Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Let's see your distinct idea,
though I don't have any expectations.
As you see, the contamination
of famous tourist sites is
increasing each year.
And the future of the world's
automobile business is
also heading towards
low-emission vehicles.
We can expect environment conservation
acts in popular tourist sites including
the Eiffel Tower in Paris, Grand Canyon
in the US, and Australia's Opera House.
So the electric car rental
and sales business which will
lead to growth for the next generation
will clearly be lucrative.
That's all for my presentation.
You're not really smart at all.
What?
You said you'd bring up
a business item.
What's with all this?
You don?t even know these terms.
Why'd you use English when
you're not good at it?
What are you trying to sell?
To whom?
I have no idea what you're saying.
But it doesn't sound like an amateur.
Talk doesn't come first.
If you
have time to worry about others,
you should work on your own flaws.
Young Yi.
Did you give me the printouts?
Did you?
Young Yi!
Printouts.
What printouts?
The Norway case!
Yes, I'll request it.
What?
You said you requested
it and it came yesterday.
What?
When did I say that?
What's wrong with you?
Oh, the Norway case, sorry.
Gosh, look at that mess.
Print it out for him first.
Yes.
She's going out to print it out?
To the copier.
Why'd she become Geu Rae
all of a sudden?
You wanted printouts, right?
Yeah.
Young Yi.
Is something wrong?
No.
It seems something's wrong.
No, everything's fine.
Geu Rae must've really
wanted to do well.
He overdid it, didn't he?
Shall we just end it like that?
Shouldn't we tell him what's wrong?
Tell him what?
You've been treating
Geu Rae differently this year.
How so?
No way.
He's a good employee.
It's a shame.
It'll be hard, won't it?
Him working full-time?
It'll be hard.
Then he'll have to start preparing.
There will be a position for him where
he can use what he learned here.
The landlord said we can pay monthly.
I just ask you for
the security deposit.
I can?
We don't have anywhere to go now.
No way.
I won't do it this time.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Young Yi.
Read the third point
in the Norway contract.
Yes.
Now.
Please wait a minute.
The number?
- What are you doing?
- Yes.
Hurry up.
Why's it taking all day?
What are you doing?
- Sorry, I can't remember it.
- 2875.
Why, you guys?
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
I'm so sorry.
Dang!
It'll be hard, won't it?
Him working full-time?
It'll be hard.
Then he'll have to start preparing.
There will be a position for him where
he can use what he learned here.
All throughout my life!
You know how I've lived
because of you, Dad.
How?
How could you ask for money again?
What did I do wrong to you?
I said I'm sorry.
I'd be so grateful for the
money during these hard times.
This is really the last time.
I always wanted a son, but
have I ever treated you badly?
Daughters are children too.
Dad!
Come on, help me out one last time.
Don't ever call me again.
Young Yi, I was just?
I wonder what's wrong with her today.
It's strange.
Maybe something bad has happened.
Why worry about her?
I don?t want to, but?
You can't help it since we
work together every day.
Young Yi.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sir.
Young Yi.
Is something wrong at home?
- You've been?
- No.
Don?t worry.
Take care of your personal
affairs before you come to work!
Don't make a mess at work
so we don't have to work!
Come on.
Geez.
Don't you think you went too much?
Actually we can't even care for her.
She built a thick wall around herself.
Get away, I don't want to talk about it.
Geez.
You can't climb stairs
without a foundation.
You can't ultimately climb stairs with
success where there's no foundation.
You end up on the ground again.
Shouldn't we tell him what's wrong?
Geu Rae.
Yes?
It's $100.
Go sell anything out there.
You want a cool business, right?
Business?
Don't be fancy, it's just selling stuff.
Making a profit after
buying it cheap.
Buying good items and selling
it to people who need it.
Go find out the basics
of selling stuff.
Exclude your family.
By 7:00PM.
What a long title.
How did he do to get rejected?
He deserved it.
Hello?
How are you?
I checked the email.
But the price won't work,
so I'll tell Mr. Oh.
But I think it'll be tough.
I'll let you know after checking.
[Electric car rental and sales business
for environment conservation of popular
tourist sites by Jang Geu Rae]
Bye.
What's with me?
You want to smell my new cologne?
- It's no fun.
- Ok.
Baek Ki.
You shouldn't look at that.
I'm sorry.
I just happened to?
It's not confidential.
Geu Rae just got in trouble
for it, so it's embarrassing.
But
it's not that bad.
Why??
You tell him since you've read it.
What?
Yeah, tell me your opinion.
Yes.
I think?
?for rental businesses, specific site
selection methods should be given.
Automobile inventory handling and
depreciation strategies aren't either.
And
the part on profits is quite abstract.
Since simulation should be redone,
this proposal has to be rewritten.
$100 for Geu Rae?
Probably.
Tell him to take Baek Ki too.
What?
Why should I??
Where shall we go?
Baek Ki.
Shouldn't we decide what to buy first?
Then what should we buy?
How should I know?
Anyway let's go where we can buy items.
Yes, where?
That's what we're trying to decide.
You buy anything you want.
It's your homework, not mine.
I'll sell anything for you?
Come to that café over there.
Hello.
How are you?
Hi, Baek Ki.
It's been a while.
How's work?
Good.
How's your business going?
Come on, leasing service
is no business.
It's nothing fancy.
I just took over from my family.
We should go for a drink.
Yes.
So can I visit you today?
Why ask?
You're welcome to come anytime.
Yes.
See you later.
I wonder how Geu Rae's doing now.
I hope he learns something.
As he gets in trouble out there,
he'll learn why his report failed.
I wonder what he'll sell.
I had a hard time deciding what
to sell with this mission too.
I went to this store
and that like crazy.
$10, it's practically free!
So I thought I'd buy something
cheap that everyone will use.
[8 pairs of socks or 5
underwear for $10]
Buying something cheap and
selling a lot of them.
Yeah, that's the trap.
That's cheap.
You'd think buying something cheap
and selling a lot of them would work.
That's the trap of this mission.
Choose a nice one.
Sir, do these socks sell well?
Of course, they're less than half-price
of what you buy at markets.
And you can see how durable it is.
Look.
8 pairs of socks or
5 underwear for $10!
Sir, I'll get $100 worth.
- $100?
- Yes.
Just socks?
Just underwear?
Half half, please.
- Hi, Mr. Kim.
- Geu Rae.
How's it going?
I've just started.
Break the record for highest profit.
Buy it cheap and earn big money.
Yes.
Then will we be able to
party with that profit?
Yes.
Good luck.
He keeps saying "yes."
I hope he didn't buy
those cheap cart socks.
The full package with underwear.
I can't even drink
water in front of you.
So scary.
Did you reflect yourself well?
Will you drop it, guys?
All the newbies attack their
bosses like this at first.
I'll train him well.
Do a good job please.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Bring it.
It's the inventory status file.
Do it over.
What part wasn't done properly?
You study it or ask the noticeboard.
Answer that.
Yes, Fabric?
I'll put him on.
It's Chungsol Fabric.
Mr. Lee.
My cell was turned off.
Where?
I'll call you back now.
You're a new employee.
You can get company
loans after a year.
New employees aren't allowed yet.
Here you go.
You can withdraw up to $10,000.
Where is she all day
when we have to do this?
Norway budget?
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Yoo is doing your job!
Young Yi.
Can't you hear the phone?
Resource?
Resource Team 2
Yoo Hyung Gi speaking.
Total budget for the Norway business?
Yes, it'll be ready by today.
Don?t worry.
Yes.
Bye.
You said everything's fine.
This is fine?
Your mind's not on work
and making a mess?
What, don?t worry about it?
Young Yi.
Go have some coffee.
Hey!
You didn't hear her?
She said don?t worry about it!
Hey, Mr. Ha!
I'm sorry.
What's this?
Socks and underwear.
You said you'd sell anything I buy.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Hello.
Hi, Baek Ki.
Long time no see.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Bring us some tea.
- Sure.
Thanks.
Baek Ki.
You're looking good.
I'm Jang Geu Rae of
One International.
Nice to meet you.
Take good care of Baek Ki.
Sit down.
I'm still sorry about
the treat for getting my job.
It was over $1,000.
Come on.
I love feeding my juniors.
What is the favor you
want to ask of me?
My company wants me
to sell something.
- It's like practical training.
- What is it?
Uh?
You know?
This.
It'd be nice if you buy them high.
Thank you.
Is this your company's product?
Oh, no.
We bought it on the way here.
Where is it made by?
China OEM?
Probably so.
How much will you sell it for?
I'll give you a good deal?
Why a good deal?
Since you know me?
Or since the quality is low?
Uh?
I won't buy them.
I can buy you drinks and more.
But I won't buy these.
You know why?
Since I don't need it.
Baek Ki.
Are you sure you bought
this to sell it to me?
Then I'm disappointed.
How could you buy
something like this?
You told me to buy anything.
We'll be able to sell it
where there are many people.
Baek Ki.
Just go back if you can't do it.
As you said, it's my homework and
as you said, I have a lot of flaws.
So I have many more
desperate moments.
I have to sell this within
Mr. Oh's deadline today.
How's it going?
You can't sell
products in the subway?
Let's go, this won't work.
No.
Let's sell it here.
Geu Rae.
I said before we'll go where
there are many people.
Look.
You said we couldn't sell
it out on the streets.
We have to sell it here.
I can't sell it here.
Why not?
All the people are staring.
Let's go somewhere else, please.
There's no time.
The subway is the best.
Many people come and go,
so we'll go through?
If you're so confident,
you sell it on your own.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Don?t you... need socks?
Take a look.
Six pairs for $10.
They're very elastic and much
cheaper than the markets.
Take a look.
Please take a look.
People of all genders
and ages can wear them.
Both guys and girls can
wear them, so take a look.
Please take a look.
How much is it?
$10, sir.
They're great quality.
- For how many?
- Six pairs for $10.
It's really cheap for six pairs.
You want to feel it?
Want to see another product?
Your family can wear them together.
I don't need it.
They'll like it.
Ma'am, I'll show you some socks.
They're one size and?
I said I don't need it.
As you said, I have a lot of flaws.
So I have many more
desperate moments.
I have to sell this within
Mr. Oh's deadline today.
Six pairs for $10.
Ma'am, I'll show you some socks.
Aren't you being too greedy?
Are you jealous of someone who
struggled from the bottom?
- Here.
- Yes, would you like them?
Sorry.
- Would you like some socks?
- I don't need it.
They're made in China and
they're great quality.
Made in China?
They're made in China
with Korean quality.
You can feel the difference.
Come on.
I'm selling this and you'll
see they're different?
- How much is it?
- Oh, $10.
Six pairs for $10.
- Six pairs for $10?
- Yes.
The cute characters?
It's too expensive.
It's not expensive.
It's usually 10 pairs for $10.
You can't buy six pairs
for $10 elsewhere.
- It's okay.
- I'll give you one more.
It's okay, one more is nothing.
- I'll give you one more, only you.
- I don't need it.
- Just you.
I said I don't need it!
Geez!
Who pays $10 for subway sales?
So why'd you work so hard
without being smart?
I guess you'll have
to work hard at least.
Keep working hard.
Please wait here.
Where will you go?
I'll sell it.
- Where?
- Stay here.
Geu?
Having a memory is wonderful.
[Korea Go Institute]
But they say forgetting
is truly wonderful.
What you can forget
is no longer a wound.
I came in.
As with all games,
you realize you're not ready
the moment you start to play.
Strong resolutions and
shouts before that
are intuition signs of anxiety.
When you want to run away,
it means it's too late
or you?ve already started playing.
Captain.
Geu Rae.
How are you?
Good.
Where is he?
Go?
Why'd he come here?
Does he know anyone here?
Go?
I couldn't do it right then.
Did you see?
Geu Rae's here.
-Really?
- Really?
Yeah.
He must got a job somewhere.
He's wearing a suit.
Geu Rae?
I never thought he'd
set foot here again.
But he's here?
Yeah.
I heard you work for a trading company.
Sungwon's CEO helped me out.
Yeah.
He really liked you.
How's work?
- Good.
- That's great.
But what brings you here?
Uh?
My boss gave me a mission.
Mission?
Yes, I have to sell these.
I was wondering if
I could sell them here.
According to the rule of games,
everything goes forward.
They're underwear and socks.
Even if hell is at the end.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
You shouldn't have come here.
Because
everyone here will buy it for you
out of sympathy or encouragement.
Then you couldn't say you
pulled the mission off.
Exclude your family.
Your boss won't want
you to do this either.
Right.
Geu Rae was so good, it's a shame.
We thought he'd be
the first to become a pro.
He's much better than Pro Kim.
It's a shame.
He started at seven, right?
That's too late to become a pro.
But he became a student in a year,
he beat Lee Se Chang
in grade school and
he always excelled in
competitions especially.
He was a good student too.
When he quit high school, I saw the
teacher come and
dissuade our master.
He could've made it if it weren't
for his financial situation.
I heard he even had
part-time jobs at dawn too.
It seemed he came to ask a favor.
He must not have wanted to come.
How could you after giving up on Go?
-It must be hurt.
- It must be hurt.
Sir.
I'll get going.
Bye.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
What is it?
You couldn't sell a single pair?
I'm sorry.
If we go in, it'll be past 7PM.
Yes.
Let's go.
Suk Yool.
Working late?
Yes.
Bye.
Shall we have a cup of tea?
Hang in there.
Mr. Lee.
Can you check on previous cases
of Sales employees with GEDs?
Excuse me?
I haven't seen any so far.
Mr. Oh.
Sit down.
Your whole team seemed
to be working late.
Why aren't you having dinner with them?
I thought you were getting along,
but you're an outcast again?
Shall I trip him again?
No.
I made a mistake.
Mistake?
What mistake did you make?
It's all their fault.
It's always their fault.
I was flustered earlier.
Earlier?
Earlier when?
Everything becomes a mess
when it involves my dad.
Aren't you going home?
This kid has to come home first.
It's almost 7PM.
I heard Geu Rae and Baek Ki
went to sell items.
Yeah, hopefully they'll
sell at least one.
I don't know what it is,
but I'm sure they will.
You know Geu Rae.
Right?
Yes.
Can you just go back like this?
Geu Rae.
I have no choice.
Hey!
Are you ok?
[Sauna]
I'm so tired.
I'll go rest at the sauna nearby.
[Go Room included]
Put me on if a buyer calls.
I'll be at the sauna.
I can't go home and come back.
I'll sleep at the sauna.
Geu Rae.
I have to wear this underwear again?
If I knew I'd go to the sauna,
I would've brought a new pair from home.
Geu Rae.
- Here.
- What?
Where are you going?
Drink this.
What?
Let's sell it here.
The people who will
buy this are all here.
That's nonsense.
[Public sauna]
Geu Rae.
Are you talking about that?
I saw you in the subway.
You'll need this.
If you don't need it, give it to me.
I never said that.
[Public sauna]
[3 pairs of socks, 1 underwear $10]
Hello, everyone.
We're newbies of One International.
How do you do?
Three pairs of socks,
one underwear
are a total of $10.
$10.
No.
They are so comfortable!
You can throw them out
without any guilt!
It's better if you can wash them if
you want to wear them again!
A great price!
$10.
Only $10.
Five pairs of socks for $10!
- No guilt?
- Hello, hold on.
You'll need these socks underwear
and socks for working late.
So they must be on a mission.
Geu Rae.
[Geu Rae: "Yes" in Korean]
- We did a lot of these too.
- Oh, oh!
Did you say Geu Rae?
- Geu Rae.
- I'm Geu Rae.
Geu Rae.
Ok.
Socks from Geu Rae.
As you see?
?they stretch forever.
They wreak of alcohol.
We drank too then.
If you buy 10 bucks' worth,
we'll give you another pair of socks.
Ok.
If you buy 30 bucks' worth,
we'll give you another underwear.
They're getting down to business.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
Look.
Look here, company employees.
When you have a get-together
after working late,
when you go to the sauna,
you'll really like the
products and our idea.
Ok, ok, three pairs of socks,
One underwear at $10.
We sell the underwear in singles too.
Yes, we do!
We won?t force you.
If your socks and underwear don?t
stink, you can just go ahead.
We won?t force you.
Go ahead.
Can we check?
We'll check your socks.
I'll buy them, I'll buy them.
$10, $10.
I sold them all.
Hey, it's so late!
That's not important.
I sold them all, Mr. Oh.
Nice.
Selling them is not important.
Why isn't it important?
I worked so hard
to sell all of them.
What did you learn?
That underwear and socks should
be sold in front of saunas.
Why?
Since
knowing your market is key?
Give me a report.
What?
- Get sober!
- Yes
Even if you have to stay up all night!
So I see it tomorrow.
You're still here?
I was writing a report.
I see.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
I still
don?t think your time
is the same as mine.
Still
I'll see you tomorrow.
[Misaeng]
Born for the site!
Then you go to the site!
I feel abandoned by the site.
Why would the company invest
in someone who will leave?
Who sympathize whom?
- So?
- All sold out.
Life itself is politics, not just work.
Don?t you want to get promoted?
Work is war?
Outside is hell.
Can you help out Geu Rae?
Come to my office sometime.
To play Go.