Not Yet Alive
Mr. Oh.
Hello.
We're on the same team.
Mr. Kim.
You always seem like
the perfect worker.
I'm Jang Geu Rae.
Oh, the contract worker
with connections?
I heard you only have a GED.
You're lucky.
How did he make it?
I heard he's not even competent.
My seat?
Where is it?
It's here, right?
Whose is this?
Let's make a good team.
What are you saying?
Send another man, please.
If you can't, you don't
need to send anyone over.
Hey.
Why are you acting like a kid?
I'm saying, I need someone
to help the team.
That's Mr. Park.
You can't find anyone better nowadays.
Even when I was with Resource,
he brought in all the profits.
No one is a perfect fit.
You need to get used to each other.
Work is the priority.
Hey.
I heard you recommended Mr. Park.
Yes, isn't he talented?
What's with you?
You want me to clean up a mess?
-Mess?
-I have ears too.
I hear the rumors also.
Do you think I don't know you suffered
when you worked with him?
I just thought he was good,
but he didn't suit our team.
I think he was like that due
to my lack of leadership.
Sounds like you would even sacrifice
yourself to send him away.
GED.
Yes.
Come here.
I heard you never went to college.
A rags-to-riches story, isn't it?
Interesting.
How did you pull off the
entrance presentation?
Mr. Kim, did you give out
the tasks in advance?
You won't know how to do anything.
You're pretty, so you can
be the face of our place.
Looks are key to sales positions.
So keep your chin up.
You have a girlfriend, don't you?
Show me her picture.
Come on.
You can get familiar later,
get organized first.
Mr. Oh.
Pay me some respect in
front of the subordinates.
Save me some face here.
What did they call you before?
Of course?
How did you address Mr. Park
when he was in your team?
Ok.
I don?t think I was out of line.
Sure, sure.
You didn't have to check that.
Why are you standing there?
I'm sorry.
Why were you just standing there?
Huh?
Yeah, how could you
possibly put up with him?
Why did they send Mr.
Park of all people?
We're in big trouble.
[Misaeng]
Geu Rae.
[Episode 9]
Get the meeting files ready.
These are the meeting files.
Those are the Middle East items.
See if there's anything good.
What's the rush?
I've only been here for three days.
I haven't gotten myself oriented yet.
When will I read all these papers?
This will just be super tight.
This one won't be worth the effort.
GED.
You did this?
Mr. Oh.
This is no good.
You need more than ambition
for the Middle East.
Then think of some plausible items.
You didn't hear me, did you?
I haven't gotten myself oriented yet.
Even with poker, when you join
mid-game,
you take your time for that.
Gosh.
You're talented.
I'll come tomorrow.
Call me if anything comes up.
Yes, sir.
Hello, this is Jang Baek Ki.
Has the interview date been set?
Yes.
It's a weekday.
No.
I can take a day off.
Bye.
Hey.
I never asked you for this.
Don't do what
I didn't even ask you to.
Dang.
Here.
Young Yi.
What are you doing?
Didn't you allow this?
As you said, I'll keep out of it.
I'll run your errands
while you're on that item.
Yeah?
Fine, go ahead.
Empty all the trash cans.
Also, wash the bins.
What, you can't do it?
No, I'll do it.
Wash everyone else's
too while you're at it.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
What's with her?
I gave her work since
she was dying for some.
What's with you, man?
You shouldn't have made her do that.
I know.
Baek Ki.
Is this how you can be a team member?
Why throw that out there?
Baek Ki.
Dang.
I mean? dang!
Let's talk.
What's going on?
They? seem? weird.
They're not dating, are they?
Answer me, Geu Rae.
I don't know.
Ok.
You and I don't deserve
this treatment here.
I don't think you need to stay
if the company doesn't want you.
-I think you should just leave too.
-Baek Ki.
Don?t ever butt in my
business like this again.
I didn't mean "give in" like this.
Letting them have their
way is your solution?
Yes.
I chose to do that.
That's not right.
Then what can I do?
What?
Tell me if you know.
Working hard doesn't work,
and I can't just do nothing.
What else can I do?
We didn't learn in school
how to approach to those
who shut you out.
Not in math or English class.
That's why.
That's why I'm just doing what I can.
I mean whatever I can.
This is my solution.
You said you found your solution.
So let's just
do our own thing on our own.
I'm going to quit.
Oh!
Suk Yool!
I sent the files to Tae Jin.
Good job.
I can trust you.
-Shall we have some coffee?
-Yes.
Get the most expensive one.
-Two caramel macchiatos, please.
-Sure.
Sir, you've passed the limit.
Huh?
Try it one more time.
It doesn't work.
Here.
Here's the coffee.
Thank you.
Here's your card.
-You've passed the limit.
-Huh?
Oh, right.
How much was it?
Oh, $9.
I'm out of cash.
It's ok.
It's on me.
Yeah?
You're the man.
Thank you.
The Canadian buyer will call
for the polyester item.
Get the list ready before then.
Canada?
He said he'd call at 11 AM their time.
That would be about midnight here.
Midnight?
Mm-hmm.
Also, get tomorrow's executives'
breakfast meeting ready too.
Breakfast?
5:30 at Kings Hotel.
5:30?
In the morning?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Also, I can't go due to a business trip.
It's weird.
My boss just loves me.
Take care of that.
Yes.
It feels like
not receiving my pay
after a part-time job.
Not a good feeling.
Hi, Suk Yool.
Geu Rae, can I see you
in the lounge for a sec?
What?
What is it?
Here me out.
Tell me what you think.
As you know,
Mr. Sung
has a great personality.
-I don't know.
-Huh?
Anyway?
It's weird.
-I think?
-Is he giving you his work?
Yeah.
You think so too?
It seems so to you too?
Hello?
-It's me.
-Who is this?
-Don't you know your boss's voice?
-Oh, Mr. Park.
Print of Resource and
Steel's EPC TF item.
[EPC: One-stop business providing
-Yes.
-Mr. Park's not here yet?
design, part, and material
procurement, construction]
No.
Where's Geu Rae?
I don't know.
He was here a minute ago.
Use your power.
Power, power.
Ok.
It didn't work.
It didn't.
Your phone's been ringing.
Shouldn't you pick up?
It's ok, dude.
Target... the crisis?
in front of you first.
Yes!
$10 each.
-Geez.
-$10 each.
That's absurd.
You hit it like that!
$10 each.
All you have is $10?
You too?
Forget it, dude.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Park.
Sure, make a lot of money.
Are you going to the sauna?
Yeah.
You want a coupon?
Hey, I'm a hotel VIP member.
I don't go to shabby bathhouses.
You're going to a hotel
in those slippers?
Are you crazy?
Hey!
What do you want me to do?
Put them down.
You should have brought a shoe horn.
Get it together.
I'll go meet an old client.
Take these back.
What are those?
Nothing.
Where's Mr. Park?
He's meeting a client.
He just came to our team, which client?
He said it's a client from Resource.
Call him, Geu Rae.
Yes.
What did they call you before?
How did you address Mr. Park
when he was in your team?
I don?t think I was out of line.
Those are the Middle East items.
See if there's anything good.
We're all working for a salary.
Why act like a hot shot?
Where is he?
He's off for the day?
He went to Pohang for business.
Yes, One International Steel.
Yes, he's on a business trip.
Who is this?
Yes.
Yes, I'll leave a memo.
Bye.
Give this to him.
The EPC TF item.
Mr. Kang's report has been reviewed,
so Steel can approve it first.
It's urgent, requiring Resource and
our approval too, so it's top priority.
Yes.
I'll tell him.
Where's Mr. Cha?
He's in Myanmar on business.
Your team needs more people too.
I hope you don't have
your mind on other things.
Pardon?
See you later.
[Myanmar EPC TF team]
Time flies by.
Time to take off already.
Where were you, Mr. Park?
Huh?
Geez, GED!
You didn?t tell him?
I told you I'd see a client.
-I?
-You meet clients at a sauna?
I can smell the mugwort.
Your sense of smell is as
keen as ever, Sang Sik.
Mr. Park.
Yes.
Call me Mr. Oh at work.
Ok.
You've become authoritative
over time.
You weren't like this before.
Don't go to saunas during work.
You're neglecting your work.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
We should work.
Halal?
Shall I work on this?
[Halal: Products prepared
as prescribed by Muslim law,
You think it's good?
Arabic term meaning
"lawful or permissible"]
Well, it's not a big item.
It's perfect for learning
about the Middle East.
I think it's ok for Sales Team 3?
Ok, then.
I can't do it alone.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes.
Give me Geu Rae.
He'll do.
He's still?
No?
Why not?
You can't do it?
I don't need great support.
I'll give him something
that only requires a GED.
You have a GED.
Aren't I right?
Mr. Park.
Mr. Oh.
If you allow it, I'll support Mr. Park.
Geu Rae.
What are you saying?
Who's higher here,
Mr. Oh or Mr. Park?
Listen to yourself talking.
Dong Sik.
Come on, don't make
this an issue, dude.
"Dude?"
Don't call me "dude," sir.
-What?
-Stop.
This team is all messed up.
Subordinates talking
back to those who are higher.
Wow.
Things are looking good.
You're close already?
Hello, Mr. Kim.
Hi.
How do you like your team?
I look forward to fantastic teamwork.
This team is important.
Work hard.
I did my best to send you here.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
-Ok.
-Sir.
Where do you go to
shoot pool nowadays?
-I sprained my wrist last time.
-Oh.
So I'm taking a break now.
Are you ok?
I'm ok.
Anyway I have high hopes.
See you later.
See you, sir.
You shouldn't screw me over like this.
He used to be a good worker.
He'll help our team as
a Middle Eastern expert.
I know.
He was the legend in the Steel team
with $120,000 Jordan export contract.
That was Steel's best achievement.
Mr. Park was amazing then.
Yeah?
He was an assistant manager
and in charge of communication
with the site workers.
He was hands down the contract pro.
That's when things started to get risky.
Let's take him.
He's a part of Sales Team 3 now.
We should accept our
members no matter what.
It's your frigging luck.
Come on.
Support him well with the
Halal item starting tomorrow.
Be patient.
You're good at that.
Being patient.
Huh?
Mr. Oh, I don't like that either.
Geu Rae.
What's with you?
Of course you can be told off
for lacking skills at work,
but personal insults
are a different issue.
You should say no if you don't like it.
People would think you have no pride.
Support him well with the
Halal item starting tomorrow.
Be patient.
You're good at that.
Being patient.
I don't like that either.
Geu Rae.
What's with you?
Of course you can be told off
for lacking skills at work,
but personal insults
are a different issue.
You should say no if you don't like it.
People would think you have no pride.
[Inspiration of attacks]
Jumping down a bridge doesn't
mean you're courageous.
I heard you only have a GED.
Ignoring a path which makes
you want to jump down a bridge,
and going your own path
requires courage too.
It's not smart to respond
immediately when there's trouble.
When you keep your cool while
your opponent doesn?t,
ultimately gives them trouble.
If you allow it, I'll support Mr. Park.
So keeping my cool is the best way
to defend myself and attack others.
Hold on!
I'm sorry.
-Hello.
Oh, it's Baek Ki.
Uh?
Baek Ki.
Huh?
What?
Uh?
You were an intern with Resource, right?
Yes.
What was Mr. Park like?
You must know since
he was in Resource?
You want me to badmouth my boss?
No.
I'm sorry if that's how you took it.
He'll be a bit
hard for you to handle.
I can imagine how he treats you,
but don't take it personally.
That will make it easier for you.
Just ignore him.
It's the Halal meat distribution list.
Already?
Wow.
You're really unqualified,
but a competent newbie.
How did you find it?
I got the contacts from another
team who did a Halal item.
I called the Arab-related companies
and asked if they could do it.
I'm impressed.
I'll be asking for easy support,
but you should know the basics.
Basics.
I mean the basics.
You should know the
trade terms for example.
You know what AS is?
We're not talking about
after-sales service.
They're conditions to provide
when a promissory note is presented.
I'm impressed.
Volume rate?
A discount on large freight.
It's a cheap rate you apply
on the transport charges
as the number of containers increase.
Knockdown.
A method of assembling and
selling a machine in parts.
The custom rate is higher than
the parts and it's economical
for nations with low labor costs,
so it's profitable for the importer.
W/M.
A standard for transport
charge calculation.
Whether to use weight or
volume is the ship company's choice.
Hello, Mr. Jang.
We consider Halal food to be
contaminated when they come into contact
with any non-Halal food.
I understand the packaging process,
but not the storage procedures.
Please provide us with the specifics
for the storage procedure
for your suggestion.
How will you reply to
that buyer's request?
You don't understand?
English is a basic skill
for a trading company.
What should we do about him?
There's no solution.
Good job.
So childish.
Arrogant jerk.
Yes, Mr. Kang.
Bye.
Baek Ki.
Mr. Kang said he can't come today.
Ok.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Mr. Kang is coming, right?
When's he coming in?
He can't come in today.
He can't?
What should I do?
What's going on?
The EPC TF budget changed.
Finance needs approval
from each team today.
Steel will need to submit it too.
Can you do it?
It's not hard.
What?
The whole report is complete,
so just summarize that into 5 pages.
Just prepare the revised
budget and timetable.
Mr. Kang won't like it.
I'll call him now.
Would you like some coffee?
I'm fine.
[Myanmar EPC TF team budget]
I'll answer it.
One International,
Jang Baek Ki speaking.
It's me.
I heard from Mr. Yu in Resource.
Can you take care of it?
Yes, sir.
Ok.
I hope you don't do a bad job
just because you're quitting.
Thanks.
[Approval request:
Approval for Mr. Kang]
[Would you like to request
an approval document?]
[Yes]
[The approval document
has been requested.]
Mr. Park.
I've completed the butchery
and certification research
according to type and nation.
Leave it there.
Hey.
Could you massage my shoulders?
It hurts so much, so
massage them, will you?
I wonder why they ache so much.
What?
You can't do it?
It's fine.
It's so soothing.
Hey.
Did you get professional training?
Why are you so good?
Wow, you can make
a living after you quit.
Mr. Oh.
He's so good.
That's enough.
Geu Rae has a lot of work to do.
It won't take long.
That's enough.
I feel good now.
Geu Rae.
Did you learn how to
massage feet too?
Massage them just a bit.
Geu Rae.
It hurts so much every
time I go like this.
Come on.
It hurts.
Wait, stop.
Mr. Kim, yes.
I'm doing good.
Yes.
Things are going well, right?
I changed my team.
Geu Rae.
Let's talk.
Is it because of your name?
Huh?
You just keep saying "yes" to
everything because that's
what "Geu Rae" means?
If you can't do it, say
"no" since it's ok.
I'm not just talking about Mr. Park.
Once you start working, your
true colors are bound to show
when you face frustrations.
But not in your case.
You always obey without
a single complaint.
It seems like you're
ready to accept anything.
Like a long-term prisoner
who was released.
Like you're struggling
to adjust to society?
That was too much.
I'm sorry,
but you're really like that.
I don't know your past.
I just know you have a GED and
haven't done anything so far.
What kind of past can make you this
cooperative and self-sacrificing?
You know?
I want to get to know you
better in the near future.
See you soon.
Get some sleep.
You worked all night and
coordinated the breakfast.
Did you get any sleep?
I'm ok, sir.
Assistant managers usually
take care of the breakfast.
Good job.
Mr. Sung must have it hard too.
Working all night and
the business trip too.
Working all night?
Why did he volunteer to go on
the unnecessary business trip?
Unnecessary business trip?
I wonder how far the Canada
polyester items are coming along.
You don't know about his item, right?
Oh, I know?
Hello, sir.
I'm back.
Are things ok, Suk Yool?
Good job.
Bring the Polyester item.
-I'll make a report now.
-Sure.
Suk Yool.
You haven't emailed the
polyester items yet.
You should have CC'ed it
to me if you're done.
You forgot?
You were doing fine.
Here you go.
I revised the whole list yesterday.
-Let's hurry with it.
-Yes, sir.
You heard him.
Let's hurry.
Mr. Sung.
Yeah.
I'd like to talk with you.
I can't do it.
What?
You can't do it?
I'm too busy to do it.
Can you please do it?
-What?
-It's your job.
The polyester case and
the breakfast too.
Suk Yool.
I'm really busy with the
next quarter's work.
I can't do your work on top of it.
What?
You can't do my work?
Listen to yourself talking.
You're saying I gave my work to you?
-In some ways?
-Hey!
New generation newbies are no good.
Can't you help your senior?
Also, I'm training you,
I didn't give you my work.
Watch what you say!
Baek Ki.
We got a reply for the
report to Finance.
Alright.
[Rejection: Kim Sun Joo]
What?
No reason for Finance to hold off on it?
Kim Sun Joo?
"No reason for Finance to hold off
on it" is the way she words it.
It means you should find
the reason yourself.
It means the basics are
missing or it's good,
but something key is missing.
That's the usual case.
I see.
I'm sure you have the basics.
Double-check what's missing.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
It means the basics are
missing or it's good,
but something key is missing.
Dang basics.
Here.
Young Yi.
Yes.
Wipe my desk too.
Yes, sir.
-Young Yi.
-Yes.
Wipe my desk too.
Yes.
-Mine too.
-Yes, sir.
You're still not ready?
Hurry, it's time for the meeting.
I'm ready.
Geez, clean that up.
Yes.
Hey.
Are the files ok?
Huh?
Yes.
I'm glad, be careful.
Young Yi, clean that up.
Yes.
Stay.
I'll bring it.
What's with us newbies?
A big pushover.
A tormented maid.
A stressed out guy.
As well as me.
Gosh.
Dang, Young Yi.
Attack them.
What did I say?
You have to be strong.
You know what they say?
It's not smart to respond
immediately when there's trou?
When you keep your cool while
your opponent doesn?t,
ultimately gives them trouble.
What's he saying?
Hello?
I'm Lee Ji Hyun at headhunting
firm, Search & Brains.
I called to confirm your
interview for tomorrow.
It was tomorrow, wasn't it?
I can make it.
No, I'll take a day off.
Bye.
Sit down.
I heard you got rejected by Finance.
Yes.
Also, you don't know why.
Right.
I just went there.
Is this it?
Yes.
You shouldn't write out
the schedule like this.
Make a chart for the approval format.
You should have calculated
the man month.
[Man month: Number of people needed
for each month in a project]
You only have the cost, and you
don't know how many people.
You need to calculate it.
This new format is mighty refreshing.
What's this new format?
Didn't you learn our
format during training?
Submit a revised version.
Finance keeps mentioning it.
I guess the smiling masked
witch is nagging them.
-Keep it up.
-Thank you.
-Refreshing.
Even Geu Rae doesn't do that.
Mr. Oh.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-See you.
-Bye.
Geu Rae.
You should go home too.
Ok, Mr. Oh.
Geu Rae.
-Young Yi.
-Getting off work?
Yes.
What a long day.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sure.
GED!
Getting off work?
Yes.
Times have changed.
You're leaving at 6 sharp.
Mr. Park, see you tomorrow.
Look at you.
Hey.
If she gets married,
she'll be like Ms. Sun.
If she doesn't, she'll be
like Ms. Kim Sun Joo, right?
See you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
It seems like you're
ready to accept anything.
Like a long-term prisoner
who was released.
Like you're struggling
to adjust to society?
A long-term prisoner
who was released.
What's wrong with that?
I'm showing everything now.
Why is the past necessary?
What?
Where are you, Mr. Kim?
The subway station.
Could you wait for me?
Why?
I have something to show you.
Oh.
This way.
Great view.
Tiring, isn't it?
It's ok.
My house.
-Here?
-Yes
Hi, Mom.
You're early.
Have dinner.
I cooked mackerel.
I made a mistake and
the tail smells fishy.
It's always smelly.
So let's decide who
will eat the tail now.
Don't think the mom
should always eat it.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
This is my team's Mr. Kim.
Hello, ma'am.
Oh.
Your boss is here.
Did you have dinner?
I'm fine, I'll leave soon.
He wanted to show me something.
Show him what?
Maybe a hidden bride or something?
Maybe not.
Why, you!
What are you up to?
What are you up to to have
such dirty rumors spreading?
Ma'am!
That was a joke!
-Joke?
-Yes.
That was a joke.
-I know.
-Yes.
-Huh?
-I was joking too.
This is what I call a real joke.
You should work on your jokes.
It's neither funny or touching.
Let's go in, Mr. Kim.
Let's eat, Mom.
I'm sorry?
Excuse me.
I'm so full.
I hope you liked it.
Oh, it was so good!
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes.
Oh?
It smells too fishy.
Yeah?
Then I'll just eat it.
I'll?
I thought your taste
could be different.
But why?
-Then enjoy your time.
-Bye.
The tail, I should've eaten that.
That's her type of joke.
She thinks it's funny,
but it's not at all.
Joke?
Yes, don't worry about it.
Joke.
Right.
-I have a question.
-Yes.
Why is your place so vacant?
I threw everything out.
A released long-term prisoner
doesn't need a lot.
I was out of line.
I'm sorry.
Remember I said sorry.
I threw out a lot, but
there's still a lot left.
What's with this Go board?
I used to play Go.
Go?
Yes.
My uncle taught me as a kid for fun.
I must have seemed to have talent.
I entered the real world.
The real world means
a world just for Go.
I only had friends in
the Go contest world.
I played Go for over 10 hours a day.
That was my teenage life.
I wanted to be a professional player.
Of course, I failed and met you.
I threw out almost all
I had except one thing.
These are the basics of
all the games I played.
Can I see?
Yes.
I wrote down reasons for
each success or failure.
Then my master would write this.
I started this since I was 11.
It reminds me of
everything at that time.
You're amazing.
Amazing.
What's this?
The circumstances of the company.
-Circumstances?
-Yes.
It's like a diary and
each day is a game of Go.
Why are there so many
pages for this day?
It's like a one-to-multiple-players
game.
Usually, you play against one player.
Sometimes a pro will play
against a bunch of amateurs.
The pro usually wins them all.
I learned one-to-multiple-player
games exist in society.
The difference is,
the amateurs have to
play against many too.
I play with you.
I play with Mr. Oh.
I play with other depts.
I also play with competitors.
One day,
I'll have to play against the company.
I'll show you a trick
when you play Go.
When amateurs play with pros,
they start off with 4 or 8 extra points.
In reality, the pros start off with
extra points instead of the amateurs.
The pros begin with 4, 8 or
a countless number of points.
What's scarier is that the
amateurs' rules don?t change.
Amateurs' rules?
You need to put in extra.
In my case especially, I can't beat?
make it maintaining the status quo.
New employees?
They have to create results although
they don't have experience.
How did you come to our company?
I have a sponsor.
It's a small firm called Seong Won.
He's the president there.
He's acquaintances with Mr. Choi.
So the executive director
pulled some strings.
That's why Mr. Oh?
Get out.
Get out, man!
You have great connections.
He probably doesn't even remember.
I never saw him personally
after I came.
Why couldn't that sponsor
help you earlier?
He did.
I worked for him right
after I got my GED.
Why did you quit?
At that time?
At that time, I didn't hide
my past as a Go player.
They were interested in it at first.
Then they became suspicious.
It led to uncomfortable conviction.
"He's inflexible because he played Go."
"That Go player always
goes by the book."
I barely worked for a year
and served in the army.
That's why you hid your past?
Because you might seem like a failure?
You're not a failure.
As a community college graduate,
it was hard for me to get a job.
After I passed and came to work,
it felt like I had simply
opened a door, not a success.
I think we keep opening doors our whole
lives instead of succeeding or failing.
Then what's success?
Wouldn't it depend on what
meaning you give to that moment?
Sometimes contracts you couldn't
seal make you feel fulfilled.
Would that mean a failure?
Sometimes you fail in Go
matches, but you feel good.
Would it be something like that?
I'm not sure but
I guess so?
Let's start anew starting tomorrow.
Thank you.
I actually have a Twitter ID.
I was never really active.
You want to join too?
Follow me.
I read somewhere not
to use SNS with bosses.
Bye.
Face?
Never mind.
Good night.
Just go back home, Geu Rae.
See you tomorrow.
Haven't you learned
anything in our team?
I think it's time for me
to apply what I've learned.
I've learned the basics in school,
as an intern, and work training.
If the basic skills are so important,
why didn't you tell me from the start?
I gave you many chances
to see your own mistakes.
Teaching me the basics
is just an excuse.
I think you just don?t like me.
Just attack them.
Regardless of hierarchy.
Hello?
Baek Ki.
Didn't you call regarding
the budget plan?
Yes.
Which part?
It was rejected because
I lacked the basics.
You didn't add
the man months, did you?
Right.
How do I add them?
It's $8,000 for the 4-month project.
Categorize it as four mid-level people.
It's usually calculated
as $4,500 per person.
Calculate it as manpower.
You forgot the piping map,
didn't you?
Piping map?
We made one before, but the
agency sent a revision.
We need to reflect that.
There's an attachment
which you can ask Ms. Shin about.
Yes, so that needs to be reflected
in the timetable and budget too?
Right.
Use the company's format including
margins like I told you before.
Let them know the percentage
difference from last time.
Baek Ki.
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
[Jang Geu Rae]
[Kim Dong Sik]
[Follow]
I don't know what is shown,
but the world is full of
those who want to be seen.
I wonder why people
confess about themselves.
In the game of Go, the parts
are determined by the whole.
The rules in the world
of Go are already set.
If the Go board's
possibilities are infinite,
if the world's possibilities
are infinite,
is it possible to win or lose?
Really?
I'm determined by this whole land.
People show themselves to be
comforted and understood.
I have to put up with this?
It's always crashing.
Dang.
I can't? work with
you anymore like this.
What?
[Misaeng]
Mr. Park is good.
I can't believe this.
-Keep an eye on your subordinates.
-Hey!
-Doesn't he work there?
-I don't know?
Let's find out what's going on.
We'll find out.
You don't know anything, man.
Let's have a proper dinner.
Baek Ki.
Please.
-Drop it.
-Geu Rae.
You jerk?