Not Yet Alive
Suk Yool.
Extremes can relate to each other.
Geu Rae.
You're early.
In order to withstand helplessness,
in order to withstand
injustice and phoniness,
Suk Yool chose to keep his mouth shut.
He was erasing time
by training how to numb himself.
He lost his smile
and we lost him.
I started to miss his
annoying chatter long ago.
But none of us could
dare to give him advice.
It's been 17 months since
we started working.
We knew clearly by now.
You had to withstand
hardships by yourself.
But I still wanted to tell him,
"Even if you lose a stone,
"the game goes on
Suk Yool."
[Misaeng]
[Episode 16]
October is already over,
get ready to hibernate. -Ms. Ha
Yes, be careful not to catch colds.
It's become cold.
You're early.
Hi, Geu Rae.
- Hello.
Day to succeed for a change, isn't it?
What was the first item?
Tourist site?
Environmental conservation?
You got in trouble for
that random report.
You've sold socks and underwear.
What was next?
- Rice?
- That was random too, right?
I don't know what
you're trying to sell.
Rice or processed rice goods?
Brown rice or health supplements?
You'll make it today.
Mr. Oh didn't say anything.
Hello, Mr. Oh.
Mr. Oh, today is the day of
destiny for Geu Rae's proposal.
Yeah?
It came?
Let's see.
[Approval]
You made it, you made it!
Finance approved of the budget.
Why'd they do that?
Congratulations, Geu Rae.
Thank you.
Refreshing!
Anyway good luck since
you got the green light.
Yes.
Good luck!
Yes, sir!
Treat us to coffee since you're in
charge of a proposal for the first time.
- Yes.
- I want Americano.
What would you like, Mr. Chun?
- Latte?
- Latte.
It's sold out.
Just buy four cups of anything.
Yes.
[Yes.]
[Business proposal]
It hasn?t been approved yet?
Don't worry, it'll pass.
I thought they'd approve it
yesterday, but it's late.
I'm sure they're still on the budget.
Since Finance is fussy
about a few categories.
I see.
[Montenegro Scented H-beam Cover Export]
Check if the steel frame
order has arrived.
Ok.
Baek Ki.
Steel frame order.
Yes?
Ms. Sun.
Hi, Young Yi.
You must've been to the sauna.
Did you work late?
I stood up all night
because of a bidding.
I forgot to take my makeup,
my face felt so tight.
You need to apply stuff at this age.
You still have great skin.
Yeah?
I never have time to get skin care.
It's still improved a lot.
Your loan interest is past
due, Ms. Ahn Young Yi.
Please check since you might
experience disadvantages
such as suspension of credit card.
Why are you sighing?
I'm fine.
Shall we go for some coffee?
- Mr. Oh.
- Hi.
Staring at the rain?
I heard the headquarters are
reviewing your team's items.
Yes.
I heard the group will expand
their businesses from next year.
Did you submit your item?
Yes.
All the newbies were
told to submit it also.
What if your proposal makes it?
I doubt it.
That would bring more worries.
What?
Do you still eat sandwiches alone?
No, we eat together too.
You know?
There's no excuse to trip him anymore
since you're not suffering like before.
But it doesn't seem
like you're tight either.
It sounds like
you must be looking
at Young Yi all day.
Of course, I haven't
given up on you yet.
I'll do my best to bring
you to my team next time.
It's my limit.
I can't really relate to
others personally,
so seniors won't feel
comfortable around me.
It's because you're a perfectionist.
Right?
Guys could have fistfights over who was
right, but make up easily at the sauna.
But what can girls do?
You never had such concerns, right?
My blood type is O.
My blood type is O too.
You know what?
Mr. Ma's blood type is O too.
What?
Hanging in there?
Yes?
Gosh.
Is the meeting over?
Yeah.
Something happened?
Gosh.
We're in trouble.
The headquarters likes
your item the best.
What?
That means trouble.
What will we do?
Yes, sir.
What do the headquarters know?
How could they ignore experience and
evaluate with a few pieces of paper?
It should be fair!
I thought of your idea too,
but I didn't proceed with it.
They think anything bold can become
ideas, items, and businesses?
Have you ever done a business before?
Mr. Ma is rooting for Resource Team 3.
He had been with them for a long time.
He must've wanted to support his team.
The structure's looking good.
- Let's check the costs with Mr. Chun.
- Yes.
Mr. Chun, look at Geu Rae's proposal.
And there's a rumor that Mr. Ma failed
with HR by a small difference.
So what would happen if headquarters
took Resource Team 2's side?
He'll think he's a real failure.
Don?t do it.
Tell them you won't do it.
She worked overnight
on it for a month?
Yes.
Give it over to Team 3.
Then what should we tell headquar?
Hey!
We're the pros.
Persuade them that our
proposal has more potential.
Yes.
Email the person in charge
saying you can't do it.
Report to me directly after you do.
Answer me.
What an arrogant one.
But they're both ideas
from teams under Mr. Ma.
He gives them approval too.
Geu Rae.
Did you forget about the Iran case?
What?
It's similar, think about it.
The team that backed him up failed.
What would happen if a female
newbie's idea is chosen?
Think of it as
Mr. Ma's long-term race.
They put so much effort into
people who back them up.
Office politics give
you a headache, right?
Avoiding isn't the answer.
I checked it.
Ours always changes, so
check the forwarded content.
Thank you.
Life itself is politics, not just work.
You got to get used to it.
That way, you can survive.
Anyway, mind your own business.
- Focus on your first business.
-Yes.
Bring in big profits and
treat us to a big dinner.
- Yes.
- Beef.
- Beef?
- Sounds good, right?
Yeah.
Regular spandex can't be dyed
in the manufacturing process,
but One International factory's
spandex is dyed in acid dyes.
Yes, I'll send you the sample.
I'll sort out the rest
and email it to you.
Yes, thank you.
Suk Yool, coffee.
Mr. Sung does me proud.
The US market isn't easy.
10,000,000 yards of sofa fabric.
The bosses showered me
with compliments.
The factory is running fine, right?
Of course, they said they
can meet the deadline.
But
I'm worried.
It'll be tough with only our factory.
Don?t worry.
Subcontractors would
decrease our profits.
It's not like we can't do it.
Nice, nice.
What would we do without you?
Hello.
You seem to be going through puberty.
You're so quiet now.
Oh.
Are you already in that phase at work?
That's early.
That usually comes after two years.
Sir.
I don't think our own factory can
do it without subcontractors.
Even if they go all-in, there
are other team's work too.
I don't think it'll be possible.
Mr. Sung said he talked
it over with the factory.
They said it's possible too.
Don?t worry.
I'm sure Mr. Sung knows
what he's doing.
Hot!
The data?
What are you doing?
What?
That's from KOTRA.
Yes.
It says in Kazakhstan,
they greet you and say their
names even if you're a stranger.
- In Kazakhstan?
- Yes.
What else?
When you shake hands,
you take a strong grip.
A strong grip?
What else?
You hug people you're close with.
Hug?
What if you love them?
- It should be on the next page.
- Next page?
But why are your ears red already?
You want a double sniff of my cologne?
Oh?
What does it say next?
Sales Team 3?
Yes, sir.
Change the person in charge?
Yes.
They said Geu Rae won't do.
Resubmit it by Mr. Chun and Mr. Kim.
What's the reason?
He's a contract employee
with less than a year to go.
It's not a long-term business.
It's a two month case and Geu Rae
can pull it off with responsibility.
He's prepared thoroughly
and no one can do?
Mr. Oh.
You really thought so?
You thought Geu Rae could
take full responsibility?
No one thinks so here.
Including the company rules.
I'll
meet with the Chief of Planning.
Chief of Planning?
Why do you keep causing trouble?
He's just a contract employee.
Just resubmit it by the others.
There have never been any
contract employees in Sales.
So there are no rules for that.
No?
Right, they're all full-timers.
If there are no rules,
couldn't we make a precedent?
Precedent?
No.
The plan is to make a rule
that it won't be allowed.
That will prevent these issues.
Issues?
Sir, this is unfair.
- Geu Rae?
- Mr. Oh.
An infrastructure is built for the
companies and buyers for a new business.
The company's conclusion is
Geu Rae, a temp, can't handle that.
Related businesses are created
even after the business ends.
It?s the company's loss if the person
in charge changes midway.
So it's absurd to exclude the person
who created the new business to
make the new infrastructure?
Geez.
I'm not getting through to you.
I'll make it simple.
Why would the company invest
in someone who'll leave?
Geu Rae's been on that
proposal for a while.
It's all useless if you're
going to ignore it!
Mr. Oh, you shouldn't
get emotional over this.
Why would the company invest
in someone who'll leave?
I think it's ok.
- Ask Mr. Chun.
- Yes, sir.
- What?
- Yes.
Ok.
How's this?
The conditions aren't bad, but?
Yes.
Let's go with Insun.
Shinsung is good, but they have
little experience and know-how.
But their conditions are the best.
- Contact them.
- Yes.
And have a meeting first?
Yes, thank you.
Sure.
Mr. Oh.
Mr. Oh, that's not fair.
It is what it is.
That's absurd!
You know how Geu Rae didn't even
get enough sleep for two months.
But we take that?
Submit it with my name?
No way!
I can't do that!
There's really any other way?
You saw how excited he was about it.
He's about to memorize all
the Kazakhstan street names.
He's about to get married
to a bride there.
How could they treat Geu Rae like this?
Since it's a company.
They can do that since it's a company.
But he worked so hard till now!
Don't act like he saved
the country or something.
He just worked for his salary.
So, will you really do that?
Tell them you won't do it.
Give it over to Team 3.
Email the person in charge
saying you can't do it.
Just do as Mr. Ma says.
That will give you the least trouble.
This is no competition no
matter how hard you try.
There's no chance of winning.
I'm not saying, just always back down.
You should know when to
fight and when to back down.
I'm not saying this
out of worry for you.
I just don't want further trouble
and Mr. Ma going insane.
What threat was that?
Nothing.
You think
bosses know everything?
They don't know diddly.
They can't make the deadline.
Wait and see.
The site won't sit and watch.
Da In.
Hello, this is Jang Baek Ki
from Steel team.
When do Finance's results regarding
our Indonesia case come in?
Regarding the pipes.
Yes, sir.
And our team's additional
proposal H-beam case?
No, no.
It's not urgent.
You're still reviewing it?
Baek Ki.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
The Youngjin report is not finished yet?
I just have to print it out.
That and
print out East Europe exports data for
the last two weeks from
the KOTRA database.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kim.
It can be provided 20%
cheaper than Japan,
but it's 20% more
expensive than Malaysia.
How should I persuade the buyer?
- This?
- Yes.
Even though it's cheap,
it won't withstand heat.
There were lots of complaints
when there were cracks, right?
Yes.
Didn't you choose them since few
products withstand 80 degrees?
Yes, but
it's a new company.
Mr. Oh...
You should go with the good conditions.
They'll build know-how with time.
Yes.
Sales Team 3 Jang Geu Rae speaking.
Hello. I see.
I'll be right down.
They brought documents.
- I'll go get them.
- Ok.
He just wants to run with others.
And they want us to break his legs?
Mr. Chun.
Don't mess with these items.
I know there was a similar business.
But the conditions and
profits are better?
Mr. Chun.
You can't work on those items.
You shouldn?t work on them.
What do you mean?
Those items were only done by the elite
employees from open recruitment.
You know what I mean?
You weren't even chosen
by open recruitment.
Thought you had learned experience
comes second when
working for Sales Team 3.
Why don't you get it?
What will you do?
Geu Rae will be so disappointed.
No way.
It's not the end of the world just
because the person in charge changed.
But it looks like the end of
the world for you, Mr. Oh.
Me?
No way.
I know.
You can't do anything this time.
This is different from Dong Sik's case.
I can't tell you to go
to Mr. Choi this time.
Just comfort him.
Uh, are you from Shinsung?
Are you in Sales Team 3?
Yes.
I'm Han Sung Jin from Shinsung.
- Yes.
- Here.
I didn't bring my card.
It's ok.
Thanks.
We're behind in our career,
but we really work hard.
The whole company has
high hopes for this.
I see.
If you give it to us, you
won't be disappointed.
We'll take a good look.
Thank you.
Sure, I appreciate it.
- Go ahead.
No, you go ahead first.
Okay, bye.
Hello.
Get in.
Yes.
You're Jang Geu Rae, right?
Sales Team 3.
Yes. I'm Jang Geu Rae
in Sales Team 3.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
You did Mr. Park's case and
the Jordan case, right?
I thought, what a daring new employee.
I wondered who it was.
You're the one related
to Youngsung's Mr. Kim.
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
But what did you do before?
You said you played Go, right?
Yes.
Ok.
Come on up someday
to play Go.
I received the additional
documents, sir.
Their executive director came himself.
Ok.
He really wanted it to work out.
The whole company has
high hopes for this.
He was sweating in this weather.
I felt sorry for him.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Who are you feeling sorry for?
What?
You can't be feeling sorry for him
in front of a head of a family.
I'm sorry.
Just focus on the papers.
Yes.
Before too.
The person in charge
should know what to do.
You prepared so much
and kept asking others.
That won't do!
I'm sorry.
[Jang Baek Ki's proposal: Pending]
Go get the fax and scan
it for Turkey, Baek Ki.
It's urgent.
[Free on Board, Cost and Freight, Sales]
Typos.
Maybe that's why it was disapproved.
- Baek Ki.
- Yes?
The fax.
Where shall I send it?
The company's not paying you
to do your business only.
What?
Is the meeting report complete?
Not yet.
How can you do any project like that?
I know you care about
your first business.
But I can't let you do that ignoring
your current work, you know why?
That's when you make
mistakes, you know
you haven't given me
the KOTRA data?
I'm sorry.
Go get the fax and scan it for Turkey,
also find the China
samples in the storage.
Yes, sir.
Are you sleeping?
What?
I thought you were sleeping
with your eyes open.
No.
Uh, I heard you submitted a new item.
Did they approve?
Not yet.
I heard the headquarters liked yours.
Is something wrong?
No.
See you later.
And Geu rae?
Never mind.
Bye.
[On my 29th Birthday,
I Decided to Die a Year Later]
As I sweated like a dog,
the miserable two hours went by.
My body was shaking terribly till
I returned to the waiting
room to get dressed.
Life is not easy for anyone.
This is Ahn Young Yi
in Resource Team 2.
Due to personal reasons,
I won't be able to?
?continue with the business item.
Thank you for the interest.
I request you to replace
it with another business.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
How have you been?
In front of the company?
Business proposal season, right?
You must be swamped.
Yes, I'm waiting for approvals.
How's your business?
Same old?
Isn't it tough since
it's not a franchise?
You know?
What?
Is something wrong?
It was fine.
I was confident about pizza.
When I was a resident employee,
and since I ate so much
on business trips.
It wasn't a name brand,
but rumors spread.
It was introduced on the Internet too.
But business hasn't been good?
We closed it after a market opened.
I used the funds I received
when I left work
and also got a big loan.
I thought I'd start a new life.
Mr. Kim, Mr. Chun.
Yes.
Mr. Oh hasn?t taken care of it yet?
Why hasn't he submitted it?
Excuse me?
Geu Rae's Kazakhstan case.
I told him to change
the person in charge.
Uh?
Mr. Oh didn't tell you?
Why won't he listen to me?
I made sure he'd understand.
He checked with Planning
too, what's he doing?
Sir?
One of you two take it.
Why are you acting so foolish?
I know you care about him.
He's a temp. It's not realistic.
What does a person in charge do?
He takes responsibility until the end.
When Mr. Oh comes in,
tell him to submit it.
Bye.
Hello.
Geu Rae.
This is insane.
Sorry, there's no room.
Ok, go ahead.
Maybe I should've hung in there then.
Go along with the politics.
Maybe I should've
at least acted like I was
lining up with the authorities.
I can't sleep
out of regret.
I'd go on 3-4 overseas
business trips a month.
The kids wanted gifts
thinking I went sightseeing.
But then
I thought I was doing
a great job as a trading man.
But it's all useless.
My wife is sacrificing so much.
I can't watch my kids grow up.
Hey.
Remember that time?
Back then, our business
partner was something else.
I kept going to their embassy every day
and asked for so much info.
It was when you were new.
We still talk about you over drinks.
Right.
So much ambition.
We'd grab them by the collar.
"Give us the data."
"I need to make a living too."
It was like war.
I gave him a good shake.
He became so obedient.
Trading men aren't ambitious
like that these days.
You can't afford it now.
The company is like
a battlefield, you said?
Don't quit until you're kicked out.
Outside?
it's hell.
I'll have to go out to the battle.
Yeah?
Then I'll
go back to hell.
- Don't see me off.
- It's ok.
Don't see me off.
We ended up drinking.
You should go back.
- Go on.
- Ok.
I should've brought you a gift.
Buy your kids a snack or something.
I'm sorry about coming empty-handed.
What is this?
Just accept it.
Take it. Bye!
Bye.
Bye!
Buy your kids a snack or something.
I need to work again.
I want to find the line I left behind.
The overseas companies will
still remember me.
I left and I was so mad back then.
But I need to work again.
I have no choice.
Help me out.
Mr. Oh.
Yeah.
What?
Uh, Geu Rae found out as
he overheard us speaking.
So?
He won't answer his calls.
The companies are calling us too.
It's ok.
It's not like the country failed.
He'll come back.
Do your work.
Yes.
One International,
Kim Dong Sik speaking.
Jang Geu Rae?
He's not at his desk right now.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Oh.
The companies are calling
the person in charge.
You're not answering them.
We can't back you up!
We're not a call center!
Come down.
I'll go to the Trade Insurance Corp.
Ok.
Mr. Chun.
Yes, sir.
How's your team these days?
Everything ok?
I'm sorry?
Geez.
Mr. Oh has a condition.
A mental condition.
He keeps at it though
he knows the results.
Age doesn't change him.
It's useless.
But I like that about him sometimes.
Sir.
Can you possibly help Geu Rae out?
I'm sorry.
Why are you dragging for half a day?
Wouldn't she need time to calm down?
She worked on it for a long time.
You.
Were you always this emotional?
Don?t act so soft just
because she's the first girl.
Hey, Mr. Jung.
Yes.
Don't you want to get promoted?
Wow.
What a gloomy day.
Young Yi.
Yes.
Can't you give up?
Then let's say I'm asking you
a favor on this.
Excuse me?
I have a promotion review.
Let's support
Mr. Ma.
But none of us could dare
to give each other advice.
It's been 17 months since
we started working.
We know clearly by now.
You have to withstand
hardships by yourself.
You were right.
My item?
My item
actually won't work out.
You really think so?
Yes.
I hadn't thought it out.
I already emailed the headquarters.
What?
The factory is boycotting?
-They're coming?
-Where is he?
I told you we can't work!
Mister.
We made it clear we can't do it.
It's just an impossible mission!
Other teams have orders too!
We've only been getting
3-4 hours of sleep a day!
You want us to work the old machines?
The manager clearly promised me
to make the deadline!
We know you forced us to do it.
You said we had no choice!
The manager promised me,
so you can go argue with him!
Hey, listen!
Old machines are still machines.
He said they work too!
You guys are so ignorant.
- What?
Ignorant?
If you don?t go back to work today,
it'll all be your faults.
When Sales makes an order,
the factory should just do it!
And it's been promised!
If you have the time
and energy to do this,
you should go back and start working!
Gosh, let's go.
We were crazy to think we
could get through to them.
Fine!
Do whatever you want!
We'll go on strike starting tomorrow!
- Let's go!
- Uh...
This is ridiculous.
How can you treat me like this?
You guys are all responsible for
the loss with the subcontractors!
Mr. Sung!
- Suk Yool, do something.
- What?
You worked as an intern
in Ulsan, right?
We can't get our work done like that.
Persuade them so they
don?t go on strike.
What can I do?
You must be able to talk to them.
You said you know people at the site.
What can he do?
Just leave it.
I'll make sure they take
responsibility if anything happens.
Yes, sir.
I'll take care of it.
Suk Yool!
Ok, go do whatever possible.
Yes.
*Ahjusshi!
[Ahjusshi: middle-aged man]
Ahjusshi!
Ahjusshi.
You can leave like this.
Let's talk comfortably over a meal.
What? Meal?
We can't eat in this situation!
Ahjusshi.
If you leave like this,
if you go on strike,
it's your loss too.
Loss?
You always valued the site,
but now you're one of them.
Now that you sit in the office, you
can just make orders to the factory?
You can't make things
happen just by forcing us!
Don't you have a dad and a family?
Come on.
Can you work with an old machine?
Ahjusshi, excuse me, boss.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
My whole family relies on me.
How would kids like you working
comfortably in the office
understand that?
I'm Suk Yool, I went
to the site last time.
I was born for the site.
Ok, then you go to the site!
Let's go.
Suk Yool.
Are you ok?
[Kazakhstan Port Water Tank Export]
- Mr. Oh.
- Yeah.
The data for the Kazakhstan
Port water tank export case.
Thanks.
Mr. Oh.
Yeah.
Please switch the Kazakhstan case's?
?person in charge.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
Did you find it?
Uh, Mr. Kang?
Ok.
Are you sure about the currency?
I'm sure I asked for Euros.
Yes, I'll revise it now.
- Baek Ki.
- Yes.
Congratulations.
What?
[Jang Baek Ki's proposal is approved]
Good job.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I mean, thank you.
I guess the person in charge was
switched for Geu Rae's case.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, sure.
Bye, Young Yi.
For generations, my family,
well, most of my relatives
are blue-collar workers.
We know the value of labor
and integrity of sweat.
We have pride in the site.
Hello?
Ahjusshi?
Ahjusshi.
You're still here.
Did it hurt a lot?
I'm ok.
You saw the man with the glove on?
He's my older brother.
He worked the machines
with me two years ago.
He lost two of his fingers
in the existing machine.
It causes an accident every year.
After the accident he went
to the team for faulty goods.
Can you work with an old machine?
My whole family relies on me.
How would kids like you working
comfortably in the office
understand that?
Suk Yool.
It's not like we're trying not to work.
I just want to protect my hand.
My family depends on it.
My son's tuition depends on it.
If I'm not well,
my family can't survive.
You said you have pride
in blue-collar workers.
You said that's your
family's background.
You should've considered this.
Geu Rae.
Yes.
Yes, Baek Ki.
I?
...am so embarrassed
of my specifications.
What's wrong with your specifications?
I know.
I found out today.
It's?
It's not your fault,
nor mine.
Nor my specifications,
nor your past?
Anyway,
I found out it's not our fault.
So?
Cheers!
Let's drink.
Long time no see.
Is your husband home?
He'll be probably drinking nearby.
It's tough, right?
It's just that my husband
can't accept the fact.
Hi.
Why'd you come to my house?
You could just call.
Don't do this.
How will you face your kids?
Keep sober.
If you're drunk, you can't do anything
when new opportunities come.
It's dangerous to be drunk
when you're successful.
But it's dangerous to be drunk
when things aren't going well.
Our team has a new employee.
He reminds me of you.
He works hard without procrastination.
But he's different from you.
He works hard but
it's natural and he's passionate,
but still rational.
The young guy's not drunk.
I'll get going.
Ok.
Mr. Kim?
He started a business after quitting.
He just watched me get kicked out.
He started with three employees,
but he's struggling without an expert.
Go see him.
Was he fired too?
You know what it's like.
Fire and getting fired.
Come on, no hatred.
There's no hatred.
Oh, the guy you mentioned
who's not drunk.
Yes.
Make sure this doesn?t happen to him.
It's not up to us.
I hope he succeeds.
That guy.
Mr. Oh.
Are you home?
Yes.
Ok.
Geu Rae.
Yes, Mr. Oh.
Don't be drunk.
Yes.
Bye.
Right,
I'm not drunk.
You were right.
But realistically we can't give
it to a contract employee.
Then you go to the site!
Let's go.
I can't be drunk.
Even if I lose a stone,
the game must go on.
I couldn?t do it.
I'll hire a subcontractor.
Suk Yool!
You were acting arrogant
and what have you done?
You couldn't send the
employees back to the site!
You shouldn't disregard the site.
We shouldn't give them work for the
old machines and just badger them.
It wasn't possible to begin with.
Mr. Sung must've known
it was impossible too.
What?
Hey.
You better choose good subcontractors.
If you can't find them by today,
the factory can't ever
meet the deadline!
Mr. Sung!
Do what you can to
find subcontractors.
If you can't,
our performances will be bad
and we'll have a huge debt.
That would mean trouble.
I'll find them.
It would've been better
to use the old machines.
Sir, this is Han Suk Yool in Fabric.
Please work as hard as you
can without the old machines.
We'll find subcontractors
and fill in what we can.
Ok, thanks.
But it won't be easy to
find subcontractors now.
We'll do our best.
Thank you.
I should grow out my hair fast.
We worked with them many times,
what do you mean bankruptcy?
What about insurance?
What are you talking about?
Oh, uh?
Give it to me.
What?
What are you talking about?
How can you not do further checks?
Then will you take responsibility
for not doing so up to now?
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
How can you do sales
on credit like that?
- Insurance?
- It's applied.
Come here!
Our company?
What?
What do you want to say?
What did you do?
Why are you working like this?
Come here!
What did you do?
Get your act together!
How can you get paid
for this kind of work?
And you!
Mr. Ma.
I just checked that our
company has insurance.
Can't you see the messed up schedule?
Can't you?
Is everything ok since
you get insurance money?
Mr. Ma.
I'll finish the phone call.
It's me.
Risky of bankruptcy?
Are you sure?
Ok, keep me posted.
Mr. Ma.
Please don't touch my,
I mean, our bodies again.
I'm glad you did that.
Stop trembling.
Thank you, sir.
No.
We were all victims.
That was something.
We're all dead now.
Dang, we're so dead.
[Solar Panel Export]
What's this?
I used to manage it.
Let's start with the reviewed ones.
Do it since it's stable.
I've discussed it with
upper management.
What are you talking about?
You really don't understand
or are you feigning ignorance?
[Personnel record]
Don't you know what I mean by,
go do it since I chose this item?
So why are you giving this to me?
You pulled off the Jordan case.
You take charge of this
too and make profits.
I'll give you my position and go up.
It's stable.
So just improve it a bit.
Did Mr. Choi give this item?
Yeah.
[Misaeng]
[Solar Panel Export]