Not Yet Alive
[Previously]
So, that's him.
- Connections…
- Maybe he went to an ivy league school.
I only have a GED.
What did you do for 26 years?
- You can't do anything.
- Hello?
- There's a call and I can't understand.
- Huh?
Sorry, no room.
I understand you have a GED.
But you speak no languages,
have no skills.
- My effort is different.
- Ok, let's see how different.
He works really hard.
We called you.
- Gone?
- They already left…
I was abandoned because
I didn't work hard.
You say I work hard?
No.
I'm out in the world because
I didn't work hard.
I was abandoned because
I'm here right now because...
...I didn't work hard.
I wanted to prove...
...a categorization standard
and efficient application.
A method to kill two birds
with one stone.
And above all else…
…prove it to myself.
Hello.
You're early today.
Do you know of any
cleaners around here?
No.
You didn't go home yesterday?
They're strict with
how the interns dress.
Huh?
I didn't know how to tie it.
Give it to me.
- It's ok.
- Come on, I'll do it for you.
It's really ok.
What if someone sees us?
Shall we go to the rooftop?
[Misaeng]
Wow.
[Episode 2]
This is amazing.
He spent all night on this?
He has integrity.
I'm sure that's all he has.
Why didn't you tell him
what the problem was?
What for?
He won't be here long.
True.
I wonder how the presentation
prep is going.
Who'd want to be partners with him?
But who got him the job?
Beats me.
I'm going over to headquarters.
See you later.
Hello.
- Have you…
- I saw it.
You've proven your
quantity of effort.
Geu Rae.
Why'd you ignore Mr. Oh's folders?
No, there were many iffy
files to put in them.
Geu Rae.
That's the company's manual.
You know what that means?
Everyone understood and agreed.
If there's an issue because of what you did...
...should they ask you about it?
You don't work alone.
I don't know how long
you'll work here.
But keep that in mind
while you're here.
"You don't work alone."
Different individuals, nationalities,
beginning, middle, final phases…
Different eras, people,
old and new…
It was for my little world.
Good morning.
Here…
…I don't work…
…alone.
Thanks to you,
the results were great.
Of course, thanks.
Keep in touch.
Things going ok?
Yes, sir.
- What are you doing this weekend?
- Nothing much.
Let's go hiking with
the executive director.
I forgot about
an alumni gathering.
Does that mean you
don't want to change?
I told you you have
to go high to see far.
I told him about…
I'll…
…ask my friends to go hiking.
Ok.
Excuse me.
Hiking is hiking and work is work.
Hey!
What's with you when I told you
to set the meeting ages ago?
I'm sorry.
You want to be fired?
You think we can't fire interns?
I'm sorry!
Geez!
Mr. Hwang, teach him well!
Gosh!
I'm sorry.
Breathe!
Why are you so worked up?
Every intern gets to you, huh?
Calm down.
You shouldn't have given
him that duty.
He's been sitting around
when I told...
...him to set the meeting
ages ago!
He's thorough.
I guess I can't be
as miserable as you.
Thanks for understanding.
So you heard?
You knew it all along?
I heard this morning.
What?
You know who his connection is?
Geez.
Who is it?
Who got him in?
Who?
The executive director.
Why didn't you tell him
what the problem was?
What for?
He won't be here long.
That was too much yesterday.
Something stinks.
It's octopus.
You didn't go home yesterday?
No.
Did you finish your work?
You should've just gone home.
I have to decide on my
presentation partner.
It's by tomorrow, right?
You'll find a partner
for the interview.
Or maybe not.
The individual presentations
are a bigger issue.
So much work.
I'll get going.
See you later, Geu Rae.
I'll get going too.
That makes me feel weird.
I feel I shouldn't let
that happen to me.
That'll happen if we don't pass
the final presentation interview.
Then what should I do?
What do we have to
do to avoid that?
I was just kidding.
Being an intern at One International
isn't everything.
There are tons of jobs out there.
Anyway you'll have
to find a partner.
You can't do it by yourself.
Everyone's talking about
'working alone' today.
Huh?
- Here.
- Ok.
Categorize it by the
alphabet and nations.
Double-check the costs too.
Look, Geu Rae.
The executive director got him in.
He should have gotten
someone smarter.
I don’t think he put him on
your team with ulterior motives.
He wouldn't have done
it to keep an eye on you.
What are you to him?
He could've done it
to give you trouble.
But he's not that childish.
Even if he hates you.
Ok.
I think he dumped him on your
team since he was in a pickle.
- Dong Sik.
- Yes.
Is the report ready for
the department manager?
Yes.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
- Is it ready?
- Yes, it is.
He knows how to work with Excel.
I asked him to try checking
by cost and nation.
What are you doing, man?
Huh?
Why'd you ask him?
Get your act together.
You asked him to try?
You think this is practice?
I'm sorry.
Finish it by 2PM.
Yes, sir.
Go for lunch.
Mr. Oh.
Is everything ok?
You have no friends, huh?
It looks like a diary
for yourself.
They said we don’t
work alone.
Why'd you ask him?
Get your act together.
But they're forcing
me to be alone.
You asked him to try?
You think this is practice?
He didn't want to
teach me anyway.
What do you mean,
"You don't work alone"?
Huh?
What was that?
There were only
3 types for summer.
Yes, I didn't know
what you wanted...
...so I'm bringing all of them.
I'm on my way up.
Bye.
Thank you.
Here.
It's ok, I'll carry it.
Why?
Huh?
1. Because it's heavy.
2. Because it's heavy.
3. Because it's heavy.
Did you decide on your partner?
Oh right, when is that due?
Come on, it's by tomorrow.
I haven't decided yet either.
What about the others?
They'll probably struggle
not to be the odd one out.
I'm here now.
Yes.
To Mr. Oh?
Ok.
- Dong Sik.
- Yes.
Let's start with the Cambodia case.
Ok.
Sorry, but can you
bring this to Mr. Mun?
Sure.
Yes.
Mr. Oh.
I brought the samples.
Thank you.
Did you decide on your partner?
Not yet.
I was rejected by
Baek Ki just now.
I didn’t even ask, but
he won't be my partner.
- He's smart.
- Huh?
Anyway find a good
partner or you'll be ruined.
I don't care who my partner is.
You're that confident?
It's not that.
Prepare well and pass.
Thank you.
- They're pathetic.
- Huh?
Not you, the people who left this here.
Oh, okay.
I don't care who my partner is.
Young Yi.
Huh?
Be my partner.
You said you don't care who it was.
I'll do my best for both of us.
Geu Rae?
Is there something on my face?
Huh?
Sorry.
I was thinking about something.
You were totally staring at me.
Here.
I forgot to give it to you.
Maybe I should've just asked.
Anyway you'll have
to find a partner.
You can't do it by yourself.
Geu Rae.
I looked everywhere for you.
It had totally slipped my mind…
Have you decided on
your partner yet?
Be my partner.
Why?
Let's be a good team.
What's this?
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Hello.
Here.
I see you skipped lunch.
Uh…
Have you decided on
your partner yet?
No.
Ok.
What the...?
Give it to me.
It's ok…
Partner.
What's all this?
You're popular.
Hold on, please.
Yes, by the 18th.
Ok.
18th…
How come no one's asking?
Young Yi.
You don't have your
partner yet, right?
Be my partner.
I'm saving you.
No one wants to be your partner.
Huh?
Why not?
It's obvious.
You're so good.
Teamwork is key and you'll
totally stand out alone.
I haven't decided yet either.
Let's do it.
[there (x), their (?)]
Geu Rae.
Young Yi.
Let's have a cup of coffee.
Partner?
Yes, I was too busy so
I couldn't decide yet.
- But I'm…
- I have a lot to learn too.
Let's work hard together.
To... gether…
I have a lot to learn too.
Let's work hard together.
Team?
We're a team?
Let's do it.
Let's work hard together.
- Geu Rae.
- Yes.
Are you done proofreading?
Yes, I'm almost done.
Geu Rae.
Let's have a talk.
Sit down.
- Did you decide on your partner?
- Huh?
Why are you blushing like that?
Nothing.
Gee.
Everyone wants you, don't they?
I don't know why but…
You have everything the
other interns want in a partner.
Huh?
No confidence, no comprehension
skills or talent.
But why do they all want me?
It'd be great if both members
of a team got good results.
But if it's impossible...
...it'd be smart to choose a loser.
Did you say "loser"?
Yes.
He would make the other
person look good.
They'll stand out to the judges.
That's why they want you.
Be careful of who
approaches you.
So that was it.
Familiar places I'd visit...
...after my overnight
part-time job.
Their faces, clothing
and directions...
...were all the opposite of mine.
I'd never mixed with students...
...or company employees.
I wanted to be one of them
so desperately...
...that I couldn't see
the ugly truth.
I was still going
the different direction.
I'm alone here too.
Only...
...I didn't know that truth...
...when everyone else did.
All this chaos in order…
I wonder…
…would it ever be possible
to have an agreement?
I have a lot to learn too.
Let's work hard together.
Where are you going during work?
Didn't you hear me?
I'm alone.
What?
So there's nothing I can do.
What did you say?
You said I can't work alone.
I mean the company work.
You asked me if I had friends.
That it looked like
a personal diary.
You were right.
Yes.
I had to do it alone.
I had to be fine alone.
And take responsibility alone.
- What…
- So I don't know anything but alone.
So…
…would you teach me.
Give me a chance.
You need skills for that.
What do you mean?
You know.
No, I don't.
If it's because of my educa…
Do you know how hard
these people worked...
...just to get into the lobby?
All their sweat and
tears just to stay here?
We're in a corrupted world
where those...
...who lack the basics get
on the escalator with lines.
I guess it can't be helped.
But…
…I don't support that world yet.
Sweat, tears and frustration.
How much more should I shed?
Crazy.
What have I done?
- Mr. Kim!
- Huh?
You should've told
me about the cable!
I was about to.
How come you doze
off all the time?
- Mr. Kim!
- Yes.
- Come here.
- Yes, sir.
Why haven't you given
me the file I asked for?
I'll be done soon.
- Why are you so slow?
- Yes.
Everyone's ahead of you!
You started late,
shouldn't you catch up?
Be on your toes.
You know not all
interns will make it.
Yes, sir. I'll fix it.
Don't say that!
This isn't the army, or school!
Let's go for a smoke.
I quit smoking, sir!
Then go get some fresh air!
Geez!
I know you don't
look for shortcuts.
But you need to be quick.
Yes.
- You know I support you, right?
- Yes.
Thank you.
You'll start smoking
again in 2 years.
Yes.
Don't overreact.
I'm sorry.
It's tough to sleep
at night, huh?
No.
Mr. Hwang.
Yeah.
He's here.
Why'd you overreact?
Mr. Hwang.
Listen carefully.
I have the contract
open on my computer.
Delete no. 4, get the head to
approve and bring 2 copies.
Yes, sir.
Bring the intern
weekly report too.
It should be approved today.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
I'll have it sent right away.
Sorry for being late.
Bye.
Geu Rae.
Where is it?
These are receipts.
Paste them on paper and
take it to General Affairs.
- Yes.
- Hurry up.
Sorry, I'll send it soon.
Yes, thank you.
Bye.
Hello.
Hi.
- Geu Rae.
- Huh?
What's that?
Huh?
They're scrap paper documents…
Don’t do that.
If other papers stick,
it might cause problems.
I see.
- Don't throw it all together.
- Yes.
- Check if it's confidential.
- Shred them.
- Yes
Security is an issue these days.
- There was a big mistake recently.
- Yes.
The executive director
yelled at the whole team.
Yes, sir.
I'm done.
- General Affairs.
- I'll be right back.
- Hurry up.
- Yes.
Geu Rae.
Can I borrow the glue?
It's on my desk.
Thank you.
They always lock the supply cabinet.
So I have to beg.
Over there.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm intern Kim Seok Ho.
I'll borrow the glue.
Here it is.
What's this?
Thanks, please send this.
So…
…would you teach me.
Give me a chance.
You need skills for that.
What do you mean?
I think he dumped him on your
team since he was in a pickle.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Sir, what brings you here?
[Draft]
I picked it up in the lobby.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- I think…
- Be quiet.
Let's do well.
Yes, sir.
Get back to work.
Bye.
Hey.
You…
Are you stupid?
I'm sorry.
I told you shred, didn't I?
Get out.
Right now!
You get it now?
Why you don't get a chance?
Why you're not qualified?
Are you still here?
Geu Rae.
Follow me.
Focus.
Hard.
Fool…
Focus.
Geu Rae.
Do two more rounds
and come inside.
I'm an idiot...
Hello?
Huh?
Really?
Ok!
- We made it!
- Really?
- We did it!
That's great!
200,000 won agreement!
Come on.
Congratulations.
They're really thoughtless.
Why isn't he coming by the way?
[Draft]
[Kim Seok Ho]
I'm intern Kim Seok Ho.
I'll borrow the glue.
Treat us to a drink.
Yes, let's do that!
Seok Ho should treat us.
I'll treat you to coffee.
Mr. Oh.
How about a smoke?
Seok Ho is a bit slowpoke...
...but he's meticulous.
He wrote such a good draft, the
executive director complimented him.
He totally saved us.
With his translation and
interpretation skills...
But you know…
What?
He came to borrow supplies.
He did?
He keeps forgetting
the supply key.
He works so hard,
he won't go home.
When he's a newlywed.
Newlywed?
He got married early.
He's the head of a family.
Anyway…
Keep an eye out for him.
So that he won't make any mistakes.
He's being evaluated.
What mistakes?
He's just slow.
He doesn’t make mistakes.
Bye, Young Yi.
See you tomorrow.
Geu Rae?
Yes?
Have you decided on
your partner?
Huh?
I'm intern Han Suk Yool
in Fabric team 2.
I was working
somewhere else.
I hurried over after I heard
about the presentation.
This is so refreshing.
I love factories and harbors.
Alright.
Let me hear your reason.
Huh?
Why do you want me
as your partner?
I started a week earlier
than the other interns.
I majored in mechanical engineering.
And won numerous
contest awards.
But I'm not interested in machines.
I actually like understanding the
principles and conveying it to others.
I mean sales.
You know what I'm saying?
So…
…I wanted to work for
this company.
And they sent me to
the Ulsan factory.
Why?
Because I had already passed.
Yes, you're amazing.
I've seen complicated
manufacturing processses.
I've been to interviews
and met foreign buyers…
I'm not done talking.
Geu Rae.
Geu Rae!
[Kim Seok Ho]
He got married early.
He's the head of a family.
He lef… left?
How could he just go?
I was wrong.
Mr. Oh.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Geu Rae.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
- Dong Sik!
- Huh?
You're not done?
No, I'm not.
Let's wrap up.
Let's go for a drink.
Huh?
But the Vietnamese…
Hey, you don't have to
worry about that.
I told you it has to be done.
Cut it out.
This is Oh Sang Sik.
Oh Sang Sik of
One International.
Regarding our offer…
We set a date.
How can you keep delaying it?
Yeah.
Just do it!
Dang, what are you saying?
Do it!
I said, do it!
Do it.
If you don't, I'll see
you tomorrow morning.
Bye.
- Let's go.
- Huh?
You come too.
Huh?
Uh…
What are you doing?
I'll do it.
Are you upset because
the director visited?
No, man.
Yeah.
Actually right.
I'm upset.
Right, Geu Rae?
So funny.
Laugh.
Dong Sik.
Yes?
You know what?
The folder he organized
was really practical.
Huh?
You can see the other...
...teams' work with his system.
You can see the whole...
...process up to approval.
So it's efficient.
But!
One thing!
You can't write the balance.
But!
It's good for the planning stage.
You're soooooooooooo much
better than the others.
Hey.
That glue incident…
Why bring that up again?
He didn't make the mistake.
Huh?
He didn't do it, man.
There was a misunderstanding, man!
Then who did it?
He touched those documents.
That's…
…a secret.
Gosh.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry.
Are you ok?
Water.
Carry them well.
Mr. Oh!
You must've had a drink today.
Mr. Oh.
I understand it all.
Understand what?
I'm saying!
Yeah.
You should use your
glue, not ours.
What's wrong with you?
You always hat it
when I succeed.
He's really drunk now.
I got a big one,
got a problem?
You feel bad?
Do you?
Huh?
- I'm saying!
- Yeah.
You're going to keep that up?
I want to make a good team.
What I'm saying is!
Give him some glue!
Stop talking about the supplies!
Geez!
Our kid got in trouble...
...because of what yours did!
What did my kid do?
Let's go for the second round.
Don't go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Geu Rae.
Be alert, dude.
Mr. Oh, come on!
I'm fine.
Ok.
Come on.
Hey, kids!
Stop it!
Get out!
You're home?
Did I wake you up?
Sorry.
I barely fell asleep.
Is he sleeping?
No way.
Ok.
Here.
Hey, you.
Daddy?
Here.
The baby is awake now.
I'm going to sleep.
Sleep.
Daddy?
Daddy.
Our kid got in trouble
because of what yours did!
Our kid got in trouble…
He said "our kid…"
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Geu Rae.
[We don't work alone.]
Here are the files.
I'll see you later.
Geu Rae.
I'm going back to the site.
- Geu Rae…
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Be my partner.
[Misaeng]
That loser…?
That big bluffer?
Don't forget.
These five minutes on the
rooftop will change your life.
I sent it since the system was revised.
I had that dish for the
first time thanks to you…
Don’t you remember?
I remember the restaurant.
But he went too?
- OMG.
- What's with…?
Don't ever call me again.
Huh?
The site you're talking about…
You're a pervert there?
New education committee?
Must you do that to him?
Why are you asking me to do it?
Sir!
Is it what the executive director wants?