Not Yet Alive
Episode 4
Sell something to the last guy...
?I want to sell it to?
I heard you were looking for me.
You have something to say?
I have a favor to ask
you about my team.
Favor?
What is it?
Regarding Kim Dong Sik and
the disciplinary committee.
Please reconsider it.
Please.
Let's go.
Unbelievable.
[2nd individual PT topic: What item would
you sell to your partner and why?]
The individual presentation is about
revealing yourself...
...through your partner
whether in a good way or bad way.
If I accept my partner's suggestion,
it'll only make him good...
...if I refuse, it'll make me
look like so petty.
But?
Geu Rae.
You know me.
I won't buy anything you sell me.
I won't.
No matter what.
I won't buy anything.
This jerk doesn't care
about his pettiness at all.
What should I do?
[Misaeng]
[Episode 4]
After the presentation
topic was announced...
...we haven't been able to leave work.
All the data is at work.
And we can also see our
other's process.
Some are already reading catalogues
on items that'd motivate your imagination.
Please let me think like
an elementary school student.
Some surf the net to see if
anything had anything similar.
[Gift ideas]
Hi.
You know someone who was in the
same club as my partner, right?
Some people use their connections.
I can't treat him like a boss.
Does he value site experience?
Or does he hate office work?
Doesn't site work start from the office?
[Oh Sang Sik]
Young Yi!
Tell me your taste, talent, anything.
-Young Yi!
-Sang Hyun.
That's enough.
I need this for my presentation.
Young Yi!
Say something!
Why didn't you just leave it alone?
Just a few months' paycut doesn't?
?mean I'd be fired.
Who care if I'm promoted a bit later?
Geez.
Just say "Sorry, thank you."
I know how much you hate
to ask him for favors.
I don't know why I didn't check
the verbal contract one more time.
I'm going nuts because
I was aware of it.
That's why it's a mistake.
If you make the same mistake
again, that's the limit of yourself.
I know.
Mr. Oh.
Thank you.
Also, I'm sorry.
Hi.
HR called.
I heard it'll be ok.
Yeah.
-Let's sit down.
-Sure.
You won't drink much?
Of course not.
Good job, guys.
Let's go home and
sleep after 3 shots.
You'll need the sleep.
Thank you.
I wonder what
Geu Rae is up to now.
Let's drink up.
[Draft]
Site work is completed
in the office.
Your product info is
in this document.
I need your signature here.
It also requires the signatures
of upper management.
So...
I'll sell this pen which you
can sign off the paper with.
It's lacking.
Yeah.
Mr. Oh.
You sound too desperate.
It's not persuasive.
I thought you left for the day.
Mr. Oh.
Isn't the office as
important as the site?
Of course it is.
Right?
I can't find a line to
respond to site-oriented work.
Why would this big
building be necessary?
Site work is completed in the office.
I agree.
There's no clear line
between site and office for us.
That's how it's like for trade.
You need both.
You run around like crazy at the site.
Then you work like mad in the office.
What?
Nothing.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
I found it.
What time will it end?
Huh?
How long is the test?
I think past the afternoon.
Oh?
Why'd you get so many?
You said your back hurts.
I think I'm doing it?
You'll be doing it.
You'll be jobless starting tomorrow.
You want me to pass or not?
It's ok either way.
It's ok if I fail?
If you pass, I can't
do public work.
I won't be qualified.
I'm in an awkward position.
I don't know whether to
wish you'd pass or fail.
Bye.
Geu Rae.
I'm so nervous.
Young Yi!
It'll be the hardest day here.
Hello.
Let's work hard, Geu Rae.
I mean, please work hard, Geu Rae.
You too, Suk Yool.
Don?t worry about me.
Please stand in order.
We'll go in together.
Get in order.
Go in.
Put the boxes under the desk.
1, 2, 3. Mic test.
1, 2, 3.
Please sit down.
This reminds me of our
presentation interview.
That's Ahn Young Yi, right?
A lot of teams want her.
She'll come to ours.
-Huh?
-What?
She knows my attractiveness.
We'll talk for 10 minutes
and have Q&A for 5.
You can't use any other files.
What's wrong?
Are you ok?
Please be punctual.
What's wrong?
I didn't bring it.
What?
Nice to meet you.
Some of you look familiar.
Some look new.
We may continue to
see each other...
...or this might be your final day.
We need progressive people...
...with positive mindsets.
Anyways, please do your best...
...for our company's future.
First team, Jang Gi Suk and
Gu Hyun Wu, please come out.
Hello.
We're ready to leave
a duck's footprint...
...on the international stage.
So we applied for One International and?
?we're Jang Gi Suk?
?and Gu Hyun Wu.
Nice to meet you.
We should've used ideas like that.
Next.
You think this is a play?
Get your clothes on
and try again.
Oh, Mr. Kim, how are things?
Well, life isn't easy.
We were team 1.
Thank you.
Where'd you get the logo?
Uh?
?it was captured.
It was the only one
available, so Gi Suk did it.
-But Hyun Wu?
-I'm sorry about that.
Next.
-But he?
-Next.
Myanmar is in a location
connecting China and India.
Ever since 2011, they've
been developing gradually.
But crises can be
categorized into risks?
Do you even know you're
mixing risk and crisis?
Risk is the danger of loss.
Crisis is?.
Team 3's strategy is to secure the value chain
through feed grains business for resources.
We participate productions
and secure procurement channels.
Our goal is to become a lead
trader in food resources.
It's nice...
...but you'll be more
suited for an ad company?
Yes, I too think?
This center is expected to
lead the steel industry ...
...and the center of Ukraine's strategic
business and Eastern Europe.
Ok.
How did you end up
applying for our company?
I was interested in trade.
You worked for
a trading company before.
Uh?
?I went to community college.
So I thought it wouldn't
be competitive.
So you thought you could make it
here with your background.
You went to community college, but
your GPA is good and you have talent.
How can you be so unconfident?
You want us to accept you or not?
I'm sorry.
Sorry about what?
Gosh.
Let me correct it.
I never disregarded
this company.
That doesn't work.
Thinking that being honest
will show the sincerity.
People can become honest
to give some excuses.
Regardless of the truth.
Next.
Regarding the development
of solar energy...
...the costs haven't decreased.
According to simulation results
when we build 50k watt...
-Are you sick?
-Don't talk to me.
What's wrong?
Will you be able to speak?
-Then we need to?
-I didn't say I couldn't.
Next, Ahn Young Yi and
Lee Sang Hyun.
Come on out.
Hello.
I'll be giving a presentation on
India's solar energy IPP business plan.
I think we should expand value chains
through networks and investments...
...and present plans to develop
independent power producers.
So I'd like to present ways to
enhance and specialize IPP.
There are 3 ways to enhance IPP.
If we acquire solar energy
providing networks...
...it will naturally bring higher value.
It will lead to better trading values.
We can reinforce the EPC and smart...
...manufacturing development
and create synergy.
You must be wondering
why solar energy.
This graph will explain that.
She's really good.
The solar energy?
How can you secure
materials in India?
Through materials such
as ingot and wafer...
...a value chain will be secured.
What about developing countries?
Polysilicone manufacturers?
Everything is going smooth for her.
She's so solid about her opinion.
She has guts.
Seok Ho was good too.
What about module
manufacturers' M&A?
She's shady.
Huh?
She's very shady.
So module manufacturers' M&A?
?through previous referrals?
?references to?
?developed countries?
What are previous references?
Belgium or Japan?
Yes, I'll tell you.
So module manufacturers' M&A?
...and previous references to
work with developed countries.
I'll explain briefly.
He's making her look good now.
Solar energy attracts many
attentions in the country...
...and the company, Infinity, also has
hundreds of plants in the Philippines
He looks comfortable
since he gave up.
We analyzed the ranking index
based on One International's values...
...and we found out we need to?
?develop businesses and...
?be flexible to changes
and be creative.
So we need to look at IBM's flexible
new business strategy.
They have a radical system, Crossnext,
for direct management and affiliates.
This innovative idea's focus is
on the process, not the actual profits.
He shows presentations textbook.
His words are so clear.
Very logical.
He's good...
...but he's only moving his brains.
He needs to move people's hearts to sell.
That's my presentation regarding...
...One International's future.
Thank you.
I wonder how the test is going.
Gosh.
He won't be shaking.
He's used to it.
It's nothing for him.
Next, Jang Geu Rae
and Han Suk Yool.
Jang Geu Rae's in your team?
Yes.
Don?t touch me.
Suk Yool.
Our presentation will be about...
..."trade trapped in culture..."
It's about profit-generating strategies
through countermining that.
Geu Rae.
What's with him?
He must be very nervous.
So our start is?
Hello?
Suk Yool?
He's not here now.
He's taking his intern test.
Why's everyone looking for him?
Did you take your medication?
What are you doing?
Breathe.
You look sick.
Look up.
Don't sound like you're reading it.
That's how we decided
on our topic.
-Hey.
-Huh?
Breathe.
Where's the fire?
Uh?
I'm sorry.
I need more time.
I'll go take my medication
to calm myself.
Please.
Go take it...
...but I can't give you more time.
The others won't want that.
You have 7 more minutes left.
I'll just?
I'll do it.
Why, that?
Explain it.
Why did you put that there?
Just because?
There's no such thing
as "just because."
You need a plan for every move.
That's called an intention.
Your top-right is blocked.
What will you do about the crisis?
Get rid of unnecessary ones.
Get rid of what?
Eloquence.
I'll get rid of the reason
why I chose Suk Yool.
Being trapped in culture?
?means you're trapped on?
?in the customs, locations.
That's the limitation.
Why's he stammering?
Limitations of environment?
Come on.
He won't make it.
Limitational?
?limitations?
This isn't working.
I need more than ambition.
Geez.
Dad!
Suk Yool!
Are you going to the factory?
Yeah, I'm starting the night shift.
Your hands are black.
It's heavy grease.
Why?
Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm not embarrassed of you.
My boy!
Bye.
You didn't hear the condition?
The whole labor union
will be laid off.
Suk Yool!
My dad went to his office.
Your dad is home, huh?
You must be embarrassed.
No, I'm not embarrassed.
Geez.
Not making them want it is?
?but making need it is our goal.
So that is limitation...
so environment limits...
He's probably taking his intern test.
He won't pick up.
Yeah, he's taking his intern test.
I called too.
He won't pick up.
When does his test end?
-He'll get an office job finally.
-He'll do good.
We should help him leave the site.
He has stage fright.
He took his medication?
There are no?
?not many people?
?in that region?
?so containers aren't filled?
-?full?
-Wait.
It's all good, but hard to listen to.
You need to use more
formal terms.
Not personal ones.
Don't you think it's no good?
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
Have you been to the site?
You need some creative
input about the products.
You haven't gone to
the site, did you?
No.
Interns these days know nothing.
You won't ask for a tour.
You won't go if your
boss doesn't.
Indeed?
?the site is important.
Thanks.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll continue.
Dad, I'm not ashamed of you?
?or the site.
You need to check cases
where FCL doesn't work.
Fulfilling conditions with
forwarding agents are key.
LCL or air transport is possible.
You can send a small quantity to
the consumer directly that way.
When people die in Northern Russian...
It was Suk Yool's time.
His presentation was smooth
and flawless with terms used on sites.
The executives from the
site looked impressed.
Will ancients be able to come?
He was making up for the time
he lost with his eloquence.
He took control.
He knew what he was doing.
He took full control. That's it.
Let me conclude.
Now he had become
a male Young Yi.
He changed into a pro from
a conman in 3 minutes.
Good job.
Gosh.
It was so tough.
The executive director
was so intimidating.
Wasn't Young Yi amazing?
Gosh.
Young Yi!
Don't you want coffee?
He needs to sell.
Baek Ki was great.
I think Young Yi was
best after Seok Ho.
Wasn't Young Yi amazing?
Don't let them hear you.
Anyway she's a girl...
Suk Yool was good.
Young Yi was like a pro.
I liked Geu Rae's paper
and presentation.
Too bad.
It was a good chance.
That's his limit.
It's a miracle he came here.
I liked how he didn't go on.
You're saying that
on purpose.
Don't do that.
Ultimately?
?it'll harm you.
What are you saying?
We think our past is
holding onto us...
...but it's the other way around.
That's how you look now.
Why, you?
Why should a married woman
look at a married man?
Don't look down on me just because
you got promoted earlier.
You still think you're a hottie.
Yeah.
How was Geu Rae?
No way.
He was a moron.
Huh?
I knew Young Yi was a pro.
Mr. Oh, come on.
I'll go to Ijin Chemicals.
Ok!
Trip him if you can't make it.
Huh?
You'll at least get
the pleasure of seeing him trip.
Huh?
The second presentation
interview will start.
As we've told you...
...you'll have to sell to
your partner, and why?
That will be fun, won't it?
If you reject without a good reason,
your score will be deducted.
I bought this for
$600 in Hong Kong.
I'll sell it to you for $350.
I won't buy it.
That's no good reason.
This belt is Korean but
a great imitation?
You love name brands.
You need a wallet?
I think Korean product
quality is better.
You like foreign name brands.
You bragged about buying
nice used items.
What's with him?
Used items is discovering
resources too.
You're talented, Jong Min.
You're also diligent...
...but you lack confidence.
That's because you don't
have anything original.
You're the brand, Jong Min.
Don't imitate others.
Buy this mirror to build?
?you own originality.
I don't imitate others.
What's that?
The item I'll try to
sell you is invaluable.
You can give me however
much you want.
I'll sell an exclusive...
...memory for Young Yi.
This is a day in One International...
...intern Ahn Young Yi's life.
[A day in Young Yi's life]
[Ah]
Gosh.
[Silence, Intern presentation test]
Jang Geu Rae and Han Suk Yool,
please prepare.
Go ahead.
Han Suk Yool will start.
This is what I'll sell
to Jang Geu Rae.
Here.
These are the fabrics
we're making in Ulsan.
These are various
synthetic fibers in...
...including nylon
and polypropylene.
They are creating high value...
...in the 21st century.
One more thing.
This is a book of
work environments?
...losses due to mistakes in orders?
?and analysis of miscommunication.
I'll sell this site info to you.
Make up your mind, Geu Rae.
I hope there are no issues.
Of course not.
Then?
?I will just buy the book.
The fabric?
?I won't take.
Why not?
The book has your analysis...
...so it will save my time.
The fabric can be
acquired anytime.
I don't need to buy yours.
He's good.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
All of this fabric was made...
...through my sweat and tears.
They're made through
a pro's expertise.
I had to put up with being
called a "dog" and "pervert."
Dog?
He knew that?
Oh, my!
Still, it's a crime to touch a
woman's butt without permission.
I didn't touch her butt.
I was touching the fabric.
-I?
-You might've been touching the fabric.
At the same time, you're
admitting you did touch her.
He's funny.
The fabric I wanted to touch?
?happened to be on her butt.
You saw it.
I did.
You touched her butt.
Ok.
Calm down.
What will you do, Geu Rae?
Will you buy it or not?
If I had to study...
...and build expertise
like him to sell fabric?
?then?
?I'd sell it with him.
If we both make it
and come here.
Will you sell it with me?
What will you do, Suk Yool?
Will you sell it with him?
That?
?depends on his item.
Cunning fellow.
Interesting.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, show it to me.
Whatever you sell...
What is he holding?
I'll sell this work slipper to him.
Where is my slipper?
-You don't have one either?
-No.
What's that?
This is Mr. Oh's slipper.
That's mine.
Maybe not.
Look at his shoes.
That crazy?
They're clean.
Office workers need to be...
...neat since we meet clients.
Most of the work
is done in the office.
Look at his slipper again.
What's he doing?
It's worn out.
You can see for yourself.
That dirty?
You can smell the sweat too.
The smell of sweat.
It means the office is part of the site.
I'll sell the...
...combat boot of the office.
Again, wow.
Awesome.
I won't buy it.
The office is not part
of the site.
Do you even know
what the site is?
The site employees
get laid off so easily?
...by office workers who
just sign a document!
You want to see
their combat boot?
They wear construction boots.
To protect their feet in
case heavy tools fall.
That's what you
call combat boots.
I won't buy yours.
You've always emphasized the site.
You've only emphasized the site.
You must be all about how the...
...machines work to make products.
You must be thinking about your...
...expertise and experience
in contests in the field.
What contest?
You won a contest?
I won contests?
But?
?we take the crowded
subway every day for work.
We check the foreign
currency rate every day.
We try to prevent mistakes
made by a single digit.
We check legal documents
for a single sentence.
Will you take responsibility?
We don't just sign a document.
You can't do this now.
There are tons of dialogue.
You also feel small in the process.
Sometimes we stay up all night for
foreign countries to get a single okay.
The items made at the
site start to exist?
?after the process of validating
why they should be made.
They can't exist without
going through the office.
There's no meaningless move.
There's no meaningless
product made by the company.
The reason a stone gets
in trouble is...
...because you've failed
to see intentions.
The reason a product
fails is because...
...you've failed to see
ahead and plan.
When it's in trouble,
just let it die...
...but you should use
them to your benefit.
When a product is a failure,
just let it fail...
...but you should use it to
make a better product.
The office and site are
mutually connected.
There may be mistakes
between them...
...but if you look at the big picture?
?we're all aiming for
the same goal of benefits.
The site in my mind is not...
...different from the one you do.
Applause.
Geu Rae.
Who is it?
Delivery.
Here you go.
Here.
Thank you.
Wait.
Yes.
Throw this out for me.
Excuse me!
-Two more beers.
-Sure!
Your days and nights are reversed.
Get up.
It's time to eat.
We'll need another line.
It's necessary now.
Any news?
I thought a week
would be enough.
The P-bond last time?
[P-bond: Performance Bond]
Ashley Park!
Dang!
Yes.
We'll need it by Thursday.
Geez.
I want to die.
What should I do?
So, Thursday?
I'll make it by Friday.
Thank you.
Bye.
Geu Rae.
Make 3 copies.
I better do it.
Habits are scary.
"Habits" my foot.
You just recently had
a subordinate.
We were thoughtless.
We should've
bought him a beer.
You feel bad too, right?
If Young Yi sits there?
Huh?
Let's think about
the desk location.
Gosh.
When will the announcements be out?
If I don't get extra people
on my team, I won't stay put!
Look.
The restroom's right there.
We can hear toilets being flushed.
We can't place our lovely
female employee here.
You come here.
Change seats.
I'm higher than her.
Then you take my seat.
I'll sit there.
Then next time?
Where'd he go?
You asked for delivery service?
Yes.
Here.
So it's?
[Cha Ji Hyun]
You can leave it with
the lobby info desk.
Here's the receipt.
Thanks.
[Item delivery service]
What happened?
[Geu?]
Dang.
Thanks.
Hello?
It's me.
Yeah.
I got a job.
I made it.
Yeah?
That's great.
Intern Geu Rae becomes a
2-year contract employee.
Wear this one.
It's clean.
You still don't know how to tie it?
Yes.
Men should know how to do this.
Becoming an adult is like that.
You need to be able
to do certain things.
Neck tie.
Humble but clean shoes.
Neat belt.
Those were your dad's rules.
Mom.
What?
You don't know how to do it, huh?
Wear what you used to.
I forgot how to do it.
[Barber shop]
Wearing a tie, dress shoes...
...and suit makes me feel good.
It gives you a sense of tension.
Your suit makes
you feel confident.
The pants are comfortable...
...thanks to the thin fabric.
And?
Geu Rae.
?the handkerchief
my mom gave me.
Don?t wipe your sweat
with your hands.
Don?t just sit anywhere.
Use that to wipe it.
Show with your actions, not talk.
Don't act like an adult,
but be an adult.
Young Yi.
Baek Ki.
I knew it.
I knew you guys would make it.
-Congratulations.
Here.
I guess it's just us three.
Last year, they only chose two.
Hello.
I'm surprised.
Glad to see you, Geu Rae.
Yes.
Young Yi.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You're all here.
Congratulations.
I'm Lee from HR.
Kim Seok Ho made it too.
He'll be working at
the headquarters.
You'll fill out some paperwork and
go see the executive director.
This way, please.
Nice to meet you.
Sit down.
-Young Yi.
-Yes.
Do we know each other?
No, sir.
-Geu Rae?
-Yes?
[Geu Rae: "Yes" in Korean]
You contracted 100,000 won
in 10 days of interning?
?with an item that was
forgotten for 2 years.
Please keep up the good work.
-Suk Yool.
-Yes!
Did your father teach you
site experience is important?
Yes, sir.
For generations, my family?
I have many relatives who
are blue collar workers.
We know the value
of sweat and tears.
We're proud of being site workers.
-Geu Rae?
-Yes.
That's a great attitude.
Thank you.
Baek Ki.
I really liked your
calm presentation.
Thank you.
You want to work in
the Resources team.
Is it because you worked
there as an intern?
No.
I think the company's future is there.
That's why they need elites.
I look forward to your work.
And Geu Rae.
Yes.
You're Geu Rae.
Work hard.
Yes?
These are the work manuals
and the dept. contact info.
Young Yi.
Baek Ki.
Suk Yool.
Geu Rae.
You know how to log in.
Just create an ID and passcode.
Here.
Company ID card.
Ok.
Check your departments.
Yes!
Where are you?
Resources team.
What about you?
Steel team.
Steel?
What about you?
These came in the morning,
so you can check here.
If there are any issues...
-...I'll revise it right away.
-Ok.
Hello.
I'm the new employee,
Jang Geu Rae.
Mr. Oh.
I'm here.
So!
Why you again?
Congratulations.
Geu Rae.
Thank you.
I'll get to work.
Dang.
Hey.
Where's Young Yi?
She?
She went to Resources.
Suk Yool, Fabric.
Baek Ki went to Steel.
Seok Ho went to
the headquarters.
That's how it went.
Hey.
Why'd you come to our team?
I heard you asked for me.
Me?
When did I do that?
-Did you ask for him?
-No.
I didn't ask for you!
Hey!
Hey, you're laughing!
I didn't ask for you!
Tell him, I didn't ask for him.
I didn't either.
Mr. Ko!
I didn't ask for him.
Your team looks happy.
I'm glad Sang Sik
did what he did.
The team looks tight.
I'm glad to put a smile
on your faces too.
Work hard.
What was your name?
Jang Geu Rae.
You only got your GED.
Any work experience?
You know any foreign languages?
What did you do for 26 years?
You can't do anything?
I know.
What did I do for 26 years?
I'm glad Sang Sik did what he did.
The team looks tight.
I'm glad to put a smile
on your faces too.
What's this?
Mr. Oh.
Slacking off from the first day?
No, sir.
Honestly?
?I'm not happy to see you.
As you know?
?we need someone who
can do a million jobs.
I know it, sir.
We should've gotten Young Yi.
You made it anyways.
So try to survive.
You have to survive here.
Surviving means going
towards a complete life.
Complete life?
You might not be familiar.
In the game of Go?
?there's a complete
life and incomplete life.
We're all incomplete lives.